<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Teches</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-15T15:00:42-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/tech/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/tech" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T15:00:42-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T15:00:42-04:00</updated>
    <title>Supreme Court defines when it’s illegal for public officials to block social media critics</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of the Supreme Court building with gavels behind." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/qDcyAhagcgN_zrbQ8UmbSkIMLZQ=/20x0:2021x1334/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73210251/STK463_SCOTUS_A.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Cath Virginia / The Verge | Photos via Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="rHfe8R"&gt;In an &lt;a href="https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/23pdf/22-611_ap6c.pdf"&gt;opinion signed by Justice Amy Coney Barrett&lt;/a&gt;, the Supreme Court established a test to determine when a public official can be considered to be engaging in state action in blocking someone from their social media account. The official must have both “(1) possessed actual authority to speak on the State’s behalf on a particular matter, and (2) purported to exercise that authority when speaking in the relevant social-media posts.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="fNZNNX"&gt;The court issued a unanimous decision in &lt;a href="https://www.scotusblog.com/case-files/cases/lindke-v-freed/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lindke v. Freed&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a case about whether Port Huron, Michigan city manager James Freed violated the First Amendment by &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/4/24/23695910/supreme-court-first-amendment-government-officials-block-social-media-users"&gt;blocking and deleting comments&lt;/a&gt; on his Facebook page from resident Kevin Lindke, who critiqued Freed’s pandemic policies. The test creates a new way to determine if an official can be held liable for violating a citizen’s First Amendment rights through actions on their social media pages. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="w9BQ95"&gt;But it’s not enough for a social media page to simply belong to a public official. Barrett wrote, “The distinction between private conduct and state action turns on substance, not labels: Private parties can act with the authority of the State, and state officials have private lives and their own constitutional rights—including the First Amendment right to speak about their jobs and exercise editorial control over speech and speakers on their personal platforms.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="CBnZir"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The distinction between private conduct and state action turns on substance, not labels&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ZQuj2w"&gt;Barrett suggested that simple disclaimers could make a difference in the determination. “Here, if Freed’s account had carried a label—e.g., ‘this is the personal page of James R. Freed’—he would be entitled to a heavy presumption that all of his posts were personal,” the ruling says, “but Freed’s page was not designated either ‘personal’ or ‘official.’” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1vBbNo"&gt;Katie Fallow, senior counsel of the Knight First Amendment Institute at Columbia University said in a statement the court was “right to hold that public officials can’t immunize themselves from First Amendment liability merely by using their personal accounts to conduct official business.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RRaqoj"&gt;But, Fallow added, “We are disappointed, though, that the Court did not adopt the more practical test used by the majority of the courts of appeals, which appropriately balanced the free speech interests of public officials with those of the people who want to speak to them on their social media accounts. We hope that in implementing the new test crafted by the Supreme Court today, the courts will be mindful of the importance of protecting speech and dissent in these digital public forums.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="yrVTPy"&gt;&lt;a href="https://knightcolumbia.org/cases/knight-institute-v-trump"&gt;The Knight Institute challenged former President Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt; in 2017 over blocking users from his @realDonaldTrump Twitter account. They argued his account was a “public forum” where people could not be excluded for their views, and the lower courts agreed. In 2021, when Trump was no longer in office, the Supreme Court ordered the lower court to vacate a ruling against Trump and &lt;a href="https://knightcolumbia.org/cases/knight-institute-v-trump"&gt;dismiss it as moot&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="qSw3Hb"&gt;Dhillon Law Group partner Gary Lawkowski said in an emailed statement about the new ruling that “the biggest impact of this opinion may not be the formal test set forth in its holding—rather, its language buried in the opinion that effectively creates a safe harbor for public officials who place disclaimers on their social media accounts, providing an easy way for public officials to stay on the ‘personal’ side of the law going forward.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="kjTGmq"&gt;The justices vacated and remanded the case back to the lower court.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="KBHOjw"&gt;
&lt;iframe src="https://embed.documentcloud.org/documents/24483483-scotus-lindke-v-freed/?embed=1&amp;amp;responsive=1&amp;amp;title=1" title="SCOTUS - LINDKE v. FREED (Hosted by DocumentCloud)" width="700" height="450" style="border: 1px solid #aaa; width: 100%; height: 800px; height: calc(100vh - 100px);" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-forms allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101983/supreme-court-public-officials-block-critics-social-media-lindke-v-freed"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101983/supreme-court-public-officials-block-critics-social-media-lindke-v-freed</id>
    <author>
      <name>Lauren Feiner</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T14:18:31-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T14:18:31-04:00</updated>
    <title>PC games start at just $1 in Steam’s spring sale</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/QxhWt9VzPWr3GQZCuEydQvH9L-8=/0x0:920x613/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73210131/steam_spring_sale_2024.0.png" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;From AAA blockbusters to indie cult classics, there are tons of games up to 95 percent off.&lt;/em&gt; | Valve / Steam&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="g0AV6L"&gt;You’d think most gamers would have indulged enough over the long winter season that they wouldn’t want to spend the first moments of spring doing the same, but rainy days are still a thing, yeah? And the grind never truly stops for many of us. That’s why I can appreciate the &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steam spring sale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, happening now through March 21st. It happens around this time every year and offers up to 90 percent off thousands of titles. You can find deals on game-of-the-year-worthy titles like &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1086940/Baldurs_Gate_3/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Baldur’s Gate 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; for $53.99&lt;/a&gt; ($6 off), for example, while &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2344520/Diablo_IV/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diablo IV&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is 50 percent off&lt;/a&gt; no matter which version you buy, whether it’s the base game going for $34.99 or the &lt;em&gt;Ultimate Edition&lt;/em&gt; for $49.99.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="aPUdPk"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"10 great Windows PC games from 2023 ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23979457/best-windows-pc-games-2023"},{"title":"Steam Deck OLED review: better, not faster ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23951655/steam-deck-oled-review"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="MORknD"&gt;It’s also a great chance to check out older titles you may have passed on, such as &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1091500/Cyberpunk_2077/?snr=1_4_springsale__629"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (50 percent off, down to $29.99) or &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2369390/Far_Cry_6/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Far Cry 6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for $14.99 ($45 off). There are tons of cult classics, indie hits, and other low-key titles on sale starting at just $1, too, like the undying &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/550/Left_4_Dead_2/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Left 4 Dead 2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. We’re not seeing any discounts on the &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/steamdeck/"&gt;Steam Deck&lt;/a&gt; or any of the VR headsets in &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/vrhardware/"&gt;Steam’s hardware store&lt;/a&gt;, unfortunately, but be sure to explore more games from the sale if you’re looking for something new to play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="cuowaA"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12193366"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="YOuFUD"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12193982"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="O8BIEr"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10197689"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="BoKVbF"&gt;Considering &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24089999/apple-macbook-air-m3-announced-13-15-inch"&gt;Apple has officially signaled the M1 MacBook Air’s death knell&lt;/a&gt;, Walmart’s latest sale on the outgoing model feels like a last call. The retailer is offloading the &lt;strong&gt;8GB RAM, 256GB SSD MacBook Air with M1&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FApple-MacBook-Air-13-3-inch-Laptop-Space-Gray-M1-Chip-8GB-RAM-256GB-storage%2F609040889&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$699&lt;/a&gt;, which is $300 off compared to its original price and $50 cheaper than the $749 it’s often gone for toward the end of its retail run. It’s a new all-time low price, which we predicted would happen, but perhaps not this soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="MWFMry"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Apple’s new M3 chips have big GPU upgrades focused on gaming and pro apps","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/30/23938676/apple-m3-chip-gpu-upgrade-hardware-accelerated-ray-tracing-gaming-specs-release-date"},{"title":"The MacBook Air’s wedge is truly gone — and I miss it already","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24090112/macbook-air-wedge-laptops-design"},{"title":"Look at this bonkers, beautiful Mac-iPad hybrid","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24090192/look-at-this-bonkers-beautiful-mac-ipad-hybrid"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="T3p1Cm"&gt;Although it’s discontinued, the M1 Air is still getting support and can still serve as a perfectly capable laptop for someone dipping their toes into the MacBook waters for the first time, or perhaps to replace an aging Intel-based model. It’s up to most basic school, work, and browsing tasks for those with lighter needs who would benefit from the long battery life (up to 18 hours) and power efficiency afforded by the Apple-made chipset. I’ve even found this memory-starved model capable of lightweight 4K video editing, photo editing, and other creative tasks. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="4RwrHd"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:9737407"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="gKBJ9y"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="actionbox" data-anthem-component-data='{"title":"Verge Deals on X","description":"Join more than 50,000 followers and keep up with the best daily tech deals with @vergedeals","label":"Follow us!","url":"http://bit.ly/2JzR5Ud"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;h2 id="6DvR1d"&gt;A few more ways to save&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="LzC9S2"&gt;The keyboard has become something of a fashion statement on the modern desk, and&lt;strong&gt; 8Bitdo’s wireless retro mechanical keyboard &lt;/strong&gt;— down to $84.99 ($15 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CCP8KYGG/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; — offers a distinct look resembling a Super Nintendo for those who favor a nostalgic aesthetic&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;The tenkeyless board offers both 2.4GHz and Bluetooth wireless connectivity options (in addition to wired), an integrated volume knob, and ships with two oversized buttons that you can program to execute your favorite macros and other custom functions. The hot-swappable PCB allows you to switch out the Kailh Box V2 switches with ease, too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="UsUAyM"&gt;If you own a Samsung Galaxy smartphone and you need an alternative to AirTags, it’s worth considering a&lt;strong&gt; four-pack of Galaxy SmartTag2 trackers. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://howl.me/clP25RGFVQ5"&gt;Samsung has it down to $74.99&lt;/a&gt; ($25 off). Similar to Apple’s version, SmartTag2 uses Bluetooth ultra-wideband for pinpoint compass-guided directions to your lost items. That functionality requires a&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Galaxy Note 20 Ultra, S21 Plus and Ultra or newer, or a Galaxy Z Fold 2 and newer, although you can use any Samsung phone with SmartThings Find to track down the last known location. The battery can last up to 500 days and up to 40 percent longer in a low-power state, Samsung says, and the trackers can survive a bit of rain or dust with IP67 protection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="R4Byuf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22958216/kitchen-tools-personal-gear-gadgets-favorites"&gt;favorite&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;’s Allison Johnson, the &lt;strong&gt;Breville Barista Express&lt;/strong&gt; is an attractive and versatile espresso machine that &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Breville-BES870XL-Barista-Express-Espresso/dp/B00DS4767K/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clP4iJVM1gt"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://westelm.e54b.net/c/482924/267856/4336?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.williams-sonoma.com%2Fproducts%2F2101673%2F&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Williams Sonoma&lt;/a&gt; have down to $559.99 right now ($140 off). It grinds its own beans at whichever consistency you desire and has an integrated microfoaming milk frother, both helping to make delectable cups of the good stuff with a presentation that will make you forget all about those expensive Starbies runs. It’s also easy to clean and maintain, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/10/23864688/breville-barista-express-home-espresso-maintenance"&gt;says Allison&lt;/a&gt;, whether you’re using its self-cleaning option or opening it up for a deep scrub.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="7enZCU"&gt;If you’re looking for a flagship-rivaling smartphone that simply does exactly what you need it to, we see nothing wrong with the &lt;strong&gt;OnePlus 12R.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s already a great value at $499.99 for the unlocked 128GB storage model, and both &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CW9R75NB/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clP3JT0Cvjg"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt; are throwing in a $100 gift card to sweeten the deal. We wish it had wireless charging and more substantial ingress protection compared to midrange contemporaries from Samsung and Google. Otherwise, it’s hard to find a smartphone at this price with its display quality and size (the 6.78-inch, 1080p display has a 120Hz variable refresh rate), not to mention its respectable photography potential and the strong processing power of the Snapdragon 8 Gen 2. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24072383/oneplus-12r-review-screen-camera-price"&gt;Read our review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;aside id="aSZQAL"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="newsletter" data-anthem-component-data='{"slug":"deals"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101003/steam-spring-sale-m1-macbook-air-breville-barista-express-espresso-machine-deal-sale"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101003/steam-spring-sale-m1-macbook-air-breville-barista-express-espresso-machine-deal-sale</id>
    <author>
      <name>Quentyn Kennemer</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T13:39:32-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T13:39:32-04:00</updated>
    <title>Zoomers are turning on the TikTok famous congressman who voted to ban the app</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Debt Ceiling Vote" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/4LyNetd4kOn0mEi7Y8IURzyI5cQ=/0x0:8640x5760/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73210023/1258639155.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Tom Williams/CQ-Roll Call, Inc via Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="UgxORa"&gt;Until relatively recently, Rep. Jeff Jackson, a freshman Democratic congressman from North Carolina, had more than 2.5 million followers on TikTok. Jackson’s follower count dropped by over 100,000 virtually overnight — as did his esteem among some of TikTok’s young users — after he &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24097125/house-bill-vote-tiktok-ban-china-bytedance-divestment"&gt;voted to ban the app&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gt7WOk"&gt;The bill passed with 352 votes, but to the legions of TikTokers who &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093308/tiktok-congress-ban-push-notification"&gt;called their representatives&lt;/a&gt; to urge them not to ban the app, Jackson’s vote feels like a unique betrayal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="tlQCAN"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="tiktok-embed" cite="https://www.tiktok.com/@noahglenncarter/video/7346291613947186475" data-video-id="7346291613947186475" data-embed-from="oembed" style="max-width:605px; min-width:325px;"&gt; &lt;section&gt; &lt;a target="_blank" title="@noahglenncarter" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@noahglenncarter?refer=embed"&gt;@noahglenncarter&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt;An update on Jeff Jackson. Hes losing everything right now because he boted yes &lt;a title="keeptiktok" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/keeptiktok?refer=embed"&gt;#keeptiktok&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="jeffjackson" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/jeffjackson?refer=embed"&gt;#jeffjackson&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="tiktokban" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/tiktokban?refer=embed"&gt;#tiktokban&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="foryou" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/foryou?refer=embed"&gt;#foryou&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;a target="_blank" title="♬ Stargazing (Slowed + Reverb) - Marcelo De Carvalho" href="https://www.tiktok.com/music/Stargazing-Slowed-Reverb-7221312697249531906?refer=embed"&gt;♬ Stargazing (Slowed + Reverb) - Marcelo De Carvalho&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/section&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;script async="" src="https://www.tiktok.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="2x31GH"&gt;On Wednesday, Jackson posted a video on X laying out the rationale for his vote. “I don’t think TikTok is going to be banned,” he began. If the bill passes in the Senate, Jackson said in the video, he thinks the likeliest scenario is that “TikTok will be sold for billions of dollars and will continue to operate.” His opposition, he continued, is not with TikTok itself but with China’s national security laws and the sway the Chinese government has over TikTok’s algorithms — and, potentially, over American politics. “We got a big example of how that power could be used last week, and it wasn’t subtle,” Jackson said, referring to the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093308/tiktok-congress-ban-push-notification"&gt;pop-up notification&lt;/a&gt; TikTok served users that warned Congress is “planning a total ban of TikTok.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5tu5IT"&gt;Jackson also acknowledged TikTok users’ concern that Congress is attempting to pass legislation that could potentially ban an app they don’t even understand. “I know a lot of you have seen some members of Congress be deeply uninformed about this because they don’t use TikTok and they don’t care,” he said. “But I do use it, and I think we can solve this problem and keep marching on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="o2sxAg"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet"&gt;
&lt;p lang="en" dir="ltr"&gt;The best-case scenario for TikTok is that it continues to operate but is no longer owned - and potentially controlled - by an adversarial country. &lt;a href="https://t.co/JsXHliZACJ"&gt;pic.twitter.com/JsXHliZACJ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;— Rep. Jeff Jackson (@JeffJacksonNC) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/JeffJacksonNC/status/1767936238625984739?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;March 13, 2024&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="1dBQ6P"&gt;TikTok users, meanwhile, weren’t happy with Jackson’s explanation. The comments section of his &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@jeffjacksonnc/video/7345130701836094762?lang=en"&gt;most recent video&lt;/a&gt;, posted on Monday, is full of people calling him a hypocrite. Some of the comments suggest that Jackson originally cross-posted his post-vote explanation video on TikTok, and then deleted it after a wave of backlash. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="36hLhN"&gt;“WITHOUT TIKTOK YOUR NOTHING!!! @Jeff Jackson,” said one irate viewer. “SELLLOUUUUTTTTTTTTTTT,” said another. Jackson’s office did not immediately respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="DSYikU"&gt;Jackson grew his following on TikTok by posting explainers on everything from the Russia-Ukraine war to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23635692/silicon-valley-bank-svb-collapse-explainer-startups-venture-capital"&gt;the Silicon Valley Bank collapse&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Ybqtdk"&gt;In interviews with &lt;a href="https://rollcall.com/2023/04/05/rep-jeff-jackson-congress-biggest-tiktok-star-sees-the-app-as-a-tool-for-transparency/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roll Call&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;and &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2023/04/11/tiktok-congressman-jeff-jackson/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, he’s touted TikTok as a way of educating constituents about the ins and outs of the legislative process. The app, he’s said, is good for transparency. Since the White House has forbidden federal employees, including members of Congress, from having TikTok on their government-issued phones, Jackson has the app installed &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2023/04/11/tiktok-congressman-jeff-jackson/"&gt;on a separate personal device&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="y9ag1X"&gt;Last April, Jackson told &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2023/04/11/tiktok-congressman-jeff-jackson/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;he’d vote for legislation banning TikTok “as a last resort,” though he’d prefer that ByteDance sell the app so he — and his constituents — can keep using it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Mwj9d8"&gt;For now, Jackson can still post, although his posts are being brigaded with comments like “&lt;strong&gt;                 &lt;/strong&gt;.” And despite his recent drop in followers, he remains the most-followed member of Congress on TikTok.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101851/tiktok-ban-vote-jeff-jackson-sell-bytedance"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101851/tiktok-ban-vote-jeff-jackson-sell-bytedance</id>
    <author>
      <name>Gaby Del Valle</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T12:26:31-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T12:26:31-04:00</updated>
    <title>Microsoft is stuffing pop-up ads into Google Chrome on Windows again</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Screenshot of a Bing pop-up on Windows" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/XgfK1JBj_QVULcVQ4gSx7E_CPEI=/0x0:1320x880/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209773/microsoftbingpopup.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image composite: &lt;a class="ql-link" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/antivirus/comments/1beg1bi/is_this_microsoft_bing_popup_malware/" target="_blank"&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt; (TheDyslexicCow) / Tom Warren / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="obIFaN"&gt;Microsoft is once again injecting pop-ups into Google’s Chrome browser in a bid to get people to switch to Bing. The software giant first &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/30/23851902/microsoft-bing-popups-windows-11-malware"&gt;introduced malware-like pop-up ads&lt;/a&gt; last year with a prompt that appeared over the top of other apps and windows. After pausing that notification to address “unintended behavior,” the pop-ups have returned again on Windows 10 and 11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mwvdBw"&gt;Windows users have reported seeing the new pop-up in recent days, advertising Bing AI and Microsoft’s Bing search engine inside Google Chrome. If you click yes to this prompt, then Microsoft will set Bing as the default search engine for Chrome. These latest prompts look like malware, and once again have &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/antivirus/comments/1beg1bi/is_this_microsoft_bing_popup_malware/"&gt;Windows users asking&lt;/a&gt; if they are legit or nefarious. Microsoft has confirmed to &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; that the pop-ups are genuine and should only appear once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="cFVYZn"&gt;“This is a one-time notification giving people the choice to set Bing as their default search engine on Chrome,” says Caitlin Roulston, director of communications, in a statement to &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;. Roulston framed the pop-up as offering perks to Windows users, since they can get more chat turns in Copilot if they accept the notification. “We value providing our customers with choice, so there is an option to dismiss the notification.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/WsQ3wNO9p-oLw4CESv0J73z5Noc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24883698/bingpopup0.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Screenshot by Tom Warren / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Microsoft used similar pop-ups in Windows last year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="3JI6ak"&gt;If Microsoft really valued providing Windows users with choice, then it would offer up an easy way to disable these pop-ups for good. There are a variety of ways that Microsoft attempts to prompt Windows users into switching to Bing and Edge, making it difficult to avoid them through tweaking settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EqvcBs"&gt;I’ve been growing increasingly frustrated with Microsoft’s attempts to aggressively push pop-up ads on Chrome users in recent years. Microsoft has been using pop-ups inside Chrome, on the Windows taskbar, and elsewhere to promote its own services. Microsoft even once &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/21310611/microsoft-edge-browser-forced-update-chromium-editorial"&gt;forced people into Edge after a Windows Update&lt;/a&gt;, and it regularly presents a full-screen message to try to get Windows users to switch to Bing and Edge after updates are applied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="XoF4t7"&gt;Earlier this year, Microsoft even &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/16/24074712/microsoft-edge-automatic-chrome-import-data-bug-fix"&gt;had to fix an issue&lt;/a&gt; where its Edge browser was automatically importing browsing data and tabs from Chrome without consent. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24054329/microsoft-edge-automatic-chrome-import-data-feature"&gt;I personally experienced the bug&lt;/a&gt;; after I rebooted my PC for a Windows update, Microsoft Edge automatically opened with the Chrome tabs I was working on before the update.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="734GG7"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/30/23851902/microsoft-bing-popups-windows-11-malware"&gt;I wrote in August&lt;/a&gt; that I was “counting the days until the next annoying pop-up appears,” and here it is a little over six months later. I’m still hoping Microsoft will eventually give up with these annoying pop-ups and respect Windows users’ choice to pick whichever search engine and browser they wish to use.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101887/microsoft-bing-popups-windows-11-google-chrome"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101887/microsoft-bing-popups-windows-11-google-chrome</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T12:14:39-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T12:14:39-04:00</updated>
    <title>Uber and Lyft to leave Minneapolis over ‘deeply flawed’ pay rules</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Uber company name written on a multicolored background." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/O6GRXLzYMSHtZfvE982hb1v3olc=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209741/acastro_STK106__01.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration by Alex Castro / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="TqD504"&gt;Uber and Lyft are pulling their services out of Minneapolis after the city council passed an ordinance that will increase drivers’ pay. Both companies say they will no longer offer ridesharing services in the city when the ordinance goes into effect on May 1st.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="PqTda0"&gt;The ordinance, which guarantees drivers a minimum rate of $1.40 per mile and 51 cents per minute while carrying a rider, was &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/minneapolis-city-council-uber-lyft-rideshare-ordinance-vote/"&gt;first passed last week&lt;/a&gt; but &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/minneapolis-mayor-vetoes-minimum-wage-rideshare-ordinance/"&gt;later vetoed&lt;/a&gt; by Minneapolis Mayor Jacob Frey. The City Council &lt;a href="https://minnesotareformer.com/2024/03/14/minneapolis-council-overrides-mayors-veto-of-uber-and-lyft-minimum-rates/"&gt;voted 10–3 to override&lt;/a&gt; the veto on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xms1gF"&gt;Lyft spokesperson CJ Macklin calls the ordinance “deeply flawed,” as &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/minneapolis-mayor-discusses-recently-passed-rideshare-ordinance/"&gt;the rates were determined&lt;/a&gt; before the state released a study detailing how much drivers would have to be paid to earn Minneapolis’ $15.57 per hour minimum wage. &lt;a href="https://dli.mn.gov/sites/default/files/pdf/TNC_driver_earnings_analysis_pay_standard_options_report_030824.pdf"&gt;The study&lt;/a&gt; analyzed over 18 million trips taken in 2022. &lt;a href="https://www.startribune.com/minnesota-uber-and-lyft-drivers-often-earn-less-than-minimum-wage-state-study-says/600349568/"&gt;It found&lt;/a&gt; that drivers could earn the city’s minimum wage — while also accounting for health insurance, paid leave, and retirement savings — with rates of $1.21 per mile and 49 cents per minute, lower than what the city council approved. &lt;em&gt;“&lt;/em&gt;We support a minimum earning standard for drivers,” Macklin says, “but it should be done in an honest way that keeps the service affordable for riders.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="o7pPAD"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"How Uber learned to stop fighting and play nice with taxis ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/26/23888950/uber-taxi-driver-referral-third-party-los-angeles"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zaxeQX"&gt;Uber spokesperson Josh Gold similarly tells &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; that it’s “disappointed the Council chose to ignore the data and kick Uber out of the Twin Cities.” The company says the move will leave 10,000 drivers without work. “We know that by working together with all stakeholders — drivers, riders and state leaders — we can achieve comprehensive statewide legislation that guarantees drivers a fair minimum wage, protects their independence and keeps rideshare affordable,” Gold says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ulGO1V"&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/minneapolis-uber-lyft-ridehailing-minimum-wage-d60db6a2e2580dc1d93c438a8cffa5ee"&gt;statement provided to &lt;em&gt;The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Associated Press&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Minneapolis council member Jamal Osman said that affordable rides shouldn’t come at the expense of the drivers’ welfare. “Drivers are human beings with families,” he said, “and they deserve dignified minimum wages like all other workers.” He added that the “vote showed Uber, Lyft, and the Mayor that the Minneapolis City Council will not allow the East African community, or any community, to be exploited for cheap labor.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Q3IWSX"&gt;Last year, Minnesota Governor Tim Walz &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/minnesota-veto-lyft-uber-pay-6407e997298464c931d8c0c1e6e371a0"&gt;vetoed a bill that would’ve&lt;/a&gt; increased wages for Uber and Lyft drivers across the state, saying at the time it could “make Minnesota one of the most expensive states in the country for rideshare.” With both Lyft and Uber saying they’ll leave Minneapolis, concerns remain about how people will get around the city and the &lt;a href="https://www.startribune.com/article/600350241/?refresh=true"&gt;effect it will have on those&lt;/a&gt; with disabilities. A report from &lt;em&gt;Axios&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.axios.com/local/twin-cities/2024/03/14/uber-lyft-alternatives-minneapolis-legislation"&gt;revealed that Minneapolis&lt;/a&gt; only has 39 licensed cab drivers, far less than the 2,000 cab drivers in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="za90J7"&gt;Some areas already set a minimum wage for ridesharing and food delivery drivers. Last year, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/29/23895637/uber-doordash-grubhub-nyc-delivery-worker-minimum-wage-ruling"&gt;New York City enacted a new rule&lt;/a&gt; that will increase drivers’ minimum wage to around $18 an hour to start, while &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/29/23661878/seattle-gig-workers-paid-sick-time-uber-eats-doordash"&gt;Seattle has a rule&lt;/a&gt; that requires companies like DoorDash, Uber, and Instacart to give delivery drivers paid sick time off. Uber &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/3/16/22334771/uber-uk-drivers-workers-benefits-employees-decision"&gt;also started paying&lt;/a&gt; drivers a minimum wage in the United Kingdom in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101774/uber-lyft-leave-minneapolis-minimum-pay"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101774/uber-lyft-leave-minneapolis-minimum-pay</id>
    <author>
      <name>Emma Roth</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T11:27:02-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T11:27:02-04:00</updated>
    <title>How to make an Apple Vision Pro Persona</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Vector collage showing different aspects of making a Persona on the Vision Pro." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/PuDAt2mir0wigmgijdrowZoqDXg=/0x0:3000x2000/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209576/HT047_VISION_PRO_PERSONA.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Samar Haddad for The Verge | Photo by Apple&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="fpjYR7"&gt;Now that you’ve got your &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24054862/apple-vision-pro-review-vr-ar-headset-features-price"&gt;$3,500 Apple Vision Pro&lt;/a&gt;, gone through the tutorial, and gotten the hang of things, it’s time to do the next best thing: make a Persona.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GS2EGY"&gt;Personas are Apple’s name for a digital avatar of yourself for video calls. Or, in &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/persona/#:~:text=Persona%20is%20a%20natural%20representation,upper%20body%2C%20and%20facial%20expressions."&gt;Apple’s words&lt;/a&gt;, a “natural representation of you that you can use to connect with others.” Aside from FaceTime, your Persona is also used with the &lt;a href="https://duet-cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/0x0:2700x1800/1440x960/filters:focal(1350x900:1351x901):format(webp)/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25255977/246965_vision_pro_AKrales_0002.jpg"&gt;EyeSight feature&lt;/a&gt; — you know, the ghostly eyes that appear on the Vision Pro’s front display. It’s created using image captures and 3D measurements of your head, face, upper body, and facial expressions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="q5ncJe"&gt;But before you go run off and make a Persona, there’s one thing to keep in mind. Right now, Personas are in beta which means... they look kind of cursed. I’ve heard mine described as a soft focus ‘70s-style portrait and as a memorial photo like the ones used in obituaries. Hair often looks blocky, sort of like a non-playable character in a PlayStation 3 game. You’ll recognize yourself, but it won’t quite get everything right. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="QnG8zm"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Apple Vision Pro review: magic, until it’s not ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/24054862/apple-vision-pro-review-vr-ar-headset-features-price"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="aSMc9M"&gt;Personas have gotten a bit better since launch, thanks to software updates, but mine is still not what I’d call a fully “natural representation” of me. But it’s okay — you don’t &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; to make one, especially if you’re worried about privacy, since Apple is essentially taking photos of you to generate the Persona.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;(You can read Apple’s official Persona privacy policy &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/persona/#:~:text=Persona%20is%20a%20natural%20representation,upper%20body%2C%20and%20facial%20expressions."&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="mSEHNC"&gt;How to begin&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="miVSvV"&gt;You’ll get prompted to create your Persona while you’re setting up the Vision Pro. But in the event you skipped that to explore other features, here’s how to get started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="JMNaQT"&gt;Press the digital crown, look at &lt;strong&gt;Settings&lt;/strong&gt;, and pinch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="yOWF2M"&gt;Scroll down and select &lt;strong&gt;Persona.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="PXNRq4"&gt;Select &lt;strong&gt;Get Started.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="AQQv2C"&gt;You’ll be prompted to hold out your hands. Do this, and then wait until you hear the cue to take off your headset. But don’t take it off quite yet, because... &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="DZ3TZf"&gt;...a video will pop up with some pointers. You may want to watch it, because it’s helpful for getting a sense of what you’re supposed to do — especially since you will now take off the headset to continue making your Persona. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Screenshot of the Persona Menu within the Vision Pro" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/A8Kp3N0427Dob4hcKLQAbcF7tt0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25335981/IMG_0041.PNG"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Screenshot: Victoria Song / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;After you’ve made your Persona, you can edit it or recapture. I encourage doing it a few times!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="vcVcjN"&gt;Once you take off the headset, this is a good time to fix your hair and your makeup (if you wear any). You might also want to remove dangly earrings, earbuds, glasses, and hats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="qsSLqt"&gt;Hold the Vision Pro at eye level with the front display facing toward you. Make sure your entire face is within the circle that appears. Make sure that you’re holding the Vision Pro by its frame and not the light seal or straps. Those attach magnetically and can pop off if you’re not careful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="h2iIBS"&gt;Follow the directions to slowly look left, right, up, and down. There are arrows and sounds that give you clear visual and audio cues as to where to look and whether you’re doing it correctly. You may hear instructions to redo portions or adjust your facial position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="oVEQZi"&gt;You’ll also be asked to smile with your mouth open and closed, raise your eyebrows, and close your eyes. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="DjycVF"&gt;When capture is done, put the headset back on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div id="gPYhQU"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12279322"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="WnKBJl"&gt;You should see a preview of your Persona. Bask in its cursed image. But there are still some things you can do to edit how it appears. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="Phk7Sa"&gt;You can select lighting styles. Natural is, well, natural, while Studio brightens everything up and Contour adds some extra shadowing. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="WgySFI"&gt;There are also sliders at the bottom that let you adjust the photo temperature and brightness. If you wear glasses, this is where you can swipe through various styles. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="2a6Bcf"&gt;When you’re done, tap &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt;. If it’s too cursed, you can hit &lt;strong&gt;Recapture&lt;/strong&gt; and go through the process again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mgRYkE"&gt;It’s okay if you need to try making your Persona a second time. I’ve made three thus far, and here are a couple of tips:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="ljF8sz"&gt;Open your eyes wide and exaggerate your facial expressions more than you normally would during capture. Inside the headset, I tend to have “resting sleepy face” and that makes my Persona look a little stoned. Starting out with wider eyes and bigger facial expressions has, according to my friends, resulted in my Persona looking more like me. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="8DTgQO"&gt;Make sure you have good, even lighting. If you have funky light or really strong backlighting, you might end up with odd shadowing. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Screenshot of two people talking on FaceTime with Personas in Vision Pro" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3smNjVij5eZKfJ8FOYU-EAS29n0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25336348/IMG_0095.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Screenshot: Wes Davis / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wes and I regularly FaceTime to make silly faces with our new Personas.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mGG18C"&gt;At this point, it’s imperative that you call your best friend or loved ones on FaceTime. This way, you can listen to them roast you. Better yet, if you know someone who has a Vision Pro, call them and the two of you can have a jolly time laughing at how your Personas turned out. I did this with our weekend news editor Wes Davis, and we had a great time guffawing over how his mustache would not move. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="33rrUZ"&gt;So long as you don’t go in with too high expectations, Persona FaceTimes can be a fun conversation starter with people you know. Have a lot of people laughed at my expense? Sure, but I’d be lying if I said I didn’t have a blast in the process. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gQhg6H"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24100674/apple-vision-pro-persona-how-to"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24100674/apple-vision-pro-persona-how-to</id>
    <author>
      <name>Victoria Song</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T11:26:53-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T11:26:53-04:00</updated>
    <title>Lenovo ThinkPad X1 Fold 16 review: setting the bar for foldables</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;Its beautiful 16-inch OLED display morphs into a 12-inch laptop, but do splurge for the ‘optional’ keyboard and folio. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text c-end-para" id="gX4lXL"&gt;Early into testing Lenovo’s ThinkPad X1 Fold 16 Gen 1, I briefly regretted purchasing its dual-display &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23794761/lenovo-yoga-book-9i-review"&gt;Yoga Book 9i&lt;/a&gt;. I bought it months ago, and it improved my day-to-day life in so many unexpected ways, I told myself I’d never buy another single-screen laptop. But then, the X1 Fold showed up with its folding OLED screen and tried to turn me into that Distracted Boyfriend meme as I transformed it from a 12-inch netbook to a 16-inch drawing tablet while shouting to my partner from downstairs, “Come look at this laptop!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2bL6sm"&gt;We spent some time folding and unfolding the laptop, sticking the curved centerfold close to our eyeballs so we could see how smooth the seam was. We quickly forgot that it folded in half as we played games and watched movies with it unfolded. I ultimately realized I had already bought the right laptop &lt;em&gt;for me&lt;/em&gt;, but the ThinkPad X1 Fold is a folding laptop done right, so hell yeah, I wanted it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="HIfIjC"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12277486"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ZaYRUk"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22175087/lenovo-thinkpad-x1-fold-review"&gt;Lenovo released its first X1 Fold in 2020&lt;/a&gt;, but it was too ahead of its time. Its well-built and beautiful OLED display couldn’t make up for a host of issues: short battery life; a small and dim display; an underpowered processor; a $2,500 starting price sans stylus or keyboard; and the fact that it didn’t always recognize whether it was being used as a tablet or as a laptop. Lenovo fixed almost all of those issues with its 2024 Fold. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="IDzsDo"&gt;The display is much bigger and much brighter. The battery life has doubled. The processing and integrated graphics performance have shot up like a puck hitting the bell atop a strongman carnival game. The design is even more gorgeous. Lenovo also threw in a stylus, and thank goodness it did because this laptop is as good a drawing tablet as it is a netbook. It is a better laptop in every way, except in price. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WvlWEz"&gt;Lenovo is still asking for $2,500, minimum, but the price is more justified this time around. The one caveat being it wants another $300 for a Bluetooth keyboard and kickstand folio, which are both crucial to the Fold experience. Its virtual keyboard works fine, but it’s not ideal for typing anything more than a few search phrases into Google. Plus I needed the folio to prop the ThinkPad Fold up next to my 27-inch monitor, which is how I use my Yoga Book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="k28p7v"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="imageslider:12277503"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="IT1UWX"&gt;Sure, I could drop $20 on a tablet stand big enough to accommodate the Fold’s 16-inch display, but it wouldn’t double as a keyboard cover, and it most certainly wouldn’t be as portable. I spent about an hour searching for a third-party magnetic keyboard but couldn’t find something suitable. Even if I did find one (I’m convinced they don’t exist) and it precisely covered the Fold’s bottom half, it probably wouldn’t tell the device to switch into laptop mode when attached. (I tried this with the Yoga Book’s included keyboard — no dice, and it’s too big for the Fold.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="qhc2Vi"&gt;So not only is it annoying that I’d have to buy Lenovo’s “optional” keyboard and folio to get the most out of this foldable laptop, but also the trackpad was frustrating to use. I had to clean my finger oils off the trackpad frequently or else it would miss too many swipes. That’s disappointing since typing on the keyboard is as nice as you’d expect from a ThinkPad or any other Lenovo laptop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A close-up showing the rounded corner of a foldable laptop display." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/KfOG7UH4dEUy47wWNmwPxj2kHXk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25305797/247033_Lenovo_ThinkPad_X1_Fold_16_JNelius_0009.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;No centerfold creases. No creaking noises.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="HoRgoC"&gt;Lucky for me that I most often used the ThinkPad X1 Fold the same way I use my Yoga Book 9i: connected to my monitor with a standalone keyboard and mouse. In that mode, the Fold worked better than my Yoga Book in some ways. Unlike the Yoga Book, which has two separate screens, the Fold’s hinge is behind its display and doesn’t create a gap in the middle of a paragraph, and I cannot emphasize enough how nice it was not to have to deal with &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; kind of screen gap during my time with the Fold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lWIbJK"&gt;However, my Yoga Book 9i’s two 13.3-inch physical displays do provide a larger workspace than the Fold, whether oriented horizontally or vertically. I also prefer how I can adjust the angle of the Book’s top screen to match my external monitor. Because the Book’s dual displays are connected with a visible center hinge, it doesn’t warp what’s in the center of the display like the ThinkPad Fold when I have one or two windows open. So I had to keep the Fold tilted at a similar angle to the Yoga Book’s bottom display, which was sort of awkward, but I forgot about it after a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="62Ajry"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12277490"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="yb5SFI"&gt;And that’s where my issues with the Fold end. One of my favorite Fold features is the fluidity of opening the laptop into desktop mode. When the keyboard is wrapped inside the folio cover, which attaches to the keyboard via a magnetic hinge, you simply open the ThinkPad Fold like a book until it’s totally flat, prop it up against the stand, and ta-da! All you need is a Starfleet uniform and a LCARS background, and you’re ready to go where not many laptops have gone before. (No? Just me?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="d7q6Ur"&gt;The outside surfaces of the laptop are adorned with finely woven strips of black recycled synthetic fiber (PET), and the texture is pleasantly tactile. Running my fingertips over it felt like a fabric-woven tote bag but smoother. It’s an elegant surface that hides fingerprints in its tiny crevices, too. Forget flat laptop lids, forget fun colors — I want more fun, classy textures in black! (Sorry, Yoga Book!) Those crevices do catch crumbs, so eating around the Fold is a no-go. The smaller the crumbs, the harder they are to pick out with your fingernail, but a small brush, about the size of a kid’s toothbrush, works to get them out if you have to get your snack on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="oGOu95"&gt;The Fold’s dimensions are well-balanced, which makes it feel lighter than it is while carrying with one hand or tucked into the crook of your arm. It’s only 0.68 inches thick and weighs 2.82 pounds (without the folio keyboard), which makes it one of the lightest laptops on the market — as light as a MacBook Air. I also liked how the magnetic stylus conveniently attaches to the bottom-right side in laptop mode.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A close-up of a laptop lid with a finely-woven, textured surface and a Lenovo badge." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/G5zbOgN4tC0L2evySTwO6TCUx4k=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25305798/247033_Lenovo_ThinkPad_X1_Fold_16_JNelius_0010.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;I’ve never been more enamored with a laptop lid.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="6boeiJ"&gt;I’m glad Lenovo ships a stylus with this laptop because, as a drawing tablet, this device is marvelously massive. Unfolded, it’s over 16 inches of OLED canvas that didn’t make my desk feel cluttered. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Mi7Uyv"&gt;I’m not an artist, but I gave drawing and painting a go with the Fold and didn’t find much to complain about. The experience felt nearly identical to Lenovo 2-in-1s and convertible laptops from other brands I’ve tested over the years, and the 2560 x 2024 display covers 96 percent of the DCI-P3 color gamut, so whatever paints Bob Ross decided to mix in the video, I could create a close digital version of his colors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Flj0iU"&gt;I could sometimes feel long, slender bumps spanning the length of the centerfold, which is not uncommon for folding displays. But once the entire device warmed up, it evened out, so that didn’t affect my ability to write and draw. The stylus itself was what gave me the most trouble.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A large drawing tablet showing splotches of digital paint in different colors." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/zgkeZ1h6VKx8z5yhwcv1gOTcKhM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25305791/247033_Lenovo_ThinkPad_X1_Fold_16_JNelius_0003.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;I’m no artist, but I enjoyed painting on such a large digital canvas.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="0opFlz"&gt;Well, most styluses give me trouble (thanks, dysgraphia), but the extra-pointy tip made it less fun to oil paint with Bob Ross in Adobe Fresco than it was to sketch an eye because it was difficult to find the right angle to mimic painting with a two-inch brush. To be fair to Lenovo, oil painting with &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; stylus feels totally different compared to the real thing, for obvious reasons, but once I figured out how to tweak the Fresco settings to get as close to Ross’ tried-and-true flat brushes as possible, I felt &lt;em&gt;mostly &lt;/em&gt;good about my happy digital clouds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gOhPoK"&gt;Watching movies and cloud gaming with ray tracing on was *chef’s kiss* thanks to the display’s color gamut, too, despite the 4:3 aspect ratio. &lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt; (I’m finally getting around to playing &lt;em&gt;Phantom Liberty&lt;/em&gt;) looked better on the Fold than my Gigabyte M28U gaming monitor, although I did have to mess around with the in-game resolution settings so everything didn’t look so squished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rgov80"&gt;Overall, Lenovo did a phenomenal job balancing the ThinkPad X1 Fold’s design with its hardware needs. I never had an issue with drawing applications lagging or running too many browser tabs (within reason). Its 12th Gen Intel U-series processor is miles ahead of the original’s Intel Core i5-L16G7, which was a sluggish five-core, five-thread processor designed to handle about 7W of power. (That’s right, no Hyper-Threading.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7UjbwX"&gt;In contrast, the Intel Core i5-1230U’s two performance cores are hyperthreaded (10-core, 12-thread), and its eight efficiency cores immensely helped with doubling the new Fold’s battery life; I was able to play &lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt; on GeForce Now with the display brightness maxed out (446 nits, as tested) for an average of five hours but averaged about nine to 10 hours at about 50 to 60 percent brightness if I was only using my computer for work-related tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A close, angled shot of a small laptop sitting on top of a gray kitchen counter." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/5S3_kdUUfydsQcHjkp-3wXCCjlM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25305796/247033_Lenovo_ThinkPad_X1_Fold_16_JNelius_0008.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;I normally don’t like netbook-sized laptops, but the Fold won me over.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="VMsiDG"&gt;Even with the stylus covering one of the three vents in laptop mode (there’s only one spot where it can magnetically attach, and &lt;em&gt;that’s&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;it&lt;/em&gt;), the Fold &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; got hotter than a lukewarm bath. The CPU’s power draw is capped at 26W, even though it’s designed to draw up to 29W. The chassis never went above 31 degrees Celsius, either, so I could comfortably leave it flat on my lap for an hour while Bob Ross helped me brush up on my digital painting skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="l0t1sl"&gt;Lenovo’s ThinkPad X1 Fold 16 Gen 1 has set the bar as &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; foldable laptop to beat, even if the keyboard and folio are critical add-ons to an already not-cheap laptop. The only other folding screen laptops that could provide a comparable experience are the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/14/23870597/hp-spectre-fold-foldable-windows-laptop-release-date"&gt;HP Spectre Fold&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/26/23890518/lg-gram-fold-foldable-laptop-oled-display-17-inch-price-release-dates-specs-features"&gt;LG Gram Fold&lt;/a&gt;, but the latter is only available in South Korea, and we have not tested the former — not to mention that the Spectre Fold is twice the price of the ThinkPad Fold. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="obM6fd"&gt;Still, if this Lenovo foldable is a sign of where more laptop designs are headed, I’m all in. If the company can make a folding laptop the same size as its Yoga Book and include a keyboard and folio in the future, even if the price were still $2,500, I’d buy it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="XZ6sNj"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Joanna Nelius / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="VM2m2L"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12277508"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24099045/lenovo-thinkpad-x1-fold-16-2024-laptop-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24099045/lenovo-thinkpad-x1-fold-16-2024-laptop-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Joanna Nelius</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T11:09:15-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T11:09:15-04:00</updated>
    <title>Mercedes is trialing humanoid robots for ‘low skill, repetitive’ tasks</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Apptronik’s Apollo robot carrying a blue crate in a Mercedes factory." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Hler2Mv0m6dICO6Ru6FHyUfY0kg=/503x113:5081x3165/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209516/24C0101_003.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mercedes also eventually plans to assess how Apollo handles delivering totes of kitted parts.&lt;/em&gt; | Image: Apptronik&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="JV4taN"&gt;Mercedes-Benz is the latest automotive company to trial how humanoid robots could be used to automate “low skill, physically challenging, manual labor.” On Friday, &lt;a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/apptronik-and-mercedes-benz-enter-commercial-agreement-that-will-pilot-apptroniks-apollo-humanoid-robot-in-mercedes-benz-manufacturing-facilities-302089972.html"&gt;robotics company Apptronik announced&lt;/a&gt; it had entered into a commercial agreement with Mercedes to pilot how “highly advanced robotics” like Apollo — Apptronik’s 160-pound bipedal robot — can be used in manufacturing. The news follows a similar pilot announced by &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/18/24043065/bmw-figure-robotics-humanoid-robot-workers-deployment"&gt;BMW in January&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="0neAmt"&gt;Apptronik says that Mercedes is exploring use cases like having Apollo inspect and deliver components to human production line workers. Neither company has disclosed any figures for the agreement or how many Apollo robots are being trialed. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="DyI4eX"&gt;According to Apptronik, humanoid robots would allow vehicle manufacturers to start automating manufacturing tasks without having to redesign their existing facilities. The company says its approach instead “centers on automating some physically demanding, repetitive and dull tasks for which it is increasingly hard to find reliable workers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="5g1mmz"&gt;&lt;div style="left: 0; width: 100%; height: 0; position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uJOA5IDaL5g?rel=0" style="top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute; border: 0;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="accelerometer; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share;"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="z6WJIc"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0dd1227c-0971-4d90-960e-5aef7f18ee48"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Financial Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; reports that Mercedes has started trialing an undisclosed number of Apollo robots at a factory in Hungary. The country has experienced labor shortages for several years as workers migrate to Western Europe, with &lt;a href="https://europe.autonews.com/article/20161019/ANE/161019840/audi-mercedes-face-labor-shortage-in-hungary"&gt;Audi and Mercedes&lt;/a&gt; having both expressed concerns regarding labor supply in 2016. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GZoHKY"&gt;“This is a new frontier and we want to understand the potential both for robotics and automotive manufacturing to fill labor gaps in areas such as low skill, repetitive and physically demanding work and to free up our highly skilled team members on the line to build the world’s most desirable cars,” said Mercedes’ production chief Jörg Burzer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="abeZZu"&gt;Apollo stands at five feet, eight inches tall, with Apptronik claiming the robot can lift objects up to 55 pounds. Its “face” is delightfully goofy, but otherwise its form factor isn’t too different from other humanoid robots in development, such as &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/16/23726139/tesla-robot-update-video-shareholder-meeting"&gt;Tesla’s Optimus robot&lt;/a&gt;, or the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/18/24043065/bmw-figure-robotics-humanoid-robot-workers-deployment"&gt;Figure 01 robots&lt;/a&gt; that BMW is trialing at its South Carolina manufacturing facility. Other bipedal robots like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/20/23648343/agility-robotics-digit-next-gen-bipedal-bot"&gt;Agility Robotics’ “Digit”&lt;/a&gt; are also being piloted in &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/18/23922202/amazon-robots-sorting-machines-sequoia-warehouse"&gt;Amazon’s US warehouses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101791/mercedes-robot-humanoid-apptronik-apollo-manufacturing"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101791/mercedes-robot-humanoid-apptronik-apollo-manufacturing</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jess Weatherbed</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T10:58:12-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T10:58:12-04:00</updated>
    <title>FCC clamps down on confusing ‘hidden fees’ in your cable TV bill</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Dollars float through pillars, as if to exit a bank" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/9zq22Yj8b76DwgrNB9z3hVeOpjk=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209464/STK417_H_Herrera_Money_03.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The ruling aims to make it easier to accurately compare subscription prices against other providers.&lt;/em&gt; | Illustration by Hugo Herrera / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="aT5hLP"&gt;Cable and satellite TV providers will need to ensure they show the total price of subscription plans as a “prominent single line item” — including costs described as extra fees — under a rule adopted by the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) on Thursday. The FCC says the &lt;a href="https://docs.fcc.gov/public/attachments/DOC-401215A1.pdf"&gt;new rule (pdf)&lt;/a&gt; for “all-in” pricing will make it easier for customers to compare prices against competing providers and streaming services by eliminating the “misleading practice of describing video programming costs as a tax, fee, or surcharge.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZPotRN"&gt;“No one likes surprises on their bill,” said FCC Chairwoman Jessica Rosenworcel in a &lt;a href="https://docs.fcc.gov/public/attachments/DOC-401215A2.pdf"&gt;separate statement (pdf)&lt;/a&gt;. “The advertised price for a service should be the price you pay when your bill arrives. It shouldn’t include a bunch of unexpected junk fees that are separate from the top-line price you were told when you signed up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="YWD5CF"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet"&gt;
&lt;p lang="en" dir="ltr"&gt;TV providers often use deceptive junk fees to hide real prices. We are putting an end to this form of price masking by requiring cable &amp;amp; satellite TV providers to clearly specify the “all-in” price for video programming in their promotional materials &amp;amp; on subscribers’ bills.&lt;/p&gt;— The FCC (@FCC) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/FCC/status/1768332803123352045?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;March 14, 2024&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="rfheLa"&gt;The new rules for transparent pricing on video programming will apply to both subscribers’ bills and promotional materials. The FCC says that companies often obscure certain costs and fees, which “causes significant and costly confusion for consumers.” The Commission has also proposed eliminating early termination fees issued by cable and satellite TV providers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="An example of a Comcast bill showing a breakdown of additional fees and charges." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/dkJt0t_vrgpf8nwiZgRbNl0P23Q=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25337693/HOW11878_092623_03.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Comcast Xfinity&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Bills like this &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="ql-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.xfinity.com%2Fsupport%2Farticles%2Fnew-bill-design&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F15%2F24101802%2Fcable-tv-bill-fee-satellite-tv-providers-subscription-price-fcc" target="_blank" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;example&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; from Comcast will be required to clearly display the total price, including the extra fees and charges.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="3emTKd"&gt;Forcing companies to display their subscription prices more clearly might be a relief to consumers who are sick of being surprised by unexpected additional fees, but cable providers like &lt;a href="https://www.fcc.gov/ecfs/document/10307141821162/1"&gt;Comcast, Cox, and Charter&lt;/a&gt; have argued that it’s unnecessary. The Internet &amp;amp; Television Association (NCTA) called the ruling “misguided” and claims it will only cause further confusion. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="N00PoO"&gt;“Cable providers offer clear and accurate pricing information to attract and retain subscribers, including ‘all-in’ pricing information before signing up for service,” &lt;a href="https://www.ncta.com/media/media-room/statements-of-ncta-the-internet-television-association-regarding-actions-at-todays-fcc-meeting"&gt;the NCTA said&lt;/a&gt; in response to the ruling. “The FCC’s micromanagement of advertising in today’s hyper-competitive marketplace will force operators to either clutter their ads with confusing disclosures or leave pricing information out entirely.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AlnDKE"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclosure: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Comcast is an investor in Vox Media, &lt;/em&gt;The Verge&lt;em&gt;’s parent company.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101802/cable-tv-bill-fee-satellite-tv-providers-subscription-price-fcc"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101802/cable-tv-bill-fee-satellite-tv-providers-subscription-price-fcc</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jess Weatherbed</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T10:13:33-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T10:13:33-04:00</updated>
    <title>Are we really going to ban TikTok?</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="An illustration depicting TikTok over the Vergecast team." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/EHwDyc3uJH6WLplmQFPcGzu815k=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209314/VST_0315_Site.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Alex Parkin / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="tv0Uat"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23651507/tiktok-ban-us-news"&gt;The TikTok ban&lt;/a&gt; might be for real this time. Nearly &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/9/22525953/biden-tiktok-wechat-trump-bans-revoked-alipay"&gt;four years after&lt;/a&gt; the first attempt to get the ByteDance-owned company either sold or barred from the US, a new bill is &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24097125/house-bill-vote-tiktok-ban-china-bytedance-divestment"&gt;flying through congressional votes&lt;/a&gt;, and President Joe Biden has already &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/9/24095348/president-biden-says-hell-sign-a-tiktok-ban-if-passed"&gt;said he’ll sign it&lt;/a&gt; if it comes to his desk. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="oEfzyZ"&gt;On &lt;a href="https://pod.link/vergecast"&gt;this episode of &lt;em&gt;The Vergecast&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we talk about what’s inside the Protecting Americans From Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act (everybody calls it PAFFACAA, just kidding; nobody calls it that, everybody just calls it “The TikTok Ban”) and what we know about TikTok’s connection to China. The answer: not a lot! But four years in, Congress seems more convinced than ever, and that might mean something. Or it might not. We spend a long time debating what that means.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="QkZrXb"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://player.megaphone.fm/VMP6905517148" style="border: 0; width: 100%; height: 200px;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="NC84Mv"&gt;After that, we discuss &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24097247/former-activision-ceo-bobby-kotick-is-apparently-eyeing-tiktok"&gt;who might buy TikTok&lt;/a&gt;, whether TikTok is even for sale, and what companies like Meta, Snap, and X stand to gain from a TikTok ban. And finally, we try to decide which outcome is the most likely: a TikTok ban, a TikTok sale, or nothing at all?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="bIpyw8"&gt;Once we dispense with the TikTok news, we talk about &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099533/youtube-tv-app-redesign-comments-shopping"&gt;YouTube’s new redesign for TVs&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099337/spotify-music-video-beta-11-markets-supported-artists"&gt;Spotify’s push into music videos&lt;/a&gt; — which are both, in a way, actually stories about TikTok. Neil Young &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099330/neil-youngs-music-is-back-on-low-res-spotify-two-years-after-rogan-protest"&gt;makes a surprise reappearance&lt;/a&gt; on the show, and then it’s time for a lightning round. Brought to you by your favorite new band, Algorithmic Warfare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="RNEOJ6"&gt;
&lt;div data-analytics-viewport="video" data-analytics-action="volume:view:article:middle" data-analytics-label="Are we really about to ban TikTok? | The Vergecast|115759" data-volume-uuid="5f55831ed" data-volume-id="115759" data-analytics-placement="article:middle" data-volume-placement="article" data-volume-autoplay="false" id="volume-placement-365" class="volume-video" data-volume-player-choice="youtube"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ehBTgI"&gt;If you want to read more on everything we covered in this show (there’s a lot!), here are a few links to get you started, first on TikTok:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="X9g3CD"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23651507/tiktok-ban-us-news"&gt;TikTok ban: all the news on attempts to ban the video platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="UecVfE"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091278/congress-tiktok-bytedance-ban-divest-bill"&gt;Lawmakers introduce bill that would punish app stores for hosting TikTok&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="ImCUQS"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24097125/house-bill-vote-tiktok-ban-china-bytedance-divestment"&gt;House passes bill that could ban TikTok&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="edg1nD"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/9/24095348/president-biden-says-hell-sign-a-tiktok-ban-if-passed"&gt;President Biden says he’ll sign a TikTok ban, if passed.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="r5wMDh"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099721/tiktok-ban-senate-house-vote-divest-bill"&gt;TikTok’s fate now lies with the Senate after House advances path to a ban&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="G3QQB8"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24100175/tiktok-ceo-tells-users-to-make-their-voices-heard-against-a-bill-that-could-ban-the-app-in-the-us"&gt;TikTok CEO tells users to “make their voices heard” against a bill that could ban the app in the US.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="kf72JW"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099896/nancy-pelosi-is-playing-tiktok-toe"&gt;Nancy Pelosi is playing TikTok-toe.&lt;/a&gt; (Ditto)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="wNhx2Q"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24097416/donald-trump-has-even-more-to-say-about-the-tiktok-ban"&gt;Donald Trump has even more to say about the TikTok ban.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="KwvrGU"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093308/tiktok-congress-ban-push-notification"&gt;TikTok is urging users to call Congress about a looming ban&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="dh31N5"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093490/the-tiktokers-are-revolting"&gt;The TikTokers are revolting.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="c1Y3br"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24097247/former-activision-ceo-bobby-kotick-is-apparently-eyeing-tiktok"&gt;Former Activision CEO Bobby Kotick is apparently eyeing TikTok.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="0VNlCO"&gt;And on the streaming news of the week:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="pf24W5"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099533/youtube-tv-app-redesign-comments-shopping"&gt;YouTube is revamping its TV app to make videos feel way more interactive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="KYLE54"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099337/spotify-music-video-beta-11-markets-supported-artists"&gt;Spotify now has music videos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Zt6Hg4"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099330/neil-youngs-music-is-back-on-low-res-spotify-two-years-after-rogan-protest"&gt;Neil Young’s music is back on “low res Spotify” two years after Rogan protest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="akgRDV"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099677/don-lemon-elon-musk-x-canceled"&gt;Elon Musk cancels Don Lemon’s show on X after a ‘tense’ interview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="kCPQNp"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lindayaX/status/1767675796334776506"&gt;Linda Yaccarino on X: “X is becoming a video first platform&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="ezAObe"&gt;And in the lightning round:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="QB4zvj"&gt;Alex Cranz’s pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/10/24096762/kate-middleton-edited-photo-royal-family-possible-fake"&gt;British monarchy rocked by bad Photoshop job&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="jcG1Xn"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098548/kate-middleton-royal-family-photoshop-manipulated-image"&gt;The Kate Middleton photo scandal is a rare — and consequential — flub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="DrwqJQ"&gt;Nilay Patel’s pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100501/spacex-starship-launch-third-flight-test-success"&gt;SpaceX successfully launches Starship in third flight test&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Te7A5S"&gt;David Pierce’s pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098334/apple-ios-web-distribution-eu-app-store-changes"&gt;Apple to allow iOS app downloads direct from websites in the EU&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="YNDPUb"&gt;Alex’s second pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24098771/dyson-vis-nav-robot-vacuum-hands-on"&gt;Hands-on with the Dyson 360 Vis Nav robot vacuum&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="ICMx6J"&gt;David’s second pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099723/microsoft-teams-unified-app-personal-work-accounts"&gt;Microsoft Teams is finally moving to a single app for personal and work&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Zwysf2"&gt;Nilay’s second pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093109/nikon-acquiring-red-cameras-film-motion-picture-tv"&gt;Nikon is acquiring US camera manufacturer RED&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="seBzTK"&gt;We’re really curious to hear what you think about the TikTok ban in particular. As always, you can get in touch with us by emailing vergecast@theverge.com, calling the &lt;em&gt;Vergecast&lt;/em&gt; Hotline at +1-866-VERGE11, or hitting us up on Threads. Or TikTok! For now.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24101704/tiktok-ban-kate-middleton-photoshop-vergecast-podcast"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24101704/tiktok-ban-kate-middleton-photoshop-vergecast-podcast</id>
    <author>
      <name>David Pierce</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
