<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Netflixes</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-14T14:40:52-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/netflix/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/netflix" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T14:40:52-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T14:40:52-04:00</updated>
    <title>Netflix is bringing back Black Mirror in 2025</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Annie Murphy in Black Mirror" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/xipD6xdQwNz8P99sJpSWES4JNGo=/149x0:1274x750/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73207440/black_mirror_s6.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Netflix&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="NYk6Ic"&gt;A seventh season of &lt;em&gt;Black Mirror&lt;/em&gt; is on the way. Netflix has confirmed that Charlie Brooker’s sci-fi anthology will return in 2025 and that the new season will be six episodes long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NzxdmR"&gt;There aren’t many details yet, of course. But the company does say that, while it’ll otherwise consist of new stories, one of the episodes will be a sequel to “&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/USS_Callister"&gt;USS Callister&lt;/a&gt;” from season 4, which starred Jesse Plemons. “Robert Daly is dead, but for the crew of the USS Callister, their problems are just beginning,” the description reads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="Hr7CP7"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Black Mirror season 6: exploring Netflix’s sci-fi anthology, one episode at a time","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23760609/black-mirror-season-6-episode-reviews"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="fVFXPr"&gt;The show’s return will mark a relatively brief hiatus, at least by &lt;em&gt;Black Mirror&lt;/em&gt; standards. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23760609/black-mirror-season-6-episode-reviews"&gt;Season 6 premiered last year&lt;/a&gt; and included some strong episodes, covering everything from &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/6/15/23761949/black-mirror-season-six-beyond-the-sea-aaron-paul-josh-hartnett-review"&gt;space-themed horror&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23763326/black-mirror-mazey-day-review-season-6-netflix"&gt;a paparazzi thriller&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23763339/black-mirrors-joan-is-awful-netflix-future-streaming"&gt;a satire of the future of streaming&lt;/a&gt; that proved &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/13/23794224/sag-aftra-actors-strike-ai-image-rights"&gt;all too prescient&lt;/a&gt;. So while we don’t know yet what exactly the new episodes will cover, it’s a safe bet more recent tech stories like AI and the metaverse might provide some inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24101013/black-mirror-season-7-netflix-date-trailer"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24101013/black-mirror-season-7-netflix-date-trailer</id>
    <author>
      <name>Andrew Webster</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-13T09:49:27-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-13T09:49:27-04:00</updated>
    <title>The first trailer for Netflix’s Atlas turns Jennifer Lopez into a mech pilot </title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/COBfs_9WeRFcpILuDML8BZBbPLs=/0x0:5472x3648/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73203586/ATL_MRKT_01_v3001.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Ana Carballosa/Netflix&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="htmr0b"&gt;It’s been a while since we had a really satisfying live-action feature focused on &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2013/7/8/4501378/pacific-rim-review"&gt;people piloting futuristic robots&lt;/a&gt;, but the first trailer for &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24057435/netflix-2024-movies-release-dates"&gt;Netflix’s &lt;em&gt;Atlas &lt;/em&gt;from director Brad Peyton&lt;/a&gt; makes it seem like it could be the mech genre’s next big splash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GveKP0"&gt;Set in a wild future where humanity’s begun using massive AI-powered robots to wage war, &lt;em&gt;Atlas &lt;/em&gt;tells the story of how data analyst Atlas Shepherd (Jennifer Lopez) is forced to work with a renegade machine to save the Earth. Despite the mechs’ widespread use throughout the world, Shepherd cannot shake her deep distrust for the thinking machines, which appear to be designed to operate autonomously or under the control of a human pilot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="N8RgBH"&gt;But when Shepherd’s tapped to become part of a covert mission to take out a rogue mech, she finds herself thrust into danger that only a machine can protect her from. Though &lt;em&gt;Atlas&lt;/em&gt;’ new trailer makes it hard to get a sense of the film’s plot or scope, it’s clear that Peyton and cinematographer John Schwartzman are going for an epic vibe judging from shots of Atlas plummeting to the ground in her robot from an exploding ship. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="iI0DQV"&gt;It also looks like we’ll be seeing Sterling K. Brown and Simu Liu chewing up scenery when they’re not busy getting in on the action themselves. But what’s really going to make or break &lt;em&gt;Atlas &lt;/em&gt;when it premieres on May 24th is probably going to be the amount of time the movie spends just letting its robots do sick tricks for us all to ogle.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24099430/netflix-atlas-trailer"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24099430/netflix-atlas-trailer</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-12T08:56:57-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-12T08:56:57-04:00</updated>
    <title>The 2024 Vergecast streaming draft</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="An illustration of the Vergecast team onstage at SXSW." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/PYVCzAih-ImFkbkKHkxGR2bdrfY=/0x0:3000x2000/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73200591/VST_0311_Site_Post.0.jpg" /&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="32HfhM"&gt;Keeping up with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/streaming-wars"&gt;the streaming wars&lt;/a&gt; is hard work. The movies and shows keep moving around, everyone is always bundling and then unbundling, and services like Paramount Plus and Hulu seem to be both growing fast and only &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/6/23990787/disney-plus-hulu-one-app-experience-beta-launch"&gt;barely holding onto existence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wOpTSU"&gt;That’s why, once a year &lt;a href="https://pod.link/vergecast"&gt;on &lt;em&gt;The Vergecast&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we take a moment and take stock of the streaming landscape. By drafting our favorite services! The goal is to figure out what’s working, what isn’t, and which services are likely to be on top 12 months from now. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="G8TFvb"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://player.megaphone.fm/VMP1812001918" style="border: 0; width: 100%; height: 200px;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="UdRreZ"&gt;
&lt;div data-analytics-viewport="video" data-analytics-action="volume:view:article:middle" data-analytics-label="The 2024 Streaming Draft (live from SXSW) | The Vergecast|115717" data-volume-uuid="97d62c95c" data-volume-id="115717" data-analytics-placement="article:middle" data-volume-placement="article" data-volume-autoplay="false" id="volume-placement-167" class="volume-video" data-volume-player-choice="youtube"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="J1N7O4"&gt;We recorded this episode live onstage at SXSW — thanks to everyone who came out and saw us! — and started by recapping &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/4/12/23679323/best-streaming-services-draft-vergecast-podcast"&gt;last year’s results&lt;/a&gt;. Here they are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="jSkoSk"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Nilay Patel’s picks&lt;/strong&gt;: TikTok, the Disney bundle, YouTube TV with Sunday Ticket, Apple Music, and his friend Vipin’s magical Plex server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Q6NrX6"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Alex Cranz’s picks: &lt;/strong&gt;HBO Max, Paramount Plus / Showtime, Channels, Criterion, and Apple One. Her bonus pick for spending the least money: Xbox Cloud Gaming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="ii4LTx"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;David Pierce’s picks:&lt;/strong&gt; YouTube Premium, Peacock, Netflix, Discovery Plus, Hulu with Live TV&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="qmRdV2"&gt;The audience picked last year’s winner, and we set off drafting. This year, though, we changed the rules and added categories. So instead of picking any five services, we each had to fill six categories:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="H8ABHL"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Cheap&lt;/strong&gt; (has to have a tier under $10)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="bg3p9O"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Awards &lt;/strong&gt;(has to have won an Oscar)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="WceiG8"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;4K&lt;/strong&gt; (has to offer content in 4K)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="iz7dg3"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Live&lt;/strong&gt; (has to have some live element)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="AcwDiR"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Niche&lt;/strong&gt; (has to be a genre-specific service)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="RRYhuz"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Wild card&lt;/strong&gt; (anything you want)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="efjr3G"&gt;An hour later, we’d landed in some deeply weird, surprising, maybe prescient and maybe just absurd places. Here are the results. (Don’t look until you’ve listened!):&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A scorecard showing the streaming logos from the 2024 Vergecast draft." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Oe3IXDD08-wEfJ-cOidpLnioVWU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25331623/SXSW_2024_.00_02_34_28.Still001.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="WawPyu"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Nilay’s picks&lt;/strong&gt;: TikTok, the Disney Bundle, Sony Bravia Core, YouTube TV with Sunday Ticket, MotorTrend TV, and Max&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="NtYLdr"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Alex’s picks:&lt;/strong&gt; Peacock, Hulu, Netflix, Channels, Crunchyroll, and Paramount Plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="9Pbult"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;David’s picks:&lt;/strong&gt; YouTube (with ads), Apple TV Plus, Tubi, Prime Video, Criterion, and Instagram Reels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="0KwZRB"&gt;We all think we won the draft. The audience had a clear pick, too. But only the next 12 months will tell us for sure. And who knows? Maybe half of these services won’t even exist in 2025. And maybe that Hulu-for-sports thing will be the first draft pick next year. Or maybe Nilay will keep picking TikTok and keep getting away with it. &lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098343/best-streaming-services-2024-netflix-tiktok-max-disney-vergecast"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098343/best-streaming-services-2024-netflix-tiktok-max-disney-vergecast</id>
    <author>
      <name>David Pierce</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-07T10:01:58-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-07T10:01:58-05:00</updated>
    <title>Dive into the world of Netflix’s 3 Body Problem</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/hzXF2nNFlN62QOkdVzPsrYwwVs8=/0x0:3600x2400/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73171118/3BP_102_Unit_03502RC.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;ED MILLER/NETFLIX&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Check out all of The Verge’s coverage of Netflix’s upcoming 3 Body Problem series based on Cixin Liu’s epic sci-fi novel.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="1Re15H"&gt;The idea of trying to adapt &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/7/24062452/three-body-problem-audiobook-rosalind-chao-netflix"&gt;Cixin Liu’s &lt;em&gt;The Three-Body Problem&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;for a Western audience &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/28/23375177/netflix-3-body-problem-tudum-db-weiss-david-benioff"&gt;sounds wild at first blush&lt;/a&gt; given how complex and deeply rooted in Chinese identity the book is. But every &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23955973/netflix-3-body-problem-teaser-trailer-release-date"&gt;glimpse of Netflix’s new series based on the epic novel&lt;/a&gt; has made it feel like showrunners David Benioff and D. B. Weiss and executive producer Alexander Woo might have figured out a way to pull it off. Between the show’s focus on physics-defying mysteries, metaversal gaming, and humanity making first contact with otherworldly beings, Netflix’s &lt;em&gt;3 Body Problem &lt;/em&gt;seems poised to capture viewers’ imaginations with a fascinating, larger-than-life story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="pjGcvI"&gt;&lt;em&gt;3 Body Problem &lt;/em&gt;has been on &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;’s radar from the moment Netflix first announced it, and we’ll have even more updates, reviews, and interviews to share as we get closer to the show’s March 21st release date. And given how much more there is to this tale beyond the first book, you’re probably going to want to keep an eye on this feed for even more news about potential future seasons of the show.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24083744/netflix-3-body-problem-trailers-review-interview"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24083744/netflix-3-body-problem-trailers-review-interview</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
      <name>Andrew Webster</name>
      <name>Nick Statt</name>
      <name>Andrew Liptak</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-07T09:49:22-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-07T09:49:22-05:00</updated>
    <title>Netflix’s next live event is a fight between Jake Paul and Mike Tyson</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Jake Paul punches Ryan Bourland during their cruiserweight fight at Coliseo de Puerto Rico on March 2nd, 2024, in Hato Rey, Puerto Rico." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/_yL7rePILbP_vx7btcXdDjwAhl0=/0x77:4708x3216/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73188831/2054434040.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo by Al Bello / Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="scc6av"&gt;Netflix’s foray into sports is going in a new direction. Today, the streamer announced that its next major event will be a fight between &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/21721881/jake-paul-interview-youtube-boxing-nate-robinson-ppv-controversy"&gt;YouTuber-turned-boxer Jake Paul&lt;/a&gt; and former heavyweight champion Mike Tyson that will stream live on Netflix. The bout will take place on July 20th at AT&amp;amp;T Stadium in Arlington, Texas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xAs7El"&gt;The move is part of a steady expansion into sports from Netflix. So far, that has meant &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/7/24064786/sports-streaming-docs-drive-to-survive-netflix"&gt;going all in on sports documentaries&lt;/a&gt; — including a doc about Paul’s fledgling boxing career — as well as a handful of live events featuring &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/17/23920735/netflix-cup-live-sports-broadcast-f1-drivers-pro-golfers"&gt;golf&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/11/23996783/netflix-tennis-rafael-nadal-live-sports-stream"&gt;tennis&lt;/a&gt;. But two headline (if controversial) names duking it out in an NFL stadium that seats 80,000 marks arguably the biggest bet from the company yet. (And it comes at a time when &lt;a href="https://www.espn.com/boxing/story/_/id/38679355/sources-show-exiting-boxing-nearly-4-decades"&gt;other&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2018/09/27/why-hbo-is-stunningly-leaving-boxing-behind/"&gt;broadcasters&lt;/a&gt; have largely gotten out of boxing.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wKXPgj"&gt;“It’s crazy to think that in my second pro fight, I went viral for knocking out Nate Robinson on Mike Tyson’s undercard,” Paul said in a statement. “Now, less than four years later, I’m stepping up to face Tyson myself to see if I have what it takes to beat one of boxing’s most notorious fighters and biggest icons.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="65z8J7"&gt;The news comes as sports have become an increasingly important facet of the streaming wars. Apple has been pushing on soccer in particular, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/2/27/23616811/mls-soccer-season-pass-apple-tv-opening-weekend-price"&gt;inking a streaming deal with MLS&lt;/a&gt; that got &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/27/23810301/lionel-messi-viewers-mls-apple-tv"&gt;a big boost with the arrival of Lionel Messi in Miami&lt;/a&gt;. (The company also recently launched &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/21/24079064/apple-sports-app-launch-iphone-live-scores-odds-stats"&gt;a bare-bones sports app&lt;/a&gt;.) Meanwhile, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/6/24064007/espn-fox-warner-bros-sports-streaming-partnership"&gt;ESPN, Warner Bros., and Fox are partnering on a sports service&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/20/24078607/fubotv-sports-streaming-lawsuit-disney-fox-warner-bros"&gt;with some pushback&lt;/a&gt;), and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/14/24038525/peacocks-afc-wild-card-game-was-the-most-streamed-event-ever-in-the-us"&gt;Peacock has seen some big numbers streaming NFL games&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093240/netflix-jake-paul-mike-tyson-boxing-fight-live"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093240/netflix-jake-paul-mike-tyson-boxing-fight-live</id>
    <author>
      <name>Andrew Webster</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-06T10:50:49-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-06T10:50:49-05:00</updated>
    <title>Netflix’s Avatar: The Last Airbender has been renewed for two more seasons</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A tight shot of a woman with a face painted in white with red eye shadow. The woman’s wearing a golden ornamental hat, and a a green warrior’s outfit." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/4hx0KAqAunDC5kz69Z4x1hnCl4k=/575x0:3026x1634/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73186304/Avatar__The_Last_Airbender_n_S1_00_36_42_04.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Yvonne Chapman as Avatar Kyoshi. | Netflix&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="nAbbsN"&gt;The season 1 finale of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24071094/netflix-avatar-last-airbender-review"&gt;Netflix’s live-action &lt;em&gt;Avatar: The Last Airbender&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;made it fairly clear that more episodes were probably on the way, and now the streamer’s making it official.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="6F6YEK"&gt;Netflix announced today that it has greenlit Albert Kim’s take on &lt;em&gt;Avatar: The Last Airbender &lt;/em&gt;for another two seasons that will “bring The Legend of Aang to its proper conclusion.”  Netflix also shared a new teaser image suggesting that, like the animated series, the live-action show’s second and third seasons will focus on Team Avatar’s adventures in the Earth Kingdom and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24050899/netflix-avatar-the-last-airbender-dallas-liu-interview"&gt;Fire Nation&lt;/a&gt;, respectively. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/bUUW5XDFIbiqVhhK8JiK9fpwWFk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25321054/EN_US_ATLA_s2s3_Announcement_Vertical_27x40_sRGB_PRE.jpeg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="6YP6fE"&gt;There’s no word yet on when production on the new seasons will begin or when we might expect to see them on Netflix.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092243/netflix-avatar-the-last-airbender-season-2-renewal"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092243/netflix-avatar-the-last-airbender-season-2-renewal</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-05T12:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-05T12:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Netflix continues run of excellent indie games with Hades in March</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Key art for Hades featuring the Prince Zagreus standing on a hydra skull against a hellish background" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/GXS4nF4wsWjhNfP4cttD2o__TVU=/200x0:2360x1440/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73183865/Hades_sdp_background_na_01_en.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Netflix&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="aSD6Qs"&gt;Netflix continues to strengthen its lineup of games with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23955772/hades-netflix-reveal-geeked-week-2023"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hades&lt;/em&gt; launching on iOS mobile&lt;/a&gt; on March 19th. The launch comes with a fancy new trailer highlighting how mobile controls will work for the escape-from-hell roguelike and you can pre-register for the game &lt;a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/hades-netflix/id6450063142"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="qbYcXB"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hades&lt;/em&gt; represents the latest in a handful of popular games Netflix is adding to its growing roster. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24001319/gta-trilogy-netflix-download-iphone-android"&gt;You can already play&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;Oxenfree II&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Kentucky Route Zero&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Before Your Eyes&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Spiritfarer&lt;/em&gt;, while &lt;em&gt;Katana Zero&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Sonic Mania Plus&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Braid&lt;/em&gt; are due sometime this year. Late last year, Netflix added &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/29/23981068/netflix-gta-trilogy-definitive-edition-mobile-release-date"&gt;the &lt;em&gt;Grand Theft Auto&lt;/em&gt; trilogy&lt;/a&gt;, which became &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/23/24048412/gta-is-netflixs-biggest-gaming-launch-so-far"&gt;its biggest gaming launch&lt;/a&gt; despite Netflix not sharing what “biggest gaming launch” meant in hard numbers. Netflix is also working on &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/16/23919517/netflix-game-streaming-beta-tvs-us"&gt;direct streaming of its games to TVs and PCs&lt;/a&gt;, testing the program in the UK, Canada, and to select users in the US.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rKZD79"&gt;Unfortunately, Supergiant is only working on an iOS release for &lt;em&gt;Hades. &lt;/em&gt;Sorry, Android, you’ll have to play the game one of the old-fashioned ways while you wait for &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/14/23873654/hades-ii-early-access-launch-q2-2024"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hades II&lt;/em&gt; to launch in early access sometime this year&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091183/netflix-games-hades-release-date-ios-march"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091183/netflix-games-hades-release-date-ios-march</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ash Parrish</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-05T11:03:20-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-05T11:03:20-05:00</updated>
    <title>Release dates and trailers for the biggest streaming movies and TV shows in 2024</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Picture of Noomi Rapace wearing an astronaut’s helmet, looking at something anxiously&amp;amp;nbsp;in a scene from the sci-fi TV series Constellation." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ij26EtADlcXitZk6xIIG52UMMoQ=/716x0:3124x1605/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73127098/Constellation_101_F00462F.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Noomia Rapace in Constellation&lt;/em&gt; | Image: Apple&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;From Netflix to Disney Plus to Max, here are details on the most anticipated films and TV shows coming home this year on streaming platforms. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="AAgPd1"&gt;The big-spending golden age of streaming &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/12/14/23507793/streaming-wars-hbo-max-netflix-ads-residuals-warrior-nun"&gt;is over&lt;/a&gt;, and as 2024 begins, services like Netflix, Disney, and Prime Video are &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24003126/netflix-viewing-data-ginny-georgia-witcher#:~:text=And%20second%2C%20the,what%20happens%20next"&gt;cutting back&lt;/a&gt; production, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23901586/streaming-service-prices-netflix-disney-hulu-peacock-max"&gt;raising prices, and piling on ads&lt;/a&gt;. Still, even if there aren’t quite as many new shows and movies to add to your binge-watching menu as the past few years, there will still be some worth waiting for. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="J0KaZU"&gt;And even after a merger or two (with rumors of more to come), the list of streaming platforms is still long, including Netflix, Hulu, Paramount Plus, Prime Video, Apple TV Plus, Disney Plus, Peacock, Max, and a few others. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GYkcxc"&gt;The new releases to look forward to include things like&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24065198/constellation-review-apple-tv-plus"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Constellation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (Apple TV Plus, February 21st)&lt;em&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24071094/netflix-avatar-last-airbender-review"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Avatar: The Last Airbender&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (February 22nd, Netflix)&lt;em&gt;, The Regime&lt;/em&gt; (Max, March 3rd)&lt;em&gt;, Palm Royale&lt;/em&gt; (Apple TV Plus, March 20th)&lt;em&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/23/23928591/amazon-prime-video-fallout-tv-series-live-action-premiere-date"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fallout&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (April 12th, Prime Video)&lt;em&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;as well as new seasons or spinoffs of popular shows like &lt;em&gt;Bridgerton&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23329415/the-lord-of-the-rings-of-power-review-amazon-prime"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Rings of Power&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Yellowstone&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/9/24031612/the-mandalorian-movie-star-wars"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Mandalorian&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Hacks&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Traitors&lt;/em&gt;, and many others. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uPeDHZ"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here are release dates, teaser info, and trailers for all the streaming movies and TV shows we’ll be watching in 2024: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2GUJmX"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24065499/netflix-disney-plus-max-release-date-trailer-streaming-calendar"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24065499/netflix-disney-plus-max-release-date-trailer-streaming-calendar</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
      <name>Quentyn Kennemer</name>
      <name>Andrew Webster</name>
      <name>Emma Roth</name>
      <name>Richard Lawler</name>
      <name>Wes Davis</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-01T14:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-01T14:30:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Netflix’s Spaceman is slow, sad sci-fi — with a lovable space spider</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A photo of Adam Sandler in the Netflix film Spaceman." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/kd8dnljEIcvJk_suohPmEBfhEnE=/2465x0:7067x3068/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73176421/Spaceman_n_00_19_04_23_R.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Netflix&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="yZfTI0"&gt;Truly alien creatures are hard to relate to because they’re so, well, alien. The best-realized ones have different cultures and biologies and belief systems that make them distinct from humanity and, thus, hard to understand. The alien in &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24007706/spaceman-trailer-netflix-adam-sandler"&gt;the Netflix film &lt;em&gt;Spaceman&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is one recent example: a giant spider with squirming tentacles, a disturbingly human mouth, the calming voice of Paul Dano, and the ability to experience time nonlinearly. And yet, the weird critter is also very relatable. He’s nosy and perceptive and prone to creature comforts to ease stress; he’s creepy, sure, but I kind of love him. And paired with a remarkably restrained Adam Sandler as a burned-out astronaut, his presence makes for some sad and soothing science fiction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="VLAUYZ"&gt;Directed by Johan Renck and based on the novel &lt;em&gt;Spaceman of Bohemia&lt;/em&gt; by Jaroslav Kalfař,  &lt;em&gt;Spaceman&lt;/em&gt; follows a Czech astronaut named Jakub (Sandler) on a solo journey to explore a strange phenomenon called the Chopra Cloud somewhere near Jupiter. Jakub has few people to talk to — his supervisor Peter (Kunal Nayyar) is always in his ear to keep things on track, and he’s able to video chat with his wife Lenka (Carey Mulligan) thanks to a device that looks like an ’80s arcade cabinet — but he’s physically isolated. Things only get worse as calls with Lenka become increasingly infrequent. This leads to a lot of time spent alone in the quiet of space, thinking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="9JHjFU"&gt;And then, suddenly, he’s not alone anymore. Very early on in &lt;em&gt;Spaceman,&lt;/em&gt; Jakub is joined by a mysterious alien he eventually names Hanus (Dano). The giant spider has a fascination with humans and spent an undetermined amount of time learning our history, language, and customs. But he’s especially attracted to Jakub: as a solo explorer himself, Hanus feels drawn to the lonely spaceman. And once Jakub gets over the shock of, you know, a huge talking spider making a sudden appearance in his otherwise empty world, the two quickly connect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A still image of a giant alien spider in the Netflix film Spaceman." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/XDDwTZmzMPZZ2sFIlgJazkPOy8A=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311964/Spaceman_n_00_16_45_09_R.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Netflix&lt;/cite&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="bVqZog"&gt;Hanus has the ability to peer into Jakub’s thoughts and memories, and he uses this to explore his past but mostly to understand his deteriorating relationship with Lenka. It’s a little bit &lt;em&gt;Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind&lt;/em&gt;, except Hanus takes on something of a therapist role: from his detached perspective, he’s able to use details from Jakub’s life to figure out how and why things went the way they did and then be brutally honest about his findings. &lt;em&gt;Spaceman&lt;/em&gt; starts out as a cute but weird buddy story but eventually morphs into a raw exploration of loneliness and coming to terms with our own personal failings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="28wZTv"&gt;Since so much of the film takes place with two characters in the confines of a small spaceship, the performances are a large reason why the movie works so well. Sandler sounds a bit odd at first — he’s sort of doing a Czech accent but also kind of not — but he shows a new side of himself here, one that isn’t &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/1/31/21116858/adam-sandler-netflix-deal-four-movies-murder-mystery-most-viewed-2019"&gt;outright goofball&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2019/12/13/21012837/uncut-gems-review"&gt;tense bundle of nerves&lt;/a&gt;. He’s quiet and reserved, with the haggard look of someone struggling both mentally and physically. Dano, meanwhile, is alternately cool and warm, with an alien viewpoint (his race doesn’t experience guilt, for instance) that, at times, becomes sentimental. (It turns out that Nutella tastes a lot like a certain larvae delicacy from his home world.) The two play off each other well: Jakub wants to ignore the truth, while Hanus can’t stop bringing it to the surface.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uohkwC"&gt;Eventually, the story comes back to its core sci-fi mystery, and &lt;em&gt;Spaceman&lt;/em&gt; does a very good job of tying these threads together in a way that feels natural and ends on a hopeful note, without devolving into a cliche happy ending. It’s sad, yes, but in a cathartic way — and almost makes you want to hug a talking spider. Even if Hanus would never be down for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1Qjrqk"&gt;&lt;small&gt;Spaceman &lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;is streaming now on Netflix.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24086859/spaceman-movie-review-netflix-adam-sandler"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24086859/spaceman-movie-review-netflix-adam-sandler</id>
    <author>
      <name>Andrew Webster</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-26T19:24:30-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-26T19:24:30-05:00</updated>
    <title>Netflix confirms it’s cutting off Apple billing for legacy subscribers</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Netflix’s logo on a black and yellow background" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ELLp50VfUQrmrZWxiE1Y4RhSbSQ=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73166669/acastro_STK072_05.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration by Alex Castro / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="hWkLA1"&gt;Netflix confirms to &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; that it has begun booting longtime subscribers off their Apple iTunes billing plans in some countries and will require them to pay Netflix directly using a credit card or debit card instead. As first reported &lt;a href="https://cordcuttersnews.com/netflix-will-no-longer-accept-payments-from-apple"&gt;by &lt;em&gt;Cord Cutter News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; Netflix has begun telling customers in “some territories” that their plans would need to be switched over. Netflix spokesperson MoMo Zhou told &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; in an email that the change affects “members on the basic plan who were using an iTunes method of payment,” and later added that this&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;includes Canadian and US users. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="69CDCx"&gt;It’s been a good run for anyone who signed up before Netflix stopped accepting subscriptions through Apple’s payments system. &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/meganNwalsh/status/1761565345658089752?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1761565345658089752%7Ctwgr%5E%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&amp;amp;ref_url=about%3Asrcdoc"&gt;One person indicated today&lt;/a&gt; on X that they’d kept the streaming service’s old $9.99 price for years. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="qX7ayj"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-dnt="true" align="center" data-conversation="none"&gt;
&lt;p lang="en" dir="ltr"&gt;Netflix stopped working with Apple Pay and didn’t inform me. Now I’m locked out of my $9.99 a month price I had paid for years and I had to get charged $31 until I get a refund through Apple.    Love this!&lt;/p&gt;—       (@meganNwalsh) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/meganNwalsh/status/1761565345658089752?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;February 25, 2024&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zqrmDV"&gt;Alas, if you’re like that person, you’ll now have to join the rest of us and either accept a more-than-$5 price hike for essentially the same plan you’ve had for years or pay $3 less than you have been and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24051687/netflix-ads-password-sharing-wwe-changes"&gt;let the ads wash over you&lt;/a&gt;. Or you could take the time to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23831904/streaming-wars-price-hikes-disney-plus-hbo-max-hulu"&gt;reflect on your relationship&lt;/a&gt; with streaming services, which seem to get pricier all the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="DyxEkv"&gt;The change is the end of a long saga — despite Apple adding in-app subscription options to iPhones in 2010, Netflix didn’t &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2015/9/24/9395037/netflix-ios-app-subscribe-in-app-purchases"&gt;add them&lt;/a&gt; to its iOS app until 2015 because it was opposed to Apple’s 30 percent cut. In late 2018, Netflix &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2018/12/28/18159373/netflix-in-app-subscriptions-iphone-ipad-ios-apple"&gt;decided it didn’t want to pay Apple at all&lt;/a&gt;, dropping in-app subscriptions entirely, and it never looked back. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="JMmJ7C"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Correction February 27th, 2024, 11:35AM ET: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Corrected the spelling of MoMo Zhou’s name and clarified that this change does not affect all Netflix accounts, as the article previously stated, but does include Canadian and US users. We regret the errors.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24084173/netflix-refusing-apple-itunes-subscriptions"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24084173/netflix-refusing-apple-itunes-subscriptions</id>
    <author>
      <name>Wes Davis</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
