<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Phone Reviews</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-14T08:30:00-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/phone-review/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/phone-review" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T08:30:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T08:30:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra review: just another big phone</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;It’s bigger for sure, but is that really better?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="50SrvP"&gt;The Zenfone is &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23777412/asus-zenfone-10-specs-screen-size-battery-camera"&gt;everyone’s favorite small-ish Android phone&lt;/a&gt;, except this year, it’s not: the Zenfone has gone Ultra. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HLiweD"&gt;Asus has adapted its gaming phone, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/8/24023549/asus-rog-phone-8-pro-ai-price-release-date-specs-features-gaming-smartphone"&gt;the ROG Phone 8&lt;/a&gt;, into a normie phone. It’s big, heavy, and it costs $899. It’s entirely inoffensive if big phones are your thing (&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/20/23730130/apple-iphone-13-mini-apple-phones"&gt;they aren’t mine, personally&lt;/a&gt;), but after a week of testing, I’m not seeing any compelling reason to pick it over any of the other big, heavy phones already on the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Iy6HF5"&gt;It’s possible that Asus will release a smaller Zenfone 11 later this year, but the company won’t say one way or the other whether it plans to do that. The last great small-ish Android phone &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/20/24078500/asus-zenfone-11-ultra-small-phone"&gt;might be dead&lt;/a&gt;, or it might not be. In the meantime, another big Android phone just dropped — and it’s a fine device, but I’m not sure we needed it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="RUlcFH"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12278351"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="EJA7iO"&gt;Look, I get the appeal of a big phone. You know what a big phone has a lot of? Screen. Screen as far as the eye can see! The Zenfone 11 Ultra — again, like the ROG Phone 8 Pro — offers a 6.78-inch OLED panel. It can go up to 144Hz, but only in gaming mode. The rest of the time, it’ll go up to 120Hz or, since it’s an LTPO display, down as low as 1Hz to save on battery life. It’s only 1080p, though, so it’s not quite as crisp as its competitors with 1440p displays, like the OnePlus 12 and Samsung Galaxy S24 Plus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hRyXP5"&gt;Big phones also come with big batteries, and I have zero complaints with the Zenfone 11 Ultra’s massive 5,500mAh battery. I easily got through a full day without dropping under 50 percent, and I’d feel reasonably confident stretching this battery to two days. It also supports wireless charging — not Qi2 though, just regular 15W Qi. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra on a yellow background showing homescreen." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/FRcLpcB4ntH6u2fudZklZWsk6kc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334617/DSC07066.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;More phone, more screen. Those are the rules.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="WqyM4T"&gt;The Zenfone 11 Ultra uses a Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 chipset, the top-tier processor of choice for Android phone makers, and the base model comes with a beefy 12GB of memory and 256GB of storage. I doubt I pushed its gaming phone DNA to the limit with my &lt;em&gt;Pocket City 2&lt;/em&gt; sessions — designating commercial zones and adjusting income tax sliders is probably not what the Republic of Gamers had in mind — but the 11 Ultra handled every task I threw at it with ease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KKDxOF"&gt;Like previous Zenfones, the 11 Ultra will work on AT&amp;amp;T and T-Mobile but not on Verizon. Hypothetically, you &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; use it on the Verizon network if you live in an area with good 5G coverage and you have a physical SIM card. Just theoretically speaking. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra on a yellow background showing blue back panel at an angle." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/T17eZ3f39IZI2pcRNQ0f02DXqg8=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334618/DSC07077.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;This design doesn’t do it for me, but you know what does? The Zenfone’s IP68 rating.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="dS2X5B"&gt;I definitely wouldn’t recommend it for full-time use, though, because you might see a worrying “No Service” notification pop up at the top of your screen every once in a while, and while texting and data work fine, placing phone calls seems to be a no-go. Sort of a crucial “telephone” feature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="z6Dswn"&gt;In the abstract, I like the Zenfone 11 Ultra’s design. Like, if I saw it in an ad in a design magazine, the cool blue finish and architectural camera bump would look kind of nice, you know? If I’m being honest, though, it’s not my favorite. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra on a yellow background showing headphone jack." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/yfcC0MetWZaVk1qc47pxysLZzqM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334621/DSC07086.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Look, a headphone jack! They do exist!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mGJqnw"&gt;The black edges and camera bump seem out of step with the sleek, slightly matte back panel. But mainly, I’m annoyed at how heavy and &lt;em&gt;dense &lt;/em&gt;it is. More than once, it slid out of my jacket pocket and into the crevice between the driver’s seat and center console with an alarming thud. I did not enjoy this one bit. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="XnSbav"&gt;Asus is keeping up with the times and includes a handful of AI features on the 11 Ultra, including a call translation feature that seems to work exactly like Samsung’s version. Nice to have, but the AI noise cancellation for calls is something that seems more broadly useful. It works both ways, cleaning up the audio for the listener and speaker — &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/13/23552300/google-pixel-7-pro-clear-calling-noise-cancellation"&gt;Google’s version for the Pixel&lt;/a&gt; only cancels out noise on the other end of the call so &lt;em&gt;you’ll&lt;/em&gt; have an easier time hearing if they’re in a noisy environment. I couldn’t test it out because I’m on Verizon. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="VEX6jQ"&gt;AI features are great and all, but one thing that’s more important to most people? The camera.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;The Zenfone’s coolest camera trick remains its gimbal-like stabilization. During video recording, it smooths out bumps and movement incredibly well — and if you need proof that it’s really working, you can take a close look at the main camera lens &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/allisonjo1/status/1552668060351229953?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1552668060351229953%7Ctwgr%5Ee8f3b925925024314d186b82cbf77d14cd42a758%7Ctwcon%5Es1_c10&amp;amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2022%2F7%2F28%2F23280728%2Fasus-zenfone-9-screen-camera-specs-price-ois-gimbal-stabilization-video"&gt;to see it moving&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="C0HEIg"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12278502"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="4E78jh"&gt;There’s even a HyperSteady mode that corrects for bigger movements — violently shaking the camera back and forth just looks like moderate swaying. It crops in a lot, and you need plenty of light to use it, but it’s cool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="6hpJru"&gt;Outside of video mode, the 11 Ultra looks pretty average. Portrait mode cutouts are surprisingly good, and the system chose shutter speeds fast enough to get plenty of sharp photos of my kid playing indoors. But the 11 Ultra’s cameras overall are a little inconsistent — auto white balance jumps around occasionally, and photos sometimes have a too-bright, overexposed look about them. Sometimes they don’t! But that’s the problem: inconsistency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra in hand showing homescreen." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/6eeyEmn4_Pwm58cr-xHhTebJw3U=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334622/DSC07091.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;It’s hard out there for a big Android phone.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="nNzG9h"&gt;It’s Big Android Phone season, because the Zenfone 11 Ultra arrives on the heels of the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24058916/samsung-galaxy-s24-plus-review-screen-battery-camera"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S24 Plus&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24053907/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-review-ai-screen-camera-battery"&gt;S24 Ultra&lt;/a&gt;, and the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24047368/oneplus-12-review"&gt;OnePlus 12&lt;/a&gt;. They all use the same chipset (well, provided you buy the S24 Plus in the US) and not-a-one of them has a screen smaller than 6.7 inches. I can clearly recommend three out of four of these phones, but the Zenfone, I’m just not sure about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4E22F8"&gt;The Galaxy S24 Ultra is the obvious pick for someone who wants the absolute most out of their phone. The $799 OnePlus 12 is the right choice if you want a big screen and want to spend a little less. For everyone else, there’s the Galaxy S24 Plus — the crowd-pleaser that’s readily available with trade-in and carrier deals galore. The Zenfone just doesn’t earn a clear space for itself here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7MQyjM"&gt;Maybe if it had an outstanding camera or it had better network support in the US or, I don’t know, &lt;em&gt;a thoughtful form factor unlike anything else on the market. &lt;/em&gt;The Zenfone 11 Ultra does plenty of things well but isn’t great in any one way. As it stands, it’s just one more big phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="COd5B8"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Allison Johnson / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="4flm3O"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12278353"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24099978/asus-zenfone-11-ultra-review-screen-battery-camera"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24099978/asus-zenfone-11-ultra-review-screen-battery-camera</id>
    <author>
      <name>Allison Johnson</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-16T09:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-16T09:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>The OnePlus 12R is a $500 phone with flagship tendencies</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;Time for Samsung and Google to make some room in the midrange.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="jEgQUh"&gt;Choice is a beautiful thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="CX64Zb"&gt;The OnePlus 12R has just arrived in the US, and not a moment too soon. It’s the first $500 smartphone we’ve seen in a while that gives the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23681017/samsung-galaxy-a54-5g-review-screen-camera-battery"&gt;Samsung Galaxy A54&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23716677/google-pixel-7a-review-screen-camera-battery"&gt;Google Pixel 7A&lt;/a&gt; any serious competition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="THThAS"&gt;Each of these devices is a slightly different answer to the same questions: What’s absolutely essential in a phone? What do you keep when you can’t have it all? Maybe you can’t live without wireless charging, or you want thorough water resistance and a big screen, or you want a high-end processor so the phone feels faster for longer. Guess what? You’ve got choices now! You can afford to be picky with more options on the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="1Dc8He"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12252143"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="jFnYWy"&gt;It all starts with the screen. The OnePlus 12R comes with a 6.78-inch display, bigger than the 6.1-inch Pixel 7A and 6.4-inch Galaxy A54 screens. Resolution is slightly higher than 1080p, which feels like just enough pixels to cover such a massive display. It offers a maximum refresh rate of 120Hz, and it uses a technology called low-temperature polycrystalline oxide, or LTPO, to downshift all the way to 1Hz. Other high refresh rate screens on budget phones shift between a couple of settings, like 60 and 90Hz. LTPO panels are &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23320405/apple-iphone-14-pro-max-always-on-display-screen-feature"&gt;much more common among flagship phones&lt;/a&gt;, and they offer a truly variable refresh rate, which saves on battery life. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Azxs7M"&gt;The screen maximum brightness of 4,500 nits sounds absolutely eye-searing since most phone screens top out between 1,000 and 2,000 nits. And it does get bright in direct sunlight, but because of the way we measure such things, it’s not as fantastically bright as it sounds. In any case, it’s enough to keep the screen comfortable to use outdoors in sunny conditions, which is also rare in a budget phone. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="OnePlus 12R on a green background showing display and home screen." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/DsBnrlz4T8zmwsG-biDd0SP2aFA=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25287584/DSC06626.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;A great screen is one of the OnePlus 12R’s highlights.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="cFQrIR"&gt;I did notice a strange screen flicker on a handful of occasions. It happened maybe once a day, and it’s just a fleeting thing. I asked OnePlus about this behavior, and spokesperson Spenser Blank told me it was the first he’d heard of it. It’s an unusual little bug on an otherwise great display.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HE4FkM"&gt;Under the hood, the 12R comes with last year’s flagship chipset: the Snapdragon 8 Gen 2, along with 8 or 16GB of RAM. The 8 Gen 2 is an absolute unit that powered just about every one of last year’s $1,000 Android flagships, and I had no problem cutting through daily chores and even a few rapid-fire portrait mode photos. Using last year’s chip is a smart move, kind of like buying a high-end coat at an end-of-season sale. It’s not the very latest, but it’s still a damn good coat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="eOuhL6"&gt;Design and software&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="U1mrRE"&gt;The flagship vibes carry through to the overall build. The 12R offers a sturdy aluminum frame in a price range where composite plastic is pretty common. The back panel is glass, and the front panel is Gorilla Glass Victus 2 — all very nice and high end. But here’s the less encouraging news: the 12R comes with an IP64 rating, so while it’s totally dustproof, it’s only resistant to water spray and splashes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EKeIGb"&gt;The Pixel 7A and Galaxy A54 both come with IP67 ratings, meaning they’re built to withstand brief water immersion like a brief dip in a puddle or (god forbid) a toilet bowl. The 12R absolutely looks and feels the part of a high-end phone, but under unfortunate circumstances, it might not fare as well as one. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="08OQTU"&gt;&lt;q&gt;Long live the alert slider&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="RT5iC2"&gt;Long live the alert slider: OnePlus’ signature three-stage mute switch is alive and well on the 12R. It’s a handy way to turn your volume on to watch a TikTok and quickly turn it off again, and I appreciate it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="DGxyff"&gt;I’m less keen on the phone’s curved edges — sometimes a menu option sort of disappears off the side of the screen, and I feel like I’m tapping on the side of the phone to reach it. Plus, they make the phone feel a little more slippery in your hand. This is personal preference, but flat edges on phones are making a comeback lately, and I’m here for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="OnePlus 12R on a desk with screen side up showing curved edge of the phone." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/F_-MPjKXADEvpMa7lDn-A0bSV6c=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25288146/DSC06649.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The OnePlus 12R’s curved edges look sleek, but they can be a pain to deal with.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="X2tObF"&gt;Something else that’s not so nice? No wireless charging. The OnePlus 12R supports very fast wired charging — up to 80W for the US version. Wireless charging isn’t all that common in $500 phones, but the Pixel 7A has it. It’s not a must-have for everyone, but I would personally rather have the flexibility of wireless charging than fast wired charging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="41Vagg"&gt;The OnePlus 12R ships with the company’s take on Android 14, OxygenOS 14. It’s straightforward and doesn’t require as much rejiggering as Samsung’s One UI to live with it peacefully. The company says the 12R will get three years of OS upgrades and four years of security support — not a class-leading support policy but enough to last as long as most people will want to hang onto this phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="wyGM5T"&gt;Camera and image quality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="ggGKF8"&gt;If you don’t push it too hard, the OnePlus 12R’s camera turns in very nice images. The stabilized 50-megapixel main camera’s standard 1x shooting mode produces nice, detailed images with rich colors. The 2x setting is surprisingly capable considering it’s just digital zoom — not lossless crop zoom. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="bYq4OS"&gt;I used it in dim indoor lighting, and it managed some sharp photos of my kid and his friend preparing to sauté a Beanie Baby on a play kitchen stove. (No Beanie Babies were harmed.) Despite the lighting conditions, the system kept shutter speeds fast enough to freeze the action, which is no small feat for a phone camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="3NCAzZ"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12253885"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="yhCNyG"&gt;The 12R gets out over its skis at the 5x zoom setting, though. Even in plentiful outdoor light, photos look like a smeary mess of up-rezzed digital zoom processing. Portrait mode is surprisingly capable, and wisely, OnePlus limits you to the 1x zoom setting here. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Bmm4sc"&gt;There’s a pointless two-megapixel macro camera that I’m convinced OnePlus only included to round out the number of lenses on the rear camera bump. Video recording is just fine for casual clips — 1080/30p is the default, but you can bump that up to 4K/30p without a noticeable crop. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="OnePlus 12R on a blue and green background showing rear panel." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/LNEjDvuycIM_xaJ59THKKpBynQg=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25287586/DSC06640.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="aXOkQZ"&gt;The OnePlus 12R is a sorely needed midrange contender in the US. It’s lacking some features you can find on its peers, like wireless charging and a beefier water resistance rating, but it brings enough to the table that it’s a legitimate alternative to the Pixel and Galaxy options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="sAgi81"&gt;You won’t find another screen this big and this nice on a $500 phone sold in the US, for starters. Overall build quality is right up there with the best, even if the curved edges aren’t my favorite. Opting for Qualcomm’s previous-gen flagship chipset is a smart move, too. I like its long-term prospects better than the Tensor and Exynos chips in the competition. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="p7J3Ro"&gt;&lt;q&gt;You won’t find another screen this big and this nice on a $500&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="5kHNXH"&gt;The Pixel 7A is probably still the better choice for photo quality, though I’m impressed with how narrow of a lead it has over the OnePlus. The 12R actually does better than the Pixel in some situations, like at the 2x zoom setting, but ultimately, the 7A offers a more consistent camera experience. On the other hand, the Galaxy A54 is worth considering if you’re after a bigger screen and better water resistance, though it also misses out on wireless charging and lacks some of the 12R’s finesse with its composite frame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="t4Kq63"&gt;The 12R won’t be the right choice for everyone, but you know what? That’s okay. It doesn’t need to be a one-size-fits-all device because you’ve got other options. And that’s a wonderful thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="jecVwx"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Allison Johnson / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="SzdfTx"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12253663"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24072383/oneplus-12r-review-screen-camera-price"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24072383/oneplus-12r-review-screen-camera-price</id>
    <author>
      <name>Allison Johnson</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-02T11:40:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-02T11:40:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Samsung Galaxy S24 and S24 Plus review: smart choices</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;With its newest devices, Samsung cleverly mixes original AI features with some familiar concepts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="IeOCm0"&gt;The Galaxy S24 Plus and S24 borrow some of the best ideas from Apple and Google, taking a running jump with them into the AI era.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="iO2Sud"&gt;The flat-edge design is undeniably iPhone, and the AI tech is largely Google. The software, for better and worse, is all Samsung. But I wouldn’t call either phone the best of all worlds. And although it’s tempting to call them better Google phones than the Pixel, I don’t think that’s all the way true.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="sMZqox"&gt;The standard Galaxy S24 still starts at $799 and the Galaxy S24 Plus starts at $999 — it’s only the Ultra that went up in price this year, to $1,299. Aside from screen size, the non-Ultra models share most of the same features, so I’ll refer to them interchangeably throughout this review unless otherwise specified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div id="Y9dUkM"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12241077"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="2jfACQ"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12241087"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="vxmEej"&gt;The gap between the regular models and the Ultra is wider than before, but the benefits of stepping up to the Ultra don’t feel more compelling. Sure, you get a bigger, better screen, more zoom, and an S Pen, like you always do. But a lot of what makes the Ultra good are features it shares with the cheaper models. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="Fze104"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra review: all that and AI","url":"https://www.theverge.com/24053907/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-review-ai-screen-camera-battery"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="OSifc6"&gt;That includes all of the highly touted Galaxy AI features, like generative photo editing, live language translation on phone calls, and automatic recording summaries. Like most things AI right now, they’re occasionally great and sometimes weird. But on the whole, they do more good than harm, and it’s kind of cool knowing my phone can translate a call with someone speaking Spanish if I need it to. For all the quirks in Samsung’s software, that’s something that the Pixel 8 Pro — or any other phone, for that matter — can’t do right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 and S24 Plus side by side showing screen size difference." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/HrTecOxPz7trPCDjMOmG31UL1yA=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25262609/DSC06601.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Big screen or slightly less big screen?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="lS8n2V"&gt;Displays and design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="bF1iZ9"&gt;Samsung managed to cram some extra screen into the Galaxy S24 and S24 Plus without making the phones meaningfully bigger — the S24 Plus went from a 6.6-inch to 6.7-inch panel, and the S24 has a 6.2-inch versus a 6.1-inch screen. How did Samsung manage this? Both phones are slightly taller now, and the bezels are just a hair slimmer on the new models. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WJumUr"&gt;They also get just a little brighter in direct sunlight, up to 2600 nits. It’s not a massive difference and you don’t get the excellent glare-reduction on the S24 Ultra’s panel, which really &lt;em&gt;does &lt;/em&gt;make a difference, but it’s something. Oh, and the S24 Plus’ panel is now 1440p, and it’s about time Samsung upgraded it from 1080p.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 Plus standing on edge showing flat sides." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/zsYMadIJKWHRG2hjTlCz_Z9_yJs=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25262610/DSC06608.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Allison Johnson / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;That’s a damned iPhone if I ever saw one.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="OgHRAN"&gt;There’s one year-over-year design difference that I’m particularly thankful for: the slight curve on the edges is gone in place of gloriously flat sides. It’s very much giving iPhone vibes, and I think that’s just fine. I find a flat-edge phone much easier to pick up without it flying out of my fingers, and I don’t find it any less comfortable to hold in one hand. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dnrImk"&gt;That design language isn’t the only cue Samsung’s taking from Apple — One UI 6.1 adds wallpaper dimming for the always-on display, in the manner of recent Pro iPhones, though only for the S24 phones. Better yet, there are widgets! You can arrange a handful of them in a bar below the clock to show you your phone’s battery life or your next calendar event at a glance, hands-free. We’re in an era of phones doing more for you when you’re not actively using them, and I am here for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 in purple on a light pink background." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/GUDjB1R9_rE2U7_Px43pryltv1U=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25262612/DSC06558.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Galaxy S24 is about as small as Android flagships get.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="1mwRfv"&gt;Performance, battery, and software&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="kDSCwp"&gt;If you buy the Galaxy S24 or S24 Plus in the US, it’ll come with a Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 chipset, just like the Ultra. But &lt;em&gt;unlike&lt;/em&gt; the Ultra, models sold outside the US will keep with one of Samsung’s own Exynos chips. I tested the Snapdragon versions of the S24 and S24 Plus and really can’t find a fault with them, performance-wise. The S24 Plus comes with 12GB of RAM, while the base model S24 (including my review unit) comes with 8GB of RAM. I didn’t notice any significant differences between the two in day-to-day performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="tjn3zx"&gt;Now that I’ve used all three S24 series phones, battery performance seems roughly the same on all of them — the bigger the phone is, the more power-hungry it is, but the difference is offset by a bigger battery. On previous generations, the smaller phone was noticeably worse, but I think that problem has been mostly solved at this point with more power-efficient chipsets and slightly bigger batteries. One thing I do wish Samsung had incorporated? Qi2. There’s no support for the MagSafe-esque standard, and that’s a shame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="PzbQmh"&gt;In this, the year 2024, Samsung still ships its high-end phones with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2019/8/8/20791457/google-android-q-back-gesture-controversy-app-drawer-navigation"&gt;three-button navigation&lt;/a&gt; as the default. I usually plan to spend a little extra time untangling some of Samsung’s weirder default settings whenever I use a new Galaxy phone, and the S24 devices have been no exception. No, I don’t want to talk to Bixby when I long-press the power button. No, I don’t want my app drawer arranged in a nonsensical order where I can never find anything. As usual, putting in a little work upfront to de-Samsung your phone is a basic requirement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="1Vrdcp"&gt;&lt;q&gt;Putting in a little work up front to de-Samsung your phone is a basic requirement&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mpHPeR"&gt;That’s where I have a hard time calling the S24 an outright winner over the Pixel. Once you have everything where you want it, the S24 is a triumph. But Samsung &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; makes you work for it, and Pixel phones just run better software right out of the box. Case in point: the Pixel 8 Pro doesn’t support widgets on the always-on display like the S24 does, but At a Glance will surface useful information there without you lifting a finger. It all just feels a little more turnkey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TGUlLn"&gt;Samsung is going toe to toe with Google’s new policy of supporting its flagship phones with seven years of software updates — OS upgrades and security updates included. That feels more important in the S24 and S24 Plus, which I suspect people are more likely to hold onto for longer than an Ultra owner who wants to chase the latest tech. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 Plus on a purple background showing camera array." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/wd8EpY_B4LbHVQctZeh__VRTBA8=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25262607/DSC06589.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Samsung Galaxy S24 Plus is just packed with AI.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="o9IJaQ"&gt;The S24 devices have the same AI features across the entire series, which is &lt;em&gt;not &lt;/em&gt;the case on the Pixel 8 series — some features are reserved for the bigger, pricier Pixel 8 Pro, despite it using the very same processor as the Pixel 8. I covered many of the S24 AI features in depth in &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24053907/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-review-ai-screen-camera-battery"&gt;my Galaxy S24 Ultra review&lt;/a&gt;, so you can check that out for a detailed look at &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24053907/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-review-ai-screen-camera-battery#:~:text=Automatic%20note%20and%20voice%20transcript%20summaries%20are%20in%20the%20same%20category."&gt;voice transcription and summaries&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24053907/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-review-ai-screen-camera-battery#:~:text=Take%20live%20translation"&gt;phone call translation&lt;/a&gt;, and some of the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24053907/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-review-ai-screen-camera-battery#:~:text=Samsung%20is%20the%20company%20that%20gave%20us%20AI%20Moon"&gt;generative AI photo editing features&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="B7Rtoh"&gt;The short version is that none of these features feel indispensable, but many of them are genuinely helpful even when they’re not perfect. Having a real-time translator on a call with someone who speaks another language is in no way &lt;em&gt;worse&lt;/em&gt; than not having one. Generative AI photo edits are really uneven in quality, but there’s no harm done if you want to simply live your life without using them. Samsung might start charging for these features after 2025, so it’s wisely giving itself some runway to get AI off the ground. Right now, there’s nothing worth paying for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xWKujS"&gt;One thing I will add now that I’ve been playing with AI on the S24 for a couple of weeks is that Samsung’s generative photo editor seems way more prone to adding weird shit into your photos than the Pixel. I tried erasing my husband’s arm out of the same image on both the Galaxy S24 and the Pixel 8 Pro. The Pixel did its best to just replicate the couch in the background where his arm was — the S24 instead &lt;em&gt;replaced it with a new arm made out of pillows.&lt;/em&gt; Samsung! Why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Photo of a child on a couch with blurred arm in the foreground." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/B45GvH5f5E5dhUKVjynNvmSx9cU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25262683/20240131_200646_vert.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Regular arm...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="AI generated image where arm has been replaced with an arm-shaped object made of couch texture." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/0yGxAUFM-5Zk2UjDvVU4S4fUn-o=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25262684/20240201_113528_vert.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;...Pillow Arm!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="RIqJUo"&gt;Camera and image quality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="IShmgf"&gt;The editing software may be radically different, but the camera hardware on the S24 and S24 Plus hasn’t changed from the previous generation. You still get a 50-megapixel main camera, 12-megapixel ultrawide, and an actual 3x telephoto zoom no matter which of these two phone sizes you choose — and that’s darn nice of them. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7NPyD9"&gt;There are a few processing updates under the hood, even in the absence of new hardware. Low-light images taken at 2x zoom now use a lossless crop from the middle of the sensor; on the S23 series, the camera reverted to digital zoom in dim light. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="eB10Pk"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12240919"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="qsDjOs"&gt;Samsung has also added foreground blur in portrait mode, which sounds like a small thing, but it makes a big difference in your photos looking less like cardboard cutouts. These little tweaks build on what was already a darn good camera system. Samsung’s color processing leans hard into vibrant reds and blues, per usual, which isn’t always my favorite. But when it’s good, it’s &lt;em&gt;good.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="P4dn7i"&gt;Samsung is actually one step ahead of Google in adopting Ultra HDR, the new image format supported by Android 14. It’s the &lt;em&gt;good &lt;/em&gt;HDR, not the bad stuff, and it allows your photos to pop in a way that’s not possible with the standard dynamic range images we’re used to seeing. Samsung not only supports Ultra HDR image capture, you can also edit your photos and share them to Instagram without losing the HDR information. The Pixel 8 series shoots Ultra HDR, but doesn’t yet support HDR editing in its own Photos app or sharing to social media.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 and S24 Plus side by side on purple and pink background." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/QIWlYeR3Rwni_tBSh-7bhf6N9EM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25262608/DSC06592.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Name a more iconic duo.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="yUt24c"&gt;Some of the best parts of the Galaxy S24 and S24 Plus aren’t entirely original to Samsung, and I think that’s fine. Adopting a well-liked, functional design and leaning on Google for AI is just smart — why reinvent the little black rectangle? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wQLe3G"&gt;And unlike flat device edges, AI features have a lot to prove. The S24 is a lower-stakes way to get in on the AI future than the $1,300 Ultra, or &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/9/24030667/rabbit-r1-ai-action-model-price-release-date"&gt;some&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/9/23953901/humane-ai-pin-launch-date-price-openai"&gt;other&lt;/a&gt; more radical ideas floating around out there. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lPenJS"&gt;Most importantly, it’s just a good, reliable phone. The screens on both devices are excellent, and the smaller Galaxy S24 remains one of the best &lt;em&gt;reasonably&lt;/em&gt; small phones you can buy right now. If you’re a small phone fan like me, then it’s the one to pick. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="1Hdp3H"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The Galaxy S24 Plus strikes me as the ultimate crowd-pleaser&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="62biKH"&gt;As far as big Android phones go, you really can’t do better than the Galaxy S24 Plus right now in terms of performance and value. Sure, you can go Ultra and get the absolute &lt;em&gt;most &lt;/em&gt;phone, with a big, fantastic screen, better zoom, and a built-in S Pen. But I think the Ultra demographic is a little more self-selecting, and the S24 Plus strikes me as the ultimate crowd-pleaser for someone who just wants a great Android phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="BgS6JS"&gt;That said, there are some good reasons to consider the Pixel 8 Pro instead. Its 5x telephoto has just a bit more reach for those distant subjects compared to the S24’s 3x zoom, and Pixel software is less fussy than One UI. But the Pixel’s Tensor G3 processor can run a bit hotter than the Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 if you push it, and Google stuck with the curved edge design, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/23/24048246/pixel-9-pro-leak-specs-google"&gt;for now at least&lt;/a&gt;. Sometimes, the smartest move is to recognize a good idea and embrace it — even if someone else thought of it first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Cgw8rR"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Allison Johnson / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="Xfis7p"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12236228"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24058916/samsung-galaxy-s24-plus-review-screen-battery-camera"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24058916/samsung-galaxy-s24-plus-review-screen-battery-camera</id>
    <author>
      <name>Allison Johnson</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-29T10:36:20-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-29T10:36:20-05:00</updated>
    <title>Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra review: all that and AI</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;The Galaxy S24 Ultra is packed with top-tier hardware, but its highly touted AI features are hit-or-miss — and the price is higher than ever.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="EF3gah"&gt;The Galaxy S24 Ultra is a hell of a phone. As always, Samsung has jammed it full of more high-end hardware than you can shake an S Pen at, and this year it’s also packed with cutting-edge AI features. But it’s expensive, and most of my favorite things about it have very little to do with the AI parts, which aren’t even exclusive to the Ultra.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="qapUgJ"&gt;It comes with a display that’s so easy to use outside in bright light that I want every other manufacturer to copy it. Its camera system is one of the best in the game and comes with a fantastic portrait mode. The built-in stylus remains one of the nicest and fanciest ways to make a grocery list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="z4EOJh"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12236055"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="nMG0vu"&gt;Some of the AI features really are impressive: live translation for phone calls could be really helpful for someone who makes a lot of calls in an unfamiliar language. Voice recording summaries are surprisingly good and give my beloved Pixel Recorder a real run for its money. And turning any video into slow motion is just plain fun. Are the results always great? No, but they’re usually delightful. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8tOt0B"&gt;But battery performance is just okay, and while I appreciate the new flat-screen design, it leaves some sharp corners that can be uncomfortable in your hand. Above all, the Ultra is expensive — now starting at $1,299, a $100 increase from last year’s model. Samsung’s everything-but-the-kitchen-sink device is still the most feature-packed phone money can buy, but I’m just not seeing an extra $100 worth of improvements, especially considering that the AI features will all be ported to the S23 series in a future software update. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/NvOwUi66D6MLLxy9sJWG4JRC6-U=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25253485/DSC06482.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The S Pen abides.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="oFBX9s"&gt;Display, battery, and performance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="df82L4"&gt;Ever try to use your phone in direct sunlight and find it turns into a mirror? Reflections bounce right off the glass, and whatever you were trying to look at is suddenly invisible. It’s a real pain in the buns, although it’s been less of a problem as OLED screens have gotten brighter over the past few years. The S24 Ultra goes an extra step and introduces a new anti-glare coating that does a fantastic job of cutting those reflections down. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EL3dI0"&gt;The 6.8-inch screen peaks at 2,600 nits in bright light, which makes a real difference when you use your phone outside. I prepared myself to squint at the display when I used it in some bright sunshine, so it was a real treat to realize I could see the screen almost as well as I could indoors. There’s a new Gorilla Glass Armor protecting the screen, and it purports to be much more scratch-resistant than previous versions of Gorilla Glass. It’s hard to judge that in just over a week of testing, but so far, so good. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hTZvso"&gt;Samsung followed Apple’s lead on another screen feature: dimming the wallpaper on the always-on display. You can also add a handful of widgets that will continue to display on the AOD even with the phone locked. It’s a straight-up Apple clone, and I have zero problems with that because I crave information and love widgets. Answering “What’s next on my calendar?” is as simple as glancing at my phone screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra showing always on display with dimmed wallpaper and widgets." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ODcvhaUriCVGXKeRj9DfWjU5dlk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25253490/DSC06525.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Widgets on an always-on display? A beautiful thing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="qBHnv5"&gt;The always-on display is handy, but it does seem to take a significant toll on battery performance. At the end of each day I tested it, diagnostics reported that it was responsible for about 7 percent of my battery use throughout the day. Overall, battery life on the S24 Ultra isn’t &lt;em&gt;great,&lt;/em&gt; but it’s not a disaster by any means — on days of light use, I got to bedtime with around 50 percent in the tank. Heavier days with closer to five hours of screen-on time pushed my review unit’s battery down to 30 percent. Honestly, that’s about average for a flagship phone these days, and I wish performance were a little better across the board. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KmeNjV"&gt;In any case, plenty of people will get through a full day on the S24 Ultra just fine, though it’s worth remembering your mileage will dwindle over time as the battery ages. If you’re a power user — as I suspect a lot of people interested in this phone are — you might need an afternoon recharge to avoid late-day battery anxiety. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gE0Noj"&gt;There’s 45W wired and 15W wireless Qi charging available but no Qi2, which is a real disappointment. If you want to live the MagSafe life with the S24 Ultra, you’ll need to pick up a third-party magnet case — just &lt;a href="https://9to5google.com/2024/01/18/galaxy-s24-ultra-magsafe-s-pen-issues/"&gt;don’t use the stylus with a magnetic accessory&lt;/a&gt; attached — and a MagSafe-&lt;em&gt;compatible&lt;/em&gt; (not MagSafe or Qi2) charger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra on a blue and yellow background at an angle showing flat display." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/gGlm7_Yj8f8BmOC813uR2BS4KeQ=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25253486/DSC06488.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Curved screens are out; flat screens are in.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="QZ2O6B"&gt;The S24 Ultra comes equipped with the Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 chipset no matter where you buy it — not true of the standard S24 and S24 Plus, which come with Exynos chips outside of the US. I can’t find anything wrong with performance on the Ultra. It didn’t get excessively hot in my testing, and with 12GB of RAM, it handled everything I threw at it without a problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="226LD5"&gt;The S24 Ultra is the first Ultra with a flat screen, and I appreciate it — no longer do I fear running the S Pen over the curved edge. The titanium exterior finish is lovely, but this remains an unapologetically big, heavy phone. After the first few times it slipped out of the pocket of my joggers and onto the wood floor with a thud heard ’round the house, I quit carrying it around with me and left it on the dining room table. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="myOEHI"&gt;Also, this phone is kind of sharp? The corners where the flat parts of the phone meet the curved edges are pointy, and if you don’t get it situated in your hand just right, they’re pretty uncomfortable. I’m not a case person, but I might consider one with the S24 Ultra for this reason.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra in hand showing homescreen." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3_kziarW4a6jJmAYUMg-O44f330=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25253491/DSC06531.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;That’s a whole lot of phone.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="yv3W67"&gt;Software and AI&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="QttOfl"&gt;The S24 series ships with One UI 6.1, which is Samsung’s take on Android 14. Like Android 14 itself, One UI 6.1 is a relatively light update, and the things that irritate me about Samsung software persist: a push notification urging me to check out the new Galaxy S24 (lol); lots of proprietary apps and features that I don’t have a use for (I refuse to believe &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clwvKRmDfia"&gt;Global Goals&lt;/a&gt; has inspired anyone to do anything except uninstall Global Goals); and clickbait links stuffed at the bottom of the weather app (“Tourist Finds Large Diamond at State Park,” really?). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="kmda7V"&gt;You can &lt;a href="https://www.androidpolice.com/samsung-one-ui-5-problems-solutions/"&gt;de-Samsung a lot of this stuff&lt;/a&gt; and live a peaceful existence with One UI, and there’s some good news this year: the company is promising seven years of OS upgrades, including seven years of security updates. That’s a great proposition for ROI and anyone who wants to get the absolute most years out of their phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hRCNtd"&gt;That’s the gist of the regular phone stuff — a massive screen, okay battery life, and performance fitting of a 2024 flagship. So how about the marquee feature: Galaxy AI? Settle in, because there’s a lot to cover. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra on a blue and yellow background showing rear panel and grey device color." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/f9PcFAcAGiMDhbw9Wqy5Dd0W-Zc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25253483/DSC06441.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;AI and all those cameras.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="uYNpTf"&gt;The short version is this: the S24 Ultra has an impressive collection of AI features. But it’s just that — a collection. It doesn’t feel like a unified set of tools with a collective purpose; it feels like a handful of capabilities scattered throughout the system that are excellent at times and baffling at others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WRhqwB"&gt;Take live translation: it happens on-device, and it can act as a real-time interpreter on phone calls. I tried it with my colleague Victoria Song, a fluent speaker of Japanese, and she thought it did an adequate job translating our exchange. It’s best suited for short transactional conversations because it gets impatient with pauses. It doesn’t quite get things right when talking more casually, either — I asked how Vee’s cats were doing, and the translator somehow interpreted her Japanese for “Petey is eating my chair” as “I am eating my chair.” Hilarious, but not ideal! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="z615sB"&gt;But if you need to call and ask for some information or make a reservation, it would serve the purpose. And that’s kind of amazing — if you live in a country where you don’t speak the language, I can see this being a hugely useful tool. It’s the kind of situation where AI that’s good &lt;em&gt;enough&lt;/em&gt; is better than nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Screenshot of a screen recording text" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/LDV4J1qN5eJKMM2tJXjBIrZXlLw=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25254013/Screenshot_20240128_163122_Voice_Recorder.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The S24 Ultra doesn’t transcribe as you’re recording, but it does generate the transcription fairly quickly and on-device.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Screenshot of transcriptions summary generated with AI." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/L0GysehJR-U20Ba2l1ke6Nd4-F0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25254019/Screenshot_20240128_163128_Voice_Recorder.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The S24 Ultra’s transcript summaries come with suggested keywords, subheads, and timestamps — pretty good! But it does require a trip to the cloud.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="J9wQpc"&gt;Automatic note and voice transcript summaries are in the same category. I put the S24 Ultra’s new voice recorder features up against my beloved Pixel Recorder by reading them both a passage from the closest book I had on hand, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/0997580828?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Precious Little Sleep&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;aka the baby sleep Bible. Overall, I was surprised by how well Samsung kept up with the Pixel. It doesn’t transcribe in real time like the Pixel does, but it’s on-device, and it’s relatively quick after the fact; a six-minute recording took about 90 seconds to transcribe in my testing. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KZoavH"&gt;Once you have your transcript, you can generate a detailed summary in just a few seconds, complete with subheads and timestamps. It’s not something I’d trust without double-checking the source material, but like call translation, it gives you a starting point — something useful when you’d otherwise have nothing. Samsung’s translation summaries happen in the cloud, not on-device, so they do require an internet connection. Summarization seems like it’s too much to ask of a phone processor: the Pixel 8 Pro I tested at the same time tried to summarize its recording of the same text, produced one bullet point, and then gave up after chugging for a few minutes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lwf5mb"&gt;Then there’s Circle to Search, which is only really an AI feature by association, but spiritually, it feels at home in a discussion about the S24 Ultra’s AI features. It’s a Google feature that’s debuting on the Galaxy S24 &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/24/24049669/google-pixel-8-pro-feature-drop-circle-to-search-update"&gt;and Pixel 8 series&lt;/a&gt; and will reportedly come to more high-end Android phones in the future. Basically, it’s Google Lens but everywhere on your phone — any app, anytime. You long-press the home button or navigation handle to engage it, and then a prompt appears to circle the thing you want to know more about. A page of Google results will follow, and you can tap around to learn more or dismiss the whole thing and go about your business. It’s simple, but it kind of feels like how our phones should have been working all along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra shown in-hand with Google’s Circle to Search results shown on-screen." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/9EN6Cy8t-c2RyhgN_NmONSwWhkU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25230415/DSC06312_processed.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Multisearch will prompt you to “add to your search” after an initial query, and that’s where things get interesting.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="volxeT"&gt;Google’s improvements to multisearch really make this feature stand out. After you’ve circled something to search for it, you can clarify your search with additional questions using the image as a starting point. Previously, multisearch could only work with basic modifiers, like “blue” to search for a pair of shoes in a particular color. Now, you can ask more complicated questions, and the search results will offer up an answer using generative AI. And that’s where I found the answer I was after most often.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="jT5km6"&gt;There are some obvious situations where Circle to Search makes immediate sense — a friend texts the name of a restaurant, you highlight the name, and without ever leaving the messages app, you can check where it is. I had to sort of unlearn doing this the long way while using the S24 Ultra, and now that I’m used to Circle to Search, I don’t want to go back to the old way. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="oGGEVJ"&gt;But when I was looking for more information about something, the first set of results didn’t always clear things up. Searching for a mural I photographed in San Jose brought up a page of similar-looking murals — helpful if you’re making a Pinterest mood board, less helpful if you want to know exactly what you’re looking at. But asking “Where is this?” in multisearch (shh, I knew where it was, I was just testing the computer) got me to the right answer quickly. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="9mI286"&gt;There are more AI features — naturally there are more — but I won’t go into depth about every one of them. You can have generative AI spice up your text messages with emoji or summarize webpages. They work reasonably well but don’t strike me as being quite as useful as the others. Of course, there’s one more place you’ll find AI at work: the Galaxy S24 Ultra’s camera. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra in hand showing camera app on screen." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/sAo1UuCY4Vujz2RmOPFov8N7gb8=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25253492/DSC06539.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The new 5x telephoto is good, but damn the 10x lens was a great party trick.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="kZk7x6"&gt;Cameras and image quality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="bNLa2b"&gt;First, the numbers. Per usual, there are a boatload of cameras on this phone:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="v6jF1T"&gt;Main camera: 200-megapixel f/1.7 with OIS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Jp2fbK"&gt;3x telephoto: 10-megapixel f/2.4, OIS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="agHFFY"&gt;5x telephoto: 50-megapixel f/3.4, OIS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="CIBmfN"&gt;Ultrawide: 12-megapixel f/2.2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Lr1DQG"&gt;Selfie: 12-megapixel f/2.2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="JtrbDN"&gt;They’re the same cameras that are on the S23 Ultra except for one notable substitution — the 10x lens is gone, swapped for a 5x lens coupled with a bigger, higher-res sensor. This is terrible news for me personally because I love that ridiculous 10x lens. You can take pictures of planes! In the sky! It’s such a great party trick. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lQuSct"&gt;The new version uses crop zoom to get to 10x, and Samsung insists that the image quality is just as good as the 10x optical zoom on the previous version. As far as I can tell, that’s mostly true — detail rendering looks about the same. And the S24 Ultra definitely looks better at 5x since the S23 Ultra was using digital zoom at that focal length. I do see more chromatic aberration on some of the S24 Ultra’s 10x images compared to the S23 Ultra’s, which can make certain subjects appear a little fuzzier — this seems to be less of a problem with distant subjects, like the top of a skyscraper. The switch to a 5x zoom hasn’t been a completely victimless crime. But overall, it’s a move that makes sense. The 5x focal length has a lot more practical uses, and Samsung claims it’s used more often than 10x. Fair. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="36hx8Y"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="imageslider:12236224"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="B1eDbr"&gt;Otherwise, there aren’t any drastic changes year over year. Samsung is still leaning on the saturation slider, embracing those vivid reds and blues it’s known for. It usually looks nice and occasionally looks bananas. The company made a few tweaks to the tech behind its portrait mode, which is still excellent. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22958552/samsung-expert-raw-galaxy-s22-ultra"&gt;Expert RAW&lt;/a&gt; now produces 24-megapixel images with data from 50- and 12-megapixel captures. More data, more better, as they say. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="0ZEr8X"&gt;And I’m thrilled to see Samsung fully embrace Ultra HDR — that’s &lt;a href="https://www.androidpolice.com/android-14-ultra-hdr-hands-on/"&gt;the high dynamic range image format supported in Android 14&lt;/a&gt;. You’ll see the Ultra HDR tone mapping in the live image preview as you take your photo, and the S24 series are &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/18/24042649/samsung-galaxy-s24-instagram-snapchat-super-hdr-nightography-stabilized-video"&gt;the first devices that let you upload Ultra HDR photos to Instagram&lt;/a&gt;. These are true HDR photos that look more vibrant than &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/12/23345028/iphone-samsung-smartphone-camera-photographic-styles-hdr-contrast"&gt;the washed-out “HDR” photos&lt;/a&gt; we’re used to seeing, which are really just attempts at showing a wider dynamic range on an SDR display. I’m already impatient for third-party app support to come to more phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="yDGBl3"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12236213"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="TfHPhd"&gt;Samsung is the company that &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/13/23637401/samsung-fake-moon-photos-ai-galaxy-s21-s23-ultra"&gt;gave us AI Moon&lt;/a&gt;, so naturally, there are a few AI photo and video editing features here. Generative AI edits are available behind a star icon in the native gallery editing interface. You can select objects to move around the frame or erase entirely, and you can adjust the horizon using generative fill to pad out the image rather than cropping in. The edits happen off-device, so you need an internet connection and a little patience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="bsSTbN"&gt;This is very similar to the generative AI editing tools offered on the Pixel 8 Pro, which isn’t surprising — Samsung is using Google’s models to power just about every AI feature on these phones. But I actually find Samsung’s object selection much easier to use than the Pixel’s. On the S24, you just circle an object you want to select, and on-device AI makes the selection. It’s a little uncanny how good it is. Selecting objects on the Pixel feels a little more fiddly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RgC1CX"&gt;With an object selected, you can resize it, move it around the frame, or erase it completely. With a somewhat predictable background like grass or a gravel path, generative AI can fill in the blanks convincingly. Predictably, things get dicey with more complicated edits. I selected a lamp on a table and attempted to erase it from a photo; the AI replaced it with a different lamp. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="VlZnpe"&gt;
&lt;div class="iframely-embed"&gt;&lt;div class="iframely-responsive" style="padding-bottom: 177.7778%;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.threads.net/@allisonjo1/post/C2gGhiDPzfF" data-iframely-url="https://cdn.iframe.ly/api/iframe?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.threads.net%2F%40allisonjo1%2Fpost%2FC2gGhiDPzfF&amp;amp;key=9ef4a209439e42bc59783ba959d50197"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://cdn.iframe.ly/embed.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="GS0tqf"&gt;It’s a similar story with slow-motion AI videos — impressive if you don’t challenge it too much or look too closely. The S24 Ultra can turn any video into a 120fps slow-motion video — essentially using frame interpolation but leaning on generative AI to fill in the gaps. With the right subject and background, it’s totally convincing. But if you start introducing some complexity, it kind of falls apart. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3lMJkH"&gt;I slowed down the above &lt;a href="https://www.threads.net/@allisonjo1/post/C2gGhiDPzfF"&gt;30fps video of my son on a swing&lt;/a&gt;, and you can see that the mulch on the playground and greenery in the background gave the AI some trouble. Is it still an adorable video? Yes. Will his grandparents be delighted by it despite its flaws? Also yes. It feels like a feature right on the edge between “good enough” and “too weird” to be fun. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra showing a blue and yellow homescreen, on a blue and yellow background with green translucent rectangles." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/PqhsAXZ1GsNArViK7b60jFf1aBc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25253488/DSC06515.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The AI puzzle pieces don’t quite make a complete picture.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="33CQpe"&gt;It’s hard to describe why a device that does so much so well feels like it falls flat. The Galaxy S23 Ultra felt like something truly special — a refinement of a well-balanced formula. But with the S24 Ultra, the math feels a little off. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TbasNV"&gt;It’s $100 more expensive, but it’s hard to see an extra $100 worth of value, especially considering the new AI features are shared across the whole S24 series. To be clear, I think it’s a &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt; thing that these features are available on all three phones. But if the Ultra really is the fastest, bestest phone in all the land, shouldn’t it be able to do a little more?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="bfAPqK"&gt;The new anti-glare screen coating is impressive and truly helpful on a bright day. The flat screen is an improvement, and the new titanium exterior looks and feels great. But that’s more or less the extent of this year’s Ultra-only improvements. The AI features, Ultra HDR support, seven years of OS upgrades, updated always-on display — they’re all available on the less pricey S24 and S24 Plus. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="aC1gue"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The feature-to-price ratio feels just a bit off-balance in a way that it didn’t in the S23 Ultra&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="3m9omw"&gt;That leaves the Ultra with a bigger screen, an S Pen, and a 5x zoom to distinguish it. They’re all great features and sure to please loyal Note / Ultra fans. But the feature-to-price ratio feels just a bit off-balance in a way that it didn’t in the S23 Ultra. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8ICXUw"&gt;I wish Samsung had spent a little more time on the less-flashy stuff — improving battery life  or making it lighter and more comfortable to use. Heck, I’d be thrilled if Samsung spent time on a little housekeeping on the features that have piled up over the years. Bixby Vision, Google Lens, and Circle to Search all exist on this phone. What are we doing here? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="E7jFUl"&gt;The Galaxy S24 Ultra remains the absolute &lt;em&gt;most&lt;/em&gt; phone. Massive screen, S Pen, all of the cameras, performance out the wazoo — it really has no peer. I just wish that it felt a little more worthy of its price bump when the MSRP was already sky-high before. This is an Ultra phone, alright. I just wish it came with a little extra. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rxCjRn"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Allison Johnson / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="Q6vNOB"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12236228"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24053907/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-review-ai-screen-camera-battery"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24053907/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-review-ai-screen-camera-battery</id>
    <author>
      <name>Allison Johnson</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-26T10:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-26T10:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Honor Magic V2 review: fabulous foldable running so-so software</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;It’s thin and light enough to feel like a regular smartphone when folded. That’s impressive. I just wish Honor’s software were as svelte.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="ezPzbO"&gt;Most foldable phones still feel like a phone and a half in your pocket. But Honor’s pitch for the Magic V2 is that it’s slim and light enough to feel like a regular smartphone until the moment you decide to unfold it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZeM6LJ"&gt;The Magic V2 mostly delivers on this promise. There were times when I genuinely thought I was carrying my regular smartphone in my pocket. But while the hardware represents an eye-catching competitor to the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23826325/samsung-galaxy-z-fold-5-review-screen-hinge-battery-camera"&gt;Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23773594/google-pixel-fold-review-screen-battery-hinge-camera"&gt;Google Pixel Fold&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23923599/oneplus-open-review-foldable-battery-screen-camera-price"&gt;OnePlus Open&lt;/a&gt;, its software doesn’t quite feel as polished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4LvdAa"&gt;The Magic V2 &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23791047/honor-magic-v2-foldable-china-launch-release-date-price-specs-details-hinge"&gt;has been available in China&lt;/a&gt; for over half a year, but today, Honor is launching the device in Europe, where it’ll cost £1,699.99 (€1,999, or around $2,170, although the device isn’t going on sale in North America). There’s also a more premium Porsche Design variant on the way soon with more storage, a tweaked design, and an included stylus, though Honor declined to share pricing for that model ahead of today’s launch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="cUaKX0"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12233838"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="5goAFk"&gt;My single favorite aspect of the Honor Magic V2 is its physical dimensions. The glass-backed version I’ve been using is 10.1mm thin at its thinnest point when folded and weighs 237 grams. It’s thinner and lighter than the Galaxy Z Fold 5 (13.4mm, 253g), the Pixel Fold (12.1mm, 283g), and the OnePlus Open (11.7-11.9mm, 239-245g). The vegan leather-backed version of the Magic V2 is even more compact at just 9.9mm thick and 231 grams in weight. It’s still thicker and heavier when folded than a typical large smartphone (the iPhone 15 Pro Max, for example, is 8.25mm thick and 221 grams in weight), but it’s approaching the same ballpark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="PAMuzx"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5 review: a little better is just good enough","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23826325/samsung-galaxy-z-fold-5-review-screen-hinge-battery-camera"},{"title":"Google Pixel Fold review: closing the gap","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23773594/google-pixel-fold-review-screen-battery-hinge-camera"},{"title":"OnePlus Open review: right size, wrong price","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23923599/oneplus-open-review-foldable-battery-screen-camera-price"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="DwZJ56"&gt;Those are a lot of numbers, so let me offer a real-world example. I was able to fit the Honor Magic V2 in a zipped pocket of my running shorts and head out for the better part of an hour without feeling like I was lugging a small tablet around. In fact, it was only when I got back that I remembered I wasn’t carrying my personal iPhone 14 Pro. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8flXkY"&gt;On the front of the phone, you’ll find a 6.43-inch OLED display with a resolution of 1060 x 2376, a maximum refresh rate of 120Hz, and a peak brightness of 2,500 nits. Inside, there’s a not-quite-square 7.92-inch display with a resolution of 2156 x 2344 and a similar 120Hz refresh rate but a lower claimed peak brightness of 1,600 nits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Honor Magic V2 held at an angle to the camera." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/PgWxWjb2_Jjido6F6yiMIlZvoyQ=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25246345/246977_Honor_Magic_V2_JPorter_0007.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;When folded, the phone’s thickness approaches that of a traditional large smartphone.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="honor Magic v2 folded, held in the hand." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/fLBXgSlHijbccKSn4spkkKinXzo=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25246339/246977_Honor_Magic_V2_JPorter_0002.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;It feels very similar to a regular smartphone when folded.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="JcfrGc"&gt;The cover screen is big enough that I was perfectly happy to use it for all the tasks I’d normally use a smartphone for, while the inner display was there for those times when I needed the extra screen real estate. There’s no ultra-thin glass used in the slightly plasticky-feeling internal display, and there’s still a visible crease when it catches a reflection, but Honor claims it should be able to withstand being folded 400,000 times, enough for roughly 10 years of use if you fold and unfold it 100 times a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KG3Jp6"&gt;As always, it’s difficult to know how these kinds of lab results will shake out in real-world usage. Folding a phone in a laboratory environment is one thing, but who knows how the phone will behave after it’s been squeezed into a jeans pocket or, say, a pair of running pants for two years. And there’s no IP rating for dust or water resistance, so you can’t count on the phone to easily handle dirt, dust, or splashes of water. That’s in contrast to the IPX8 rating on Samsung’s and Google’s foldables or the IPX4 rating on the OnePlus Open.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="VG1FDG"&gt;&lt;q&gt;Four years of Android updates, plus five years of security patches&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="YbYFnY"&gt;While its hinge could theoretically go the 10-year distance, software support is due to end much sooner. Honor is promising a respectable five years of security patches and four years of Android updates for the Magic V2, which is in line with what Samsung and OnePlus are promising for the Galaxy Z Fold 5 and OnePlus Open, respectively. (Google’s Pixel Fold gets three guaranteed years of Android version updates and five years of security patches.) Do note that the Honor Magic V2 ships with 2022’s Android 13, however, so one of those software updates will just be to get it up to date with Android 14.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1AvlRm"&gt;The phone’s hardware is built around last year’s Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Gen 2 rather than the Gen 3. Thankfully, the rest of the phone’s specs are more modern, and I didn’t notice any performance hiccups in daily usage. You get 16GB of RAM with 512GB of storage (rising to 1TB in the Porsche Design version of the phone) and a 5,000mAh battery that can be fast-charged at up to 66W. Unfortunately, like Samsung’s Z Fold 5 and the Pixel Fold, you don’t get a charging brick in the box, and it basically looks like you’ll have to buy &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.hihonor.com%2Fuk%2Faccessories%2Fhonor-supercharge-power-adapter-66w%2Fbuy%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F24051466%2Fhonor-magic-v2-review" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Honor’s 66W charging brick&lt;/a&gt; to get the maximum charging speeds. There’s no support for wireless charging, which is offered on the Z Fold 5 and Pixel Fold but not the OnePlus Open. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Unfolded Honor Magic V2 showing three apps onscreen at once." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/spwC88MsV1b7DPXVIi1R-jM2Xdc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25246347/246977_Honor_Magic_V2_JPorter_0009.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Two windows tiled with a third hovering over.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="QkIHt5"&gt;Keep the phone folded, and it really does feel like using a regular smartphone, but opening the Magic V2 up is when things get interesting. Like last year, you have the option of using apps across the entirety of the inner display or split screening them, and there’s also the ability to have a third window hovering over the display. It’s here that the benefits of the Magic V2 really shine, whether you’re watching a YouTube video while keeping half an eye on a noisy WhatsApp group chat or scrolling Threads while keeping abreast of Slack. But although these multitasking options are good, for my money, they’re not quite as flexible as what you’ll find on Samsung’s foldables (three tiled apps plus a fourth floating window) or OnePlus’s Open Canvas feature (three apps with multiple tiling options). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4OPvRl"&gt;I also experienced fewer pain points than I did when I reviewed Honor’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23743664/honor-magic-vs-review-foldable-phone"&gt;Magic VS&lt;/a&gt; last year.  Instagram can now expand to fill the entirety of the screen, Google Calendar no longer complains if you try to open it in split-screen mode, and Gboard will no longer obscure Slack’s text box when you open the latter in split-screen mode. Yes, far too many apps still appear with black bars on either side if you open them in full-screen mode, while others struggle to really make use of the extra horizontal screen real estate beyond just expanding to fill the empty space, but these problems are far from exclusive to Honor’s foldable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="vVNA7a"&gt;I continue to not love how Honor’s software is set up by default, but at least there’s now the option of enabling an app drawer to avoid having all your apps clutter up your homescreen. I also found the default “Dynamic” refresh rate (which attempts to find a balance between smoothness and power usage) laggy as all heck on the outer display, and you’ll want to set the refresh rate to “High” to feel like you’re actually using a 120Hz screen. The phone also comes with preinstalled bloatware including Facebook, TikTok, and Booking.com apps, which are easy enough to remove but feel a little insulting on a £1,699.99 device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Honor Magic V2 with notification warning about app power draw." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/RxsT1JFZY7Sqpj2KovFdp8v1Bac=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25246338/246977_Honor_Magic_V2_JPorter_0001.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;One of the warning messages I saw on a daily basis.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="qo4Zq0"&gt;Honor may have sanded down some of the rough edges, but quirks in its software remain. On a daily basis, the Magic V2 would warn me not to fold or unfold the screen “during use,” but I never experienced any of the display issues it warned about, and it wasn’t even clear what Honor’s device counts as use. I’d sometimes see this error message if I unfolded the phone without unlocking it and once when I hadn’t even unfolded the phone at all. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="iVVwXu"&gt;I also got daily warning messages that various apps, including X (formerly Twitter) or Threads, were draining power by refreshing too much in the background, which is not an issue I’ve had with any other phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="JAQX9u"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The warning messages make it seem as though the phone is buggier than it actually is&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="xcHNWr"&gt;In both cases, Honor’s device seems to be preemptively apologizing for problems that never arrive. Despite ignoring every one of the power drain warnings, I still averaged a respectable six-plus hours of screen-on time per charge and routinely put the foldable to charge at the end of the day with around 60 percent of its battery life remaining. The warning messages make it seem as though the phone is buggier than it actually is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="NNWkMy"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12233839"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="vhEM0Y"&gt;For cameras, the Magic V2 has a fairly typical triple array of sensors, including a 50-megapixel main, a 20-megapixel telephoto with a 2.5x optical zoom, and a 50-megapixel ultrawide. Honor typically likes its photos bright and colorful, and that continues to be the case here. Look at the photo above, and you’ll see the Magic V2 has squeezed every last ounce of blue and green the sky and grass had to offer on the winter morning I took it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gpfwAv"&gt;At the same time, however, it tends to overbrighten shadows, resulting in less overall depth and contrast, and there are times when it can go overboard with colors. This can also affect skin tones, emphasizing the pink in my face at the expense of darker beige, for example. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="C6ilwu"&gt;In low light, the Magic V2’s camera performance is inconsistent. Sometimes, it’ll hold on to colors just fine; other times, it’ll lose them. But either way, Honor’s software is content to smooth out grain and noise at the expense of detail, and low-light shots can look smudgy as a result. Shout out to the Magic V2’s close-up performance, however, where it did a great job focusing on small objects, even in low lighting conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Rear of the honor magic v2." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/wIvdcMIOeqYg28OGaX04xiPP5wo=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25246344/246977_Honor_Magic_V2_JPorter_0006.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The phone comes with a relatively standard three-camera setup.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="honor magic v2 folded standing on a desk." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/vOBvOVdL5eMgzZXNi4IgOQ2Pf7k=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25246342/246977_Honor_Magic_V2_JPorter_0004.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Not pictured: the preinstalled third-party apps.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="odmFXh"&gt;At £1,699.99 in the UK, the Magic V2’s price sits squarely between the Samsung Galaxy Z Fold 5 and Google Pixel Fold — which both start at £1,749 with less RAM and half the storage — and the £1,599 OnePlus Open with the same 16GB of RAM and 512GB of storage as Honor’s foldable. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="c2NiWL"&gt;That puts the Honor Magic V2 in a difficult position. It doesn’t have the IP rating, ultra-thin glass, wireless charging, or more powerful software of Samsung’s Z Fold 5. And the OnePlus Open manages to beat it on price, while also offering more multitasking options and less in the way of error messages. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="8aJH36"&gt;Honor’s Magic V2 is unquestionably an impressive piece of hardware. It really is slim and light enough to (mostly) feel like you’re using a regular smartphone until you want to unfold it. I just wish its software were similarly svelte.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="dq5gRa"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12233844"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="rMAgxi"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Jon Porter / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="sNGqD2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HLO2HK"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24051466/honor-magic-v2-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24051466/honor-magic-v2-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jon Porter</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-23T10:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-23T10:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>OnePlus 12 review: refreshingly basic</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;While Samsung and Google were busy shipping AI features as fast as possible, OnePlus doubled down on the essentials.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="trfzcU"&gt;In 2024, there’s one thing conspicuously missing from the sales pitch for the OnePlus 12: AI. And you know what? That’s fine. Great, even, depending on what you want out of your phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5I9m42"&gt;OnePlus’ flagship phone appears to be sitting out on the mobile tech trend of the year, which is even more obvious on the heels of Samsung’s Unpacked AI-palooza. The OnePlus 12 isn’t chasing the latest cutting-edge thing, it’s going back to the basics. And I think it gets them right — at least, a lot closer to “right” than OnePlus has in the last three years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ng9jlq"&gt;You know what’s not a hot buzz phrase in mobile tech right now? Battery life. You know what matters a whole lot to people buying a phone? Battery life. OnePlus put in some work here, and it shows: battery performance is among the best of any major flagship phone I’ve tested in the past six months. Wireless charging, a prerequisite for a flagship phone in 2024, is back after an absence on the OnePlus 11. OnePlus even kicked the IP rating up a notch from IP64 to IP65, which gives me just a little more confidence in its long-term durability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="tgPMBq"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12229996"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="YjTrTL"&gt;These improvements have come at a cost: an extra hundred bucks, or $799 versus $699 for the OnePlus 11. But that’s still on the low side for a high-end phone in 2024, especially one with a huge 6.8-inch display. It all makes the OnePlus 12 a more compelling package than its predecessor — it’s a phone worthy of a “Pro” or “Plus” title that costs a few hundred bucks less.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wgYCFp"&gt;None of these features are the kinds of new, groundbreaking tech you’ll see in Samsung or Google ads for their new phones. But at this stage, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/16/24040562/samsung-unpacked-galaxy-ai-s24"&gt;AI on mobile devices hasn’t exactly proven itself&lt;/a&gt; to be indispensable. Sure, a Galaxy or Pixel phone holds some additional appeal beyond AI if you’re entrenched in their ecosystems — or if you’re hooked on a Galaxy Watch or the Pixel Recorder app (it’s me). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="6rIR87"&gt;It’s also possible that those flashy new AI features will &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/19/24044251/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-ai-features-cost-2025"&gt;come with an extra cost&lt;/a&gt; somewhere down the line. If you’re not already devoted to another Android ecosystem, you want to sit out this hype cycle, or you just want a phone that does phone things well, then the OnePlus 12 might just be the one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="OnePlus 12 in hand with the camera on and a plant on-screen in the camera app." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ovJvp7zE1Y2pSFd2Te6WCfKmTAY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25242626/DSC06433.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Good camera, great screen.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="aF7QoC"&gt;For a phone priced well under $1,000, the OnePlus 12 really comes through with top-tier processing power starting with its Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 processor. OnePlus isn’t pushing any proprietary AI features, like generative AI photo editing or automatic language translation on phone calls, but thanks to that chipset it’ll be ready for whatever AI services Google eventually bundles and sells with a Google One subscription. You know, probably.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wp4JEb"&gt;On top of that, the $799 base model OnePlus 12 gets you 12GB of RAM and 256GB of storage. For $899, you get 16GB of RAM and 512GB of storage, like my review unit. For reference, the $799 Samsung Galaxy S24 and the $699 Google Pixel 8 both come with 8GB of RAM and 128GB of storage. In practical terms, it’s hard to throw anything at the OnePlus 12 that it can’t handle. It warms up noticeably with intensive gaming, but otherwise handles heavy processing tasks with ease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="E8WqOX"&gt;OnePlus tells us that it worked directly with Qualcomm to squeeze out an extra 30 minutes of battery life on top of what the Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 is capable of out of the box. That’s kind of impossible to test, however, I &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; say that I got through a full day of travel, including a two-hour flight delay, without a problem. When I finally got on board my flight, my seatmate mentioned that her phone was almost dead as she scrounged around for an outlet. I kept scrolling through Threads, untethered to wall wart or battery, just as smug as can be. That was with the always-on display enabled full time and with screen resolution at the highest 1440p setting, not the default 1080p.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="OnePlus 12 on a green and purple background showing home screen." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/fznGg9IRVFTYmWRmV8UZxZDxZHk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25242629/DSC06403.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The OnePlus 12 ships with Color, err, Oxygen OS 14.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="007lZL"&gt;Naturally, the OnePlus 12 offers incredibly fast wired charging — up to 80W with the included adapter and cable. Wireless charging comes and goes from OnePlus’ flagships, and I’m thrilled that it’s back on the 12. It supports up to 50W with the company’s proprietary charger (&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08WS5ZNLK?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;a cool $70 extra!&lt;/a&gt;) or 15W on a regular Qi charger (provided the charger itself can do 15W). Sure, it’s neat to drop it on a wireless charger and come back not an hour later to find it fully charged. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7rGwUd"&gt;But really, I’m just thrilled I can drop it on the same slow Qi charger that I use with every other phone and wake up to a fully charged device. There’s no Qi2 here, so if you were hoping for MagSafe-style accessories, you’ll have to settle for a third-party magnet case and “MagSafe-compatible.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="jqBPb1"&gt;The OnePlus 12’s 6.8-inch screen sings at that full 1440p resolution setting. It goes up to 120Hz so it looks fancy and smooth, and it’s as vibrant and detailed as any flagship phone screen I’ve looked at in recent history. It’s a 19.8:9 panel, so it’s a little taller and skinnier than its diagonal measurement suggests. I’m not a big fan of big phones, but I did find the OnePlus 12 easier to use one-handed than &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/17/24040715/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-specs-price-ai"&gt;another, wider 6.8-inch phone&lt;/a&gt; I’m testing. The curved edges help a little here, too, but I’d gladly trade them in for the flat panel edges that are in vogue now. Especially in bright light, viewing angles get a little wonky toward the edges of the screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="OnePlus 12 in hand showing tall format screen." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/rMdleAXunHJy731F9uPdW3mNIuw=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25242625/DSC06437_processed.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The screen’s tall aspect ratio makes it about as comfortable to use one-handed as it gets with a 6.8-inch screen.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="KoDDTJ"&gt;The beloved alert slider is here, and OnePlus has mostly reused the 11’s design for the 12. The rear camera “bump” is now see-through with a little sparkle that catches the light. The back glass panel uses a smooth matte finish that’s actually more slippery in your hand than a glossy panel. The whole thing is IP65 rated, which means it’s fully dustproof, while merely water resistant. Jumping up from IP64 means it’s better protected against water spray, so it should handle even the worst splashes and downpours fine. Just don’t expect to take it for a dip without consequences. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gqrXLF"&gt;OnePlus claims this screen has a peak brightness of 4,500 nits — that’s frankly &lt;em&gt;bonkers &lt;/em&gt;bright. Most other flagships claim somewhere between 2,000 and 2,400 nits at their brightest, and that’s enough to keep the screen comfortable to use in direct sunlight. I didn’t have any trouble using the OnePlus 12 outside on a bright day, but I also didn’t see anything that looked even close to 4500 nits of brightness. &lt;em&gt;Phone Arena&lt;/em&gt; has &lt;a href="https://www.phonearena.com/news/oneplus-12-display-max-brightness_id153236#"&gt;a good explanation of why that might be&lt;/a&gt;, but it comes down to how screen brightness is measured. In practice, I didn’t have any trouble using it on a bright day, but don’t expect the eye-searing brightness the specs suggest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dpy1Ai"&gt;The OnePlus 12 runs Oxygen OS 14, which looks a lot like Oxygen OS 13. There’s a new Dynamic-Island-esque status indicator called Fluid Cloud that currently only seems to work with a handful of apps — none of the rides or food deliveries I ordered popped up in the little pill icon at the top of the screen, but timers do. I think we’re moving toward a future where every phone has some kind of Dynamic Island of its own, and I’m for it. It’s a handy way to check time-sensitive stuff no matter what else you’re doing, and if there’s one good feature to crib from Apple, then this is it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="4sZc6f"&gt;&lt;q&gt;If you disliked the Color-OS-ification of Oxygen OS, then you probably won’t like this one much either&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="WPncW1"&gt;Generally, though, if you disliked the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/7/2/22560765/oneplus-oxygenos-coloros-oppo-android-updates"&gt;Color-OS-ification of Oxygen OS&lt;/a&gt;, then you probably won’t like this one much either. I find it inoffensive. I still opt out of using the “shelf” — a designated page in the system UI for widgets that’s usually accessible by swiping down on the homescreen — and instead assign the downward swipe to open the notification shade, as the lord intended. Personally, I’m enjoying Zen Mode more and more lately. It’s been around &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2019/5/14/18618382/oneplus-7-pro-review-android-camera-screen-phone-price"&gt;since the OnePlus 7 Pro&lt;/a&gt;, and it plays the kind of ambient spa music I need to be listening to while I write. It locks you out of certain apps, too — also helpful to the writing process. This is just a note of appreciation; don’t go buy a OnePlus phone for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZC2b4z"&gt;OnePlus promises four years of OS upgrades and five years of security updates for the 12, which is probably about as long as most people would plan to keep this phone. Recently, though, Google and Samsung have upped the ante by offering seven years of OS upgrades, including seven years of security updates for their flagship phones. If you want to squeeze the absolute most out of your investment, then seven years looks pretty good, ROI-wise. But, realistically, five years will probably do just fine for a lot of people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="a9oUu4"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12230041"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="I3687A"&gt;The jump from a 2x to 3x telephoto lens doesn’t sound like much on paper, but the upgraded telephoto camera on the OnePlus 12 makes a real difference. You get just a little closer to the details on distant subjects, and it provides a flattering angle for portrait subjects. The telephoto comes with optical image stabilization and uses a 64-megapixel sensor, so there’s enough resolution to take advantage of lossless crop zoom by using the pixels on the middle of the chip. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="cQE3TN"&gt;In low light, the telephoto will struggle to keep shutter speeds fast enough for moving subjects, but that’s a problem no phone maker has really cracked. But with plenty of light, the 3x turns in lots of detail. At 6x, the typical flaws of a tiny mobile camera lens are amplified and details can look smudgy, but only if you really go looking. All in all, it’s a big upgrade from the OnePlus 11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="BgfXFN"&gt;OnePlus’ partnership with Hasselblad continues, and it’s, like, 75 percent marketing hype. Where I think the collaboration has paid off is in the color tuning — color and contrast are some of the best in the business. The OnePlus 12 camera knows exactly what to do with warm backlighting, and it doesn’t look as prone as previous OnePlus cameras to over brightening indoor scenes. Using the 50-megapixel main camera in the standard shooting mode, I got a lot more sharp photos of my kid in a dimly lit children’s museum than I expected. Portrait mode is a little trickier, but again, OnePlus isn’t alone in that struggle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="OnePlus 12 on a purple background with green translucent rectangles." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/48Il7ANfDM7NsuxbZBRha9cOCYI=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25242624/DSC06375.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The OnePlus 12 puts the pieces together.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="NgzMGa"&gt;While Samsung and Google are busy shipping mobile AI features as fast as they can, the OnePlus 12 kind of feels like a refreshing break from the hype. I think there are &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23940685/qualcomm-snapdragon-summit-2023-8-gen-3-ai"&gt;legitimate uses for AI on our phones&lt;/a&gt;, but I also think we’re a year or two away from them really hitting their potential. Meanwhile, OnePlus has made some meaningful tweaks to its current formula, rather than going all in on something new. And it’s working.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="J83a8h"&gt;The improved telephoto coupled with excellent image processing means the OnePlus 12 has a camera system that can truly compete with the incumbent flagships. Wireless charging is back, as it should be, and a slight upgrade in water resistance makes me feel a little better about carrying this phone around the Pacific Northwest in all seasons. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="EuFdlh"&gt;&lt;q&gt;You’re just not going to find another 6.8-inch screen that looks this good at this price&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="tmb2fT"&gt;And I don’t want to undersell one of the 12’s main attractions: the screen. It’s not as fantastically bright as the specs suggest, but it’s a good all-around panel. More importantly, it’s big, and the people want big phones. I’m an exception to the rule, but I know my place. You’re just not going to find another 6.8-inch panel that looks this good at this price. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="LzOHv5"&gt;There are still good reasons to consider one of the aforementioned incumbents. The Samsung Galaxy S24 and the Pixel 8 series both include IP68 ratings for resistance against full water immersion and seven years of promised OS upgrades. They come with full-featured ecosystems of earbuds, tablets, and smart watches — something that OnePlus is still building out. And of course, they’re right at the forefront of the AI phone future — for better and worse. But for a big-screen device that gets all the regular phone stuff right, the OnePlus 12 is wonderfully basic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ECpFSy"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Allison Johnson / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hAY8Ml"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Correction January 23rd, 6:26PM ET: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;A previous version of this review stated that the OnePlus 12’s telephoto camera uses a 50-megapixel sensor; it uses a 64-megapixel sensor. We regret the error.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="SsC59h"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12230022"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="9vuyLH"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="yPDaxb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24047368/oneplus-12-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24047368/oneplus-12-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Allison Johnson</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2023-12-23T07:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-23T07:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>The Pixel 8 Pro’s videos get a whole lot brighter with video boost</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Image of Pixel 8 Pro lying on a pool table with the rear panel facing up and light reflecting on the camera lenses." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/gveef6_Q1SuzrPaW1UccIj_X9og=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/72993070/236823_Pixel_8_8Pro_Watch2_VPavic_0002.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Only the Pixel 8 Pro gets Video Boost, one of the AI camera features announced at its launch.&lt;/em&gt; | Photo by Vjeran Pavic / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="KzCyO9"&gt;When &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2018/11/14/18092660/google-night-sight-review-pixel-2-3-camera-photos-image-quality"&gt;Google introduced Night Sight&lt;/a&gt; on the Pixel 3, it was a revelation. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1i9Yd8"&gt;It was as if someone had literally turned on the lights in your low-light photos. Previously impossible shots became possible — no tripod or deer-in-the-headlights flash needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="t2mehq"&gt;Five years later and taking photos in the dark is old hat — just about every phone up and down the price spectrum comes with some kind of night mode. Video, though, is a different story. Night modes for still photos capture multiple frames to create one brighter image, and it’s just not possible to copy and paste the mechanics of that feature to video which, by its nature, is &lt;em&gt;already&lt;/em&gt; a series of images. The answer, as it seems to be lately, is to call on AI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EiMUKr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23900556/google-pixel-8-pro-hands-on-specs-price-launch"&gt;When the Pixel 8 Pro launched this fall&lt;/a&gt;, Google announced a feature called Video Boost with Night Sight, which would arrive in a future software update. It uses AI to process your videos — bringing out more detail and enhancing color, which is especially helpful for low-light clips. There’s just one catch: this processing takes place in the cloud on Google’s servers, not on your phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RpO69Q"&gt;As promised, Video Boost started arriving on devices a couple of weeks ago with December’s Pixel update, including my Pixel 8 Pro review unit. And it’s good! But it’s not quite the watershed moment that the original Night Sight was. That speaks both to how impressive Night Sight was when it debuted, as well as the particular challenges that video presents to a smartphone camera system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="7BAOR2"&gt;
&lt;div data-analytics-viewport="video" data-analytics-action="volume:view:article:middle" data-analytics-label="Video Boost|114848" data-volume-uuid="bcdc12058" data-volume-id="114848" data-analytics-placement="article:middle" data-volume-placement="article" data-volume-autoplay="false" id="volume-placement-507" class="volume-video"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original video on the left, boosted video on the right. There’s much more detail and color in the dark pergola pre-boost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="apgAK9"&gt;Video Boost works like this: first, and crucially, you need to have a Pixel 8 &lt;em&gt;Pro&lt;/em&gt;, not a regular Pixel 8 — Google hasn’t responded to my question about why that is. You turn it on in your camera settings when you want to use it and then start recording your video. Once you’re done, the video needs to be backed up to your Google Photos account, either automatically or manually. Then you wait. And wait. And in some cases, keep waiting — Video Boost works on videos up to ten minutes long, but even a clip that’s just a couple of minutes in length can take hours to process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="r2gcEP"&gt;Depending on the type of video you’re recording, that wait may or may not be worth it. &lt;a href="https://support.google.com/googlecamera/answer/14257322?hl=en"&gt;Google’s support documentation&lt;/a&gt; says that it’s designed to let you “make videos on your Pixel phone in higher quality and with better lighting, colors, and details,” in any lighting. But the &lt;em&gt;main&lt;/em&gt; thing that Video Boost is in service of is better low-light video — that’s what group product manager Isaac Reynolds tells me. “Think about it as Night Sight Video, because all of the tweaks to the other algorithms are all in pursuit of Night Sight.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="54wAyT"&gt;All of the processes that make our videos in good lighting look better — stabilization, tone mapping — stop working when you try to record video in very low light. Reynolds explains that even the &lt;em&gt;kind&lt;/em&gt; of blur you get in low light video is different. “OIS [optical image stabilization] can stabilize a frame, but only of a certain length.” Low light video requires longer frames, and that’s a big challenge for stabilization. “When you start walking in low light, with frames that are that long you can get a particular kind of intraframe blur which is just the residual that the OIS can compensate for.” In other words, it’s hella complicated. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="xQsXfU"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned="" data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C1FaaX7OU3y/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="14" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"&gt;&lt;div style="padding:16px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C1FaaX7OU3y/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="padding: 19% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"&gt;&lt;svg width="50px" height="50px" viewbox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;&lt;g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="padding-top: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"&gt;View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="margin-left: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="margin-left: auto;"&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C1FaaX7OU3y/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;" target="_blank"&gt;A post shared by The Verge (@verge)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="nB2mI7"&gt;This all helps explain what I’m seeing in my own Video Boost clips. In good lighting, I don’t see much of a difference. Some colors pop a little more, but I don’t see anything that would compel me to use it regularly when available light is plentiful. In &lt;em&gt;extremely &lt;/em&gt;low light Video Boost can retrieve some color and detail that’s totally lost in a standard video clip. But it’s not nearly as dramatic as the difference between a regular photo and a Night Sight photo in the same conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="QbvPSe"&gt;There’s a real sweet spot between these extremes, though, where I can see Video Boost really coming in handy. In one clip where I’m walking down a path at dusk into a dark pergola &lt;a href="https://seattlearts.emuseum.com/objects/1514/kobe-bell"&gt;housing the Kobe Bell&lt;/a&gt;, there’s a noticeable improvement to the shadow detail and stabilization post-Boost. The more I used Video Boost in regular, medium-low indoor lighting, the more I saw the case for it. You start to see how washed out standard videos look in these conditions — like my son playing with trucks on the dining room floor. Turning on Video Boost restored some of the vibrancy that I forgot I was missing. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="JsD1RW"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"2023 in smartphones: it was the little things","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23992429/smartphones-2023-foldables-photography-ai"},{"title":"All the news on Google’s Pixel 8 lineup","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/12/23914177/google-pixel-8-everything-need-know-news-announcment-review"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="0l8gCv"&gt;Video Boost is limited to the Pixel 8 Pro’s main rear camera, and it records at either 4K (the default) or 1080p at 30fps. Using Video Boost results in two clips — an initial “preview” file that hasn’t been boosted and is immediately available to share, and eventually, the second “boosted” file. Under the hood though, there’s a lot more going on. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="V6GUzg"&gt;Reynolds explained to me that Video Boost uses an entirely different processing pipeline that holds on to a lot more of the captured image data that’s typically discarded when you’re recording a standard video file — sort of like the relationship between RAW and JPEG files. A temporary file holds this information on your device until it’s been sent to the cloud; after that, it’s deleted. That’s a good thing, because the temporary files can be massive — several gigabytes for longer clips. The final boosted videos, however, are much more reasonably sized — 513MB for a three-minute clip I recorded versus 6GB for the temporary file. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TQWssR"&gt;My initial reaction to Video Boost was that it seemed like a stopgap — a feature demo of something that needs the cloud to function right now, but would move on-device in the future. Qualcomm showed off &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/24/23928867/qualcomm-snapdragon-8-gen-3-on-device-ai-meta-llama-2"&gt;an on-device version of something similar&lt;/a&gt; just this fall, so that must be the end game, right? Reynolds says that’s not how he thinks about it. “The things you can do in the cloud are always going to be more impressive than the things you can do on a phone.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="om4Jpb"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The distinction between what your phone can do and what a cloud server can do will fade into the background&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="2yzaeS"&gt;Case in point: he says that right now, Pixel phones run various smaller, optimized versions of Google’s HDR Plus model on-device. But the full “parent” HDR Plus model that Google has been developing over the past decade for its Pixel phones is too big to realistically run on any phone. And on-device AI capabilities will improve over time, so it’s likely that &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; things that could only be done in the cloud will move onto our devices. But equally, what’s possible in the cloud will change, too. Reynolds says he thinks of the cloud as just “another component” of Tensor’s capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Wb9IGV"&gt;In that sense, Video Boost &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a glimpse of the future — it’s just a future where the AI on your phone works hand-in-hand with the AI in the cloud. More functions will be handled by &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23940685/qualcomm-snapdragon-summit-2023-8-gen-3-ai"&gt;a combination of on and off-device AI&lt;/a&gt;, and the distinction between what your phone can do and what a cloud server can do will fade into the background. It’s hardly the “aha” moment that Night Sight was, but it’s going to be a significant shift in how we think about our phone’s capabilities all the same. &lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24012568/google-pixel-8-pro-video-boost-ai-photos"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24012568/google-pixel-8-pro-video-boost-ai-photos</id>
    <author>
      <name>Allison Johnson</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
