<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Reviews</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-15T11:26:53-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/reviews/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/reviews" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T11:26:53-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T11:26:53-04:00</updated>
    <title>Lenovo ThinkPad X1 Fold 16 review: setting the bar for foldables</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;Its beautiful 16-inch OLED display morphs into a 12-inch laptop, but do splurge for the ‘optional’ keyboard and folio. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text c-end-para" id="gX4lXL"&gt;Early into testing Lenovo’s ThinkPad X1 Fold 16 Gen 1, I briefly regretted purchasing its dual-display &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23794761/lenovo-yoga-book-9i-review"&gt;Yoga Book 9i&lt;/a&gt;. I bought it months ago, and it improved my day-to-day life in so many unexpected ways, I told myself I’d never buy another single-screen laptop. But then, the X1 Fold showed up with its folding OLED screen and tried to turn me into that Distracted Boyfriend meme as I transformed it from a 12-inch netbook to a 16-inch drawing tablet while shouting to my partner from downstairs, “Come look at this laptop!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2bL6sm"&gt;We spent some time folding and unfolding the laptop, sticking the curved centerfold close to our eyeballs so we could see how smooth the seam was. We quickly forgot that it folded in half as we played games and watched movies with it unfolded. I ultimately realized I had already bought the right laptop &lt;em&gt;for me&lt;/em&gt;, but the ThinkPad X1 Fold is a folding laptop done right, so hell yeah, I wanted it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="HIfIjC"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12277486"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ZaYRUk"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22175087/lenovo-thinkpad-x1-fold-review"&gt;Lenovo released its first X1 Fold in 2020&lt;/a&gt;, but it was too ahead of its time. Its well-built and beautiful OLED display couldn’t make up for a host of issues: short battery life; a small and dim display; an underpowered processor; a $2,500 starting price sans stylus or keyboard; and the fact that it didn’t always recognize whether it was being used as a tablet or as a laptop. Lenovo fixed almost all of those issues with its 2024 Fold. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="IDzsDo"&gt;The display is much bigger and much brighter. The battery life has doubled. The processing and integrated graphics performance have shot up like a puck hitting the bell atop a strongman carnival game. The design is even more gorgeous. Lenovo also threw in a stylus, and thank goodness it did because this laptop is as good a drawing tablet as it is a netbook. It is a better laptop in every way, except in price. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WvlWEz"&gt;Lenovo is still asking for $2,500, minimum, but the price is more justified this time around. The one caveat being it wants another $300 for a Bluetooth keyboard and kickstand folio, which are both crucial to the Fold experience. Its virtual keyboard works fine, but it’s not ideal for typing anything more than a few search phrases into Google. Plus I needed the folio to prop the ThinkPad Fold up next to my 27-inch monitor, which is how I use my Yoga Book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="k28p7v"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="imageslider:12277503"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="IT1UWX"&gt;Sure, I could drop $20 on a tablet stand big enough to accommodate the Fold’s 16-inch display, but it wouldn’t double as a keyboard cover, and it most certainly wouldn’t be as portable. I spent about an hour searching for a third-party magnetic keyboard but couldn’t find something suitable. Even if I did find one (I’m convinced they don’t exist) and it precisely covered the Fold’s bottom half, it probably wouldn’t tell the device to switch into laptop mode when attached. (I tried this with the Yoga Book’s included keyboard — no dice, and it’s too big for the Fold.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="qhc2Vi"&gt;So not only is it annoying that I’d have to buy Lenovo’s “optional” keyboard and folio to get the most out of this foldable laptop, but also the trackpad was frustrating to use. I had to clean my finger oils off the trackpad frequently or else it would miss too many swipes. That’s disappointing since typing on the keyboard is as nice as you’d expect from a ThinkPad or any other Lenovo laptop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A close-up showing the rounded corner of a foldable laptop display." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/KfOG7UH4dEUy47wWNmwPxj2kHXk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25305797/247033_Lenovo_ThinkPad_X1_Fold_16_JNelius_0009.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;No centerfold creases. No creaking noises.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="HoRgoC"&gt;Lucky for me that I most often used the ThinkPad X1 Fold the same way I use my Yoga Book 9i: connected to my monitor with a standalone keyboard and mouse. In that mode, the Fold worked better than my Yoga Book in some ways. Unlike the Yoga Book, which has two separate screens, the Fold’s hinge is behind its display and doesn’t create a gap in the middle of a paragraph, and I cannot emphasize enough how nice it was not to have to deal with &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; kind of screen gap during my time with the Fold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lWIbJK"&gt;However, my Yoga Book 9i’s two 13.3-inch physical displays do provide a larger workspace than the Fold, whether oriented horizontally or vertically. I also prefer how I can adjust the angle of the Book’s top screen to match my external monitor. Because the Book’s dual displays are connected with a visible center hinge, it doesn’t warp what’s in the center of the display like the ThinkPad Fold when I have one or two windows open. So I had to keep the Fold tilted at a similar angle to the Yoga Book’s bottom display, which was sort of awkward, but I forgot about it after a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="62Ajry"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12277490"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="yb5SFI"&gt;And that’s where my issues with the Fold end. One of my favorite Fold features is the fluidity of opening the laptop into desktop mode. When the keyboard is wrapped inside the folio cover, which attaches to the keyboard via a magnetic hinge, you simply open the ThinkPad Fold like a book until it’s totally flat, prop it up against the stand, and ta-da! All you need is a Starfleet uniform and a LCARS background, and you’re ready to go where not many laptops have gone before. (No? Just me?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="d7q6Ur"&gt;The outside surfaces of the laptop are adorned with finely woven strips of black recycled synthetic fiber (PET), and the texture is pleasantly tactile. Running my fingertips over it felt like a fabric-woven tote bag but smoother. It’s an elegant surface that hides fingerprints in its tiny crevices, too. Forget flat laptop lids, forget fun colors — I want more fun, classy textures in black! (Sorry, Yoga Book!) Those crevices do catch crumbs, so eating around the Fold is a no-go. The smaller the crumbs, the harder they are to pick out with your fingernail, but a small brush, about the size of a kid’s toothbrush, works to get them out if you have to get your snack on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="oGOu95"&gt;The Fold’s dimensions are well-balanced, which makes it feel lighter than it is while carrying with one hand or tucked into the crook of your arm. It’s only 0.68 inches thick and weighs 2.82 pounds (without the folio keyboard), which makes it one of the lightest laptops on the market — as light as a MacBook Air. I also liked how the magnetic stylus conveniently attaches to the bottom-right side in laptop mode.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A close-up of a laptop lid with a finely-woven, textured surface and a Lenovo badge." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/G5zbOgN4tC0L2evySTwO6TCUx4k=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25305798/247033_Lenovo_ThinkPad_X1_Fold_16_JNelius_0010.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;I’ve never been more enamored with a laptop lid.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="6boeiJ"&gt;I’m glad Lenovo ships a stylus with this laptop because, as a drawing tablet, this device is marvelously massive. Unfolded, it’s over 16 inches of OLED canvas that didn’t make my desk feel cluttered. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Mi7Uyv"&gt;I’m not an artist, but I gave drawing and painting a go with the Fold and didn’t find much to complain about. The experience felt nearly identical to Lenovo 2-in-1s and convertible laptops from other brands I’ve tested over the years, and the 2560 x 2024 display covers 96 percent of the DCI-P3 color gamut, so whatever paints Bob Ross decided to mix in the video, I could create a close digital version of his colors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Flj0iU"&gt;I could sometimes feel long, slender bumps spanning the length of the centerfold, which is not uncommon for folding displays. But once the entire device warmed up, it evened out, so that didn’t affect my ability to write and draw. The stylus itself was what gave me the most trouble.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A large drawing tablet showing splotches of digital paint in different colors." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/zgkeZ1h6VKx8z5yhwcv1gOTcKhM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25305791/247033_Lenovo_ThinkPad_X1_Fold_16_JNelius_0003.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;I’m no artist, but I enjoyed painting on such a large digital canvas.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="0opFlz"&gt;Well, most styluses give me trouble (thanks, dysgraphia), but the extra-pointy tip made it less fun to oil paint with Bob Ross in Adobe Fresco than it was to sketch an eye because it was difficult to find the right angle to mimic painting with a two-inch brush. To be fair to Lenovo, oil painting with &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; stylus feels totally different compared to the real thing, for obvious reasons, but once I figured out how to tweak the Fresco settings to get as close to Ross’ tried-and-true flat brushes as possible, I felt &lt;em&gt;mostly &lt;/em&gt;good about my happy digital clouds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gOhPoK"&gt;Watching movies and cloud gaming with ray tracing on was *chef’s kiss* thanks to the display’s color gamut, too, despite the 4:3 aspect ratio. &lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt; (I’m finally getting around to playing &lt;em&gt;Phantom Liberty&lt;/em&gt;) looked better on the Fold than my Gigabyte M28U gaming monitor, although I did have to mess around with the in-game resolution settings so everything didn’t look so squished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rgov80"&gt;Overall, Lenovo did a phenomenal job balancing the ThinkPad X1 Fold’s design with its hardware needs. I never had an issue with drawing applications lagging or running too many browser tabs (within reason). Its 12th Gen Intel U-series processor is miles ahead of the original’s Intel Core i5-L16G7, which was a sluggish five-core, five-thread processor designed to handle about 7W of power. (That’s right, no Hyper-Threading.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7UjbwX"&gt;In contrast, the Intel Core i5-1230U’s two performance cores are hyperthreaded (10-core, 12-thread), and its eight efficiency cores immensely helped with doubling the new Fold’s battery life; I was able to play &lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt; on GeForce Now with the display brightness maxed out (446 nits, as tested) for an average of five hours but averaged about nine to 10 hours at about 50 to 60 percent brightness if I was only using my computer for work-related tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A close, angled shot of a small laptop sitting on top of a gray kitchen counter." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/5S3_kdUUfydsQcHjkp-3wXCCjlM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25305796/247033_Lenovo_ThinkPad_X1_Fold_16_JNelius_0008.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;I normally don’t like netbook-sized laptops, but the Fold won me over.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="VMsiDG"&gt;Even with the stylus covering one of the three vents in laptop mode (there’s only one spot where it can magnetically attach, and &lt;em&gt;that’s&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;it&lt;/em&gt;), the Fold &lt;em&gt;never&lt;/em&gt; got hotter than a lukewarm bath. The CPU’s power draw is capped at 26W, even though it’s designed to draw up to 29W. The chassis never went above 31 degrees Celsius, either, so I could comfortably leave it flat on my lap for an hour while Bob Ross helped me brush up on my digital painting skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="l0t1sl"&gt;Lenovo’s ThinkPad X1 Fold 16 Gen 1 has set the bar as &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; foldable laptop to beat, even if the keyboard and folio are critical add-ons to an already not-cheap laptop. The only other folding screen laptops that could provide a comparable experience are the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/14/23870597/hp-spectre-fold-foldable-windows-laptop-release-date"&gt;HP Spectre Fold&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/26/23890518/lg-gram-fold-foldable-laptop-oled-display-17-inch-price-release-dates-specs-features"&gt;LG Gram Fold&lt;/a&gt;, but the latter is only available in South Korea, and we have not tested the former — not to mention that the Spectre Fold is twice the price of the ThinkPad Fold. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="obM6fd"&gt;Still, if this Lenovo foldable is a sign of where more laptop designs are headed, I’m all in. If the company can make a folding laptop the same size as its Yoga Book and include a keyboard and folio in the future, even if the price were still $2,500, I’d buy it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="XZ6sNj"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Joanna Nelius / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="VM2m2L"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12277508"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24099045/lenovo-thinkpad-x1-fold-16-2024-laptop-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24099045/lenovo-thinkpad-x1-fold-16-2024-laptop-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Joanna Nelius</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T09:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T09:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Mini but mighty: Blink’s tiny, inexpensive camera can now go outdoors</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;The new Blink Mini 2 wired security camera is a worthwhile upgrade to the Blink Mini, adding weather resistance, a wider field of view, and person detection for around $40.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="YcKzhV"&gt;Security cameras are a personal preference; understandably, many people don’t like the idea of potentially being watched in their homes. But these gadgets do offer useful features such as checking in on pets, monitoring your house when you’re away, or catching someone prowling in your backyard after dark. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wx22U0"&gt;The new &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0BWWZXWPL?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Blink Mini 2 ($39.99)&lt;/a&gt; is a solid inexpensive wired security camera that can be used indoors or outdoors to handle all of these scenarios. While there are a couple of wired cameras at this price point with more features, Blink’s latest offering, which just launched this week, ticks a lot of boxes. It’s especially good if you have an &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23751608/amazon-alexa-smart-home-controller-how-to"&gt;Amazon Alexa smart home&lt;/a&gt; or are already invested in Blink’s affordable battery-powered camera lineup. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="JXv2H4"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12278537"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="o5kAOC"&gt;Blink made its name with its inexpensive battery-powered cameras, which can last up to two years on two AAs. The company now offers three mains-powered models: the Blink Mini (1 and 2); the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22811985/best-smart-floodlight-security-camera#:~:text=With%201080p%20video,horizontally%20or%20vertically."&gt;Blink Wired Floodlight Camera&lt;/a&gt;; and the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/9/28/22698612/amazon-blink-video-doorbell-outdoor-camera-floodlight-solar-panel"&gt;Blink Video Doorbell&lt;/a&gt; (which can be wired or battery-powered). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uW4ov0"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/idUSKBN1FW0BJ/"&gt;Blink’s custom-built chip&lt;/a&gt; sets it apart from many other manufacturers. The company has developed super energy-efficient silicon, and a recent upgrade added on-device computer vision (CV). This enables person detection, which is found on the company’s newer cameras: the Floodlight; the Mini 2; and the new &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/24/23843590/blink-outdoor-4-security-camera-wireless-person-detection"&gt;Blink Outdoor 4&lt;/a&gt; ($120) battery-powered camera. (Person detection requires a Blink subscription.) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/k2h7hfvs414NlmjWfPlnPTMLcIY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25335553/8A0A1040.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The Blink Mini 2 can sit on a flat surface with or without its stand, which can be mounted to a wall or ceiling. However, the Mini 2 doesn’t work with the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="ql-link" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09N6YCT3Y?tag=theverge02-20" target="_blank" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blink Mini Pan Tilt mount&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="VHlqgo"&gt;The Mini 2 is a follow-up to the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/4/28/21231112/blink-mini-smart-home-camera-security-cam-review"&gt;Blink Mini&lt;/a&gt;, which took over from &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/5/30/23147362/amazon-cloud-cam-shutting-down-free-blink-mini-echo-replacement"&gt;Amazon’s indoor Cloud Cam in 2022&lt;/a&gt; after the retail giant &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/circuitbreaker/2017/12/22/16810516/amazon-blink-acquisition-smart-camera-doorbell-company"&gt;bought Blink in 2017&lt;/a&gt;, and it brings more to the table. Upgrades include indoor / outdoor compatibility, a new spotlight, on-device person detection, and USB-C power. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4TjbuK"&gt;There’s a wider field of view over the original Mini (143 degrees versus 110), enhanced image quality, better low-light performance, and a sleeker design. Plus, there’s still the option of local storage by adding a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B084RQ6MHJ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$50 Blink Sync Module 2&lt;/a&gt; and a USB stick (the module is not required to use the camera, only if you want local storage).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="BfU9Vr"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="imageslider:12278830"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="83hNzr"&gt;A teeny, tiny camera, the Mini 2 can fit pretty much anywhere. I tested it out in my chicken coop at the end of my garden, on my back patio, and in my office and kitchen, and it delivered clear, crisp video in all locations during the day. Infrared night vision was fair, but the spotlight-enabled color night vision was very grainy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="LGtAft"&gt;The Mini’s motion and people notifications are super speedy, but there are no rich notifications, which is a shame. Blink says this is due to its &lt;a href="https://support.blinkforhome.com/en_US/motion-detection/early-notification"&gt;Early Notification feature&lt;/a&gt;, designed to alert you as quickly as possible so you can drop in on a live view while the action is still happening. Personally, I prefer rich notifications with a snapshot of the action. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dxLStK"&gt;Two-way audio is still slightly staticky, an issue with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/9/28/22698612/amazon-blink-video-doorbell-outdoor-camera-floodlight-solar-panel"&gt;all Blink cameras I’ve tested&lt;/a&gt;. But it’s much improved over the original Mini. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="AAs79F"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12278543"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="kpWUt5"&gt;Blink has a great mounting system, and the ball and socket base on the Mini 2 makes it simple to adjust the camera’s angle and position even after you’ve screwed its base to a wall or ceiling. I could also just pop it on a flat surface without the base, which meant I could fit it everywhere I wanted to. It’s the smallest camera I’ve tested by far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="LjNU1L"&gt;The Mini 2 is also one of the least expensive security cameras you can buy, both out of the box and for cloud storage (just $3 a month — &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/8/24066592/ring-video-doorbell-security-camera-subscription-price-increase"&gt;Ring is now $5 a month&lt;/a&gt;, and Arlo and Google Nest start at $8). The addition of weather resistance (IP65 rated) makes it infinitely more useful, but you will need to pay extra for the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CBL57VRT?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Blink Weather Resistant Power Adapter&lt;/a&gt;, which is a sizable 13 feet long. It’s sold separately or in a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CRZC2R94?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;bundle with the camera for $49.98&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/T8r0OS3jDm8T_HXvYbbxUE__itY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25335559/8A0A1022.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Blink Mini 2 mounted using its side mounting option and outdoor cable in the chicken coop.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="YG8UHx"&gt;The Blink Mini 2 works with the Blink app with features such as customizable privacy and activity zones and two-way talk. The app is fairly basic but has plenty of customization options and schedules that let you arm and disarm your cameras (something you have to pay for with Ring). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WxzMZE"&gt;The camera’s motion sensitivity is good — almost too good. Without enabling person detection, I got alerts when the lights on one of my smart light strips changed color in my office. Adjusting the sensitivity helped a bit, but you need person detection if you don’t want to be inundated with notifications. Helpfully, you can snooze motion alerts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="BKOGk3"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12278545"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="PlQWlZ"&gt;If, like a lot of people, you don’t want to cough up $3 a month, you can still get motion alerts to let you know if something’s going on at home. But there’s no person detection without paying. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="E3hn85"&gt;You can also record video locally with a Sync Module 2 to avoid those cloud storage fees, but that’s an extra $50, and you won’t get person detection without a subscription and are limited to how long you can watch a live view; with a subscription, it’s up to 90 minutes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NJVlYj"&gt;The camera works with Amazon’s Echo smart displays to view livestreams, and I can pull up a view on my Echo Hub in a few seconds. It can also be set to announce motion or person detection on Echo speakers, but there’s no support for other smart home platforms. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="QK4n7P"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="imageslider:12278845"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="8Exnlx"&gt;The Mini’s closest competitors are models from Wyze and TP-Link, which both have indoor / outdoor cameras with smart alerts and local storage with an onboard microSD card for under $40: &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wyze.com%2Fproducts%2Fwyze-cam&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F24100149%2Fblink-mini-2-review" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Wyze with its $36 Wyze Cam v3&lt;/a&gt; and TP-Link with the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/1/23941020/tp-link-tapo-c120-indoor-outdoor-security-camera-price-release-date"&gt;Tapo’s $40 C120 indoor / outdoor wired camera&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wGYq3A"&gt;Considering &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/16/24075369/wyze-security-camera-stranger-feeds-glitch"&gt;Wyze’s recent security issues&lt;/a&gt;, the Tapo is the better option of the two. It also has better features than the Mini 2 — 2K video, dual spotlights, and free smart alerts for people, pets, and vehicles. Plus, there’s sound detection for dogs barking, babies crying, and cats meowing, making it potentially more useful than the Blink, especially as an indoor camera. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="361UmY"&gt;Personally, I’m not a big fan of indoor cameras, and as an outdoor wired option, the Blink worked better for me than the Tapo, streaming video from my chicken coop at the bottom of the garden more reliably. The Mini is also the smaller of the two cameras, comes in black or white, and has a longer outdoor power cable with a weatherproof plug (although it costs extra). But the Tapo does work with Google Home and Samsung SmartThings, which makes it a better choice if you use those platforms. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/vgTWf6HZ0YM6uUdWyykq8rSfUVo=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25335580/8A0A0904.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The sizable outdoor power cable for the Blink Mini 2 is very sturdy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mPMLXE"&gt;Overall, the Blink Mini 2 is an excellent upgrade to a popular inexpensive security camera. It’s very easy to set up and use — and its mounting system is one of the simplest and most flexible I’ve used. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="CPqIc0"&gt;Using this outdoors and cutting down on notification noise with person detection, all while staying under $50, are great improvements over the Mini 1. The video (both daytime and nighttime) and audio quality are noticeably better than the Mini 1. But the zoom is still limited, and I’d like to see more smart alerts for things like animals and vehicles; sound detection would be excellent, too. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5IabEz"&gt;My two biggest issues are that Blink’s app is not intuitive and it has limited smart home integrations. While the app has plenty of customization options, it feels clunky and outdated, especially compared to the excellent app of its sister company, Ring. I would love to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22704290/amazon-blink-ring-camera-doorbell-brands-smart-home-why"&gt;be able to use Blink cameras in the Ring app&lt;/a&gt;. The Blink Mini 2 is also locked in Amazon’s ecosystem, with no support for Google Home or Samsung SmartThings (although Blink &lt;a href="https://support.blinkforhome.com/en_US/ifttt/how-to-integrate-blink-with-ifttt-services"&gt;does support IFTTT&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="Vk08is"&gt;But if you use Alexa and / or other Blink cameras or are just looking for a simple security camera for a specific purpose and don’t need super high resolution, it’s a good, versatile, and affordable option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="cZGHhE"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12278867"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="miLE4j"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photos and screenshots by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24100149/blink-mini-2-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24100149/blink-mini-2-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jennifer Pattison Tuohy</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T08:30:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T08:30:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra review: just another big phone</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;It’s bigger for sure, but is that really better?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="50SrvP"&gt;The Zenfone is &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23777412/asus-zenfone-10-specs-screen-size-battery-camera"&gt;everyone’s favorite small-ish Android phone&lt;/a&gt;, except this year, it’s not: the Zenfone has gone Ultra. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HLiweD"&gt;Asus has adapted its gaming phone, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/8/24023549/asus-rog-phone-8-pro-ai-price-release-date-specs-features-gaming-smartphone"&gt;the ROG Phone 8&lt;/a&gt;, into a normie phone. It’s big, heavy, and it costs $899. It’s entirely inoffensive if big phones are your thing (&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/20/23730130/apple-iphone-13-mini-apple-phones"&gt;they aren’t mine, personally&lt;/a&gt;), but after a week of testing, I’m not seeing any compelling reason to pick it over any of the other big, heavy phones already on the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Iy6HF5"&gt;It’s possible that Asus will release a smaller Zenfone 11 later this year, but the company won’t say one way or the other whether it plans to do that. The last great small-ish Android phone &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/20/24078500/asus-zenfone-11-ultra-small-phone"&gt;might be dead&lt;/a&gt;, or it might not be. In the meantime, another big Android phone just dropped — and it’s a fine device, but I’m not sure we needed it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="RUlcFH"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12278351"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="EJA7iO"&gt;Look, I get the appeal of a big phone. You know what a big phone has a lot of? Screen. Screen as far as the eye can see! The Zenfone 11 Ultra — again, like the ROG Phone 8 Pro — offers a 6.78-inch OLED panel. It can go up to 144Hz, but only in gaming mode. The rest of the time, it’ll go up to 120Hz or, since it’s an LTPO display, down as low as 1Hz to save on battery life. It’s only 1080p, though, so it’s not quite as crisp as its competitors with 1440p displays, like the OnePlus 12 and Samsung Galaxy S24 Plus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hRyXP5"&gt;Big phones also come with big batteries, and I have zero complaints with the Zenfone 11 Ultra’s massive 5,500mAh battery. I easily got through a full day without dropping under 50 percent, and I’d feel reasonably confident stretching this battery to two days. It also supports wireless charging — not Qi2 though, just regular 15W Qi. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra on a yellow background showing homescreen." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/FRcLpcB4ntH6u2fudZklZWsk6kc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334617/DSC07066.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;More phone, more screen. Those are the rules.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="WqyM4T"&gt;The Zenfone 11 Ultra uses a Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 chipset, the top-tier processor of choice for Android phone makers, and the base model comes with a beefy 12GB of memory and 256GB of storage. I doubt I pushed its gaming phone DNA to the limit with my &lt;em&gt;Pocket City 2&lt;/em&gt; sessions — designating commercial zones and adjusting income tax sliders is probably not what the Republic of Gamers had in mind — but the 11 Ultra handled every task I threw at it with ease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KKDxOF"&gt;Like previous Zenfones, the 11 Ultra will work on AT&amp;amp;T and T-Mobile but not on Verizon. Hypothetically, you &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; use it on the Verizon network if you live in an area with good 5G coverage and you have a physical SIM card. Just theoretically speaking. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra on a yellow background showing blue back panel at an angle." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/T17eZ3f39IZI2pcRNQ0f02DXqg8=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334618/DSC07077.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;This design doesn’t do it for me, but you know what does? The Zenfone’s IP68 rating.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="dS2X5B"&gt;I definitely wouldn’t recommend it for full-time use, though, because you might see a worrying “No Service” notification pop up at the top of your screen every once in a while, and while texting and data work fine, placing phone calls seems to be a no-go. Sort of a crucial “telephone” feature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="z6Dswn"&gt;In the abstract, I like the Zenfone 11 Ultra’s design. Like, if I saw it in an ad in a design magazine, the cool blue finish and architectural camera bump would look kind of nice, you know? If I’m being honest, though, it’s not my favorite. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra on a yellow background showing headphone jack." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/yfcC0MetWZaVk1qc47pxysLZzqM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334621/DSC07086.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Look, a headphone jack! They do exist!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mGJqnw"&gt;The black edges and camera bump seem out of step with the sleek, slightly matte back panel. But mainly, I’m annoyed at how heavy and &lt;em&gt;dense &lt;/em&gt;it is. More than once, it slid out of my jacket pocket and into the crevice between the driver’s seat and center console with an alarming thud. I did not enjoy this one bit. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="XnSbav"&gt;Asus is keeping up with the times and includes a handful of AI features on the 11 Ultra, including a call translation feature that seems to work exactly like Samsung’s version. Nice to have, but the AI noise cancellation for calls is something that seems more broadly useful. It works both ways, cleaning up the audio for the listener and speaker — &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/13/23552300/google-pixel-7-pro-clear-calling-noise-cancellation"&gt;Google’s version for the Pixel&lt;/a&gt; only cancels out noise on the other end of the call so &lt;em&gt;you’ll&lt;/em&gt; have an easier time hearing if they’re in a noisy environment. I couldn’t test it out because I’m on Verizon. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="VEX6jQ"&gt;AI features are great and all, but one thing that’s more important to most people? The camera.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;The Zenfone’s coolest camera trick remains its gimbal-like stabilization. During video recording, it smooths out bumps and movement incredibly well — and if you need proof that it’s really working, you can take a close look at the main camera lens &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/allisonjo1/status/1552668060351229953?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1552668060351229953%7Ctwgr%5Ee8f3b925925024314d186b82cbf77d14cd42a758%7Ctwcon%5Es1_c10&amp;amp;ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2022%2F7%2F28%2F23280728%2Fasus-zenfone-9-screen-camera-specs-price-ois-gimbal-stabilization-video"&gt;to see it moving&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="C0HEIg"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12278502"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="4E78jh"&gt;There’s even a HyperSteady mode that corrects for bigger movements — violently shaking the camera back and forth just looks like moderate swaying. It crops in a lot, and you need plenty of light to use it, but it’s cool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="6hpJru"&gt;Outside of video mode, the 11 Ultra looks pretty average. Portrait mode cutouts are surprisingly good, and the system chose shutter speeds fast enough to get plenty of sharp photos of my kid playing indoors. But the 11 Ultra’s cameras overall are a little inconsistent — auto white balance jumps around occasionally, and photos sometimes have a too-bright, overexposed look about them. Sometimes they don’t! But that’s the problem: inconsistency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Asus Zenfone 11 Ultra in hand showing homescreen." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/6eeyEmn4_Pwm58cr-xHhTebJw3U=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334622/DSC07091.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;It’s hard out there for a big Android phone.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="nNzG9h"&gt;It’s Big Android Phone season, because the Zenfone 11 Ultra arrives on the heels of the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24058916/samsung-galaxy-s24-plus-review-screen-battery-camera"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S24 Plus&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24053907/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-review-ai-screen-camera-battery"&gt;S24 Ultra&lt;/a&gt;, and the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24047368/oneplus-12-review"&gt;OnePlus 12&lt;/a&gt;. They all use the same chipset (well, provided you buy the S24 Plus in the US) and not-a-one of them has a screen smaller than 6.7 inches. I can clearly recommend three out of four of these phones, but the Zenfone, I’m just not sure about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4E22F8"&gt;The Galaxy S24 Ultra is the obvious pick for someone who wants the absolute most out of their phone. The $799 OnePlus 12 is the right choice if you want a big screen and want to spend a little less. For everyone else, there’s the Galaxy S24 Plus — the crowd-pleaser that’s readily available with trade-in and carrier deals galore. The Zenfone just doesn’t earn a clear space for itself here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7MQyjM"&gt;Maybe if it had an outstanding camera or it had better network support in the US or, I don’t know, &lt;em&gt;a thoughtful form factor unlike anything else on the market. &lt;/em&gt;The Zenfone 11 Ultra does plenty of things well but isn’t great in any one way. As it stands, it’s just one more big phone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="COd5B8"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Allison Johnson / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="4flm3O"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12278353"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24099978/asus-zenfone-11-ultra-review-screen-battery-camera"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24099978/asus-zenfone-11-ultra-review-screen-battery-camera</id>
    <author>
      <name>Allison Johnson</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T02:47:06-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T02:47:06-04:00</updated>
    <title>Microlino electric bubble car review: urban delight</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/tkWFSgkYXWSk1vQUag3N9oyyM5k=/0x238:5712x4046/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73205992/IMG_2276.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Microlino Dolce is a throwback to mid-century bubble cars.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;Fun, fun, fun till a trailer towed my baby away.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="632lH8"&gt;“Wow, what an entrance!” said a well-coiffed woman as other patrons seated at the sidewalk cafe, now standing, began to applaud my exit from the electric bubble car like I was stepping out of a limousine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="I07a2i"&gt;That really happened in one of Amsterdam’s wealthiest neighborhoods, on a street dotted with Range Rovers and a G-Class Merc costing nearly ten times as much as the little &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Isetta"&gt;BMW Isetta&lt;/a&gt; throwback I was driving. What followed was a bevy of questions I had already answered dozens of times in my one week with the car: What is it? How much does it cost? Can I drive it on the highway?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="b8SW5l"&gt;It’s an Italian-made &lt;a href="https://microlino-car.com/en/microlino"&gt;Microlino&lt;/a&gt; from a Swiss-company called Micro with prices starting at around €18,000 (about $19,500). Yes, it’s highway legal. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="EvDcNt"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned="" data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C4TDi5frKa5/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="14" style=" background:#FFF; border:0; border-radius:3px; box-shadow:0 0 1px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.5),0 1px 10px 0 rgba(0,0,0,0.15); margin: 1px; max-width:658px; min-width:326px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"&gt;&lt;div style="padding:16px;"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C4TDi5frKa5/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%;" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;div style=" display: flex; flex-direction: row; align-items: center;"&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 40px; margin-right: 14px; width: 40px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 100px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 60px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="padding: 19% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display:block; height:50px; margin:0 auto 12px; width:50px;"&gt;&lt;svg width="50px" height="50px" viewbox="0 0 60 60" version="1.1" xmlns="https://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="https://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;&lt;g stroke="none" stroke-width="1" fill="none" fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;g transform="translate(-511.000000, -20.000000)" fill="#000000"&gt;&lt;g&gt;&lt;path d="M556.869,30.41 C554.814,30.41 553.148,32.076 553.148,34.131 C553.148,36.186 554.814,37.852 556.869,37.852 C558.924,37.852 560.59,36.186 560.59,34.131 C560.59,32.076 558.924,30.41 556.869,30.41 M541,60.657 C535.114,60.657 530.342,55.887 530.342,50 C530.342,44.114 535.114,39.342 541,39.342 C546.887,39.342 551.658,44.114 551.658,50 C551.658,55.887 546.887,60.657 541,60.657 M541,33.886 C532.1,33.886 524.886,41.1 524.886,50 C524.886,58.899 532.1,66.113 541,66.113 C549.9,66.113 557.115,58.899 557.115,50 C557.115,41.1 549.9,33.886 541,33.886 M565.378,62.101 C565.244,65.022 564.756,66.606 564.346,67.663 C563.803,69.06 563.154,70.057 562.106,71.106 C561.058,72.155 560.06,72.803 558.662,73.347 C557.607,73.757 556.021,74.244 553.102,74.378 C549.944,74.521 548.997,74.552 541,74.552 C533.003,74.552 532.056,74.521 528.898,74.378 C525.979,74.244 524.393,73.757 523.338,73.347 C521.94,72.803 520.942,72.155 519.894,71.106 C518.846,70.057 518.197,69.06 517.654,67.663 C517.244,66.606 516.755,65.022 516.623,62.101 C516.479,58.943 516.448,57.996 516.448,50 C516.448,42.003 516.479,41.056 516.623,37.899 C516.755,34.978 517.244,33.391 517.654,32.338 C518.197,30.938 518.846,29.942 519.894,28.894 C520.942,27.846 521.94,27.196 523.338,26.654 C524.393,26.244 525.979,25.756 528.898,25.623 C532.057,25.479 533.004,25.448 541,25.448 C548.997,25.448 549.943,25.479 553.102,25.623 C556.021,25.756 557.607,26.244 558.662,26.654 C560.06,27.196 561.058,27.846 562.106,28.894 C563.154,29.942 563.803,30.938 564.346,32.338 C564.756,33.391 565.244,34.978 565.378,37.899 C565.522,41.056 565.552,42.003 565.552,50 C565.552,57.996 565.522,58.943 565.378,62.101 M570.82,37.631 C570.674,34.438 570.167,32.258 569.425,30.349 C568.659,28.377 567.633,26.702 565.965,25.035 C564.297,23.368 562.623,22.342 560.652,21.575 C558.743,20.834 556.562,20.326 553.369,20.18 C550.169,20.033 549.148,20 541,20 C532.853,20 531.831,20.033 528.631,20.18 C525.438,20.326 523.257,20.834 521.349,21.575 C519.376,22.342 517.703,23.368 516.035,25.035 C514.368,26.702 513.342,28.377 512.574,30.349 C511.834,32.258 511.326,34.438 511.181,37.631 C511.035,40.831 511,41.851 511,50 C511,58.147 511.035,59.17 511.181,62.369 C511.326,65.562 511.834,67.743 512.574,69.651 C513.342,71.625 514.368,73.296 516.035,74.965 C517.703,76.634 519.376,77.658 521.349,78.425 C523.257,79.167 525.438,79.673 528.631,79.82 C531.831,79.965 532.853,80.001 541,80.001 C549.148,80.001 550.169,79.965 553.369,79.82 C556.562,79.673 558.743,79.167 560.652,78.425 C562.623,77.658 564.297,76.634 565.965,74.965 C567.633,73.296 568.659,71.625 569.425,69.651 C570.167,67.743 570.674,65.562 570.82,62.369 C570.966,59.17 571,58.147 571,50 C571,41.851 570.966,40.831 570.82,37.631"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="padding-top: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" color:#3897f0; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:550; line-height:18px;"&gt;View this post on Instagram&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="padding: 12.5% 0;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: row; margin-bottom: 14px; align-items: center;"&gt;
&lt;div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(0px) translateY(7px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; height: 12.5px; transform: rotate(-45deg) translateX(3px) translateY(1px); width: 12.5px; flex-grow: 0; margin-right: 14px; margin-left: 2px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; height: 12.5px; width: 12.5px; transform: translateX(9px) translateY(-18px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="margin-left: 8px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 50%; flex-grow: 0; height: 20px; width: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 2px solid transparent; border-left: 6px solid #f4f4f4; border-bottom: 2px solid transparent; transform: translateX(16px) translateY(-4px) rotate(30deg)"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="margin-left: auto;"&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0px; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-right: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(16px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; flex-grow: 0; height: 12px; width: 16px; transform: translateY(-4px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" width: 0; height: 0; border-top: 8px solid #F4F4F4; border-left: 8px solid transparent; transform: translateY(-4px) translateX(8px);"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style="display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-grow: 1; justify-content: center; margin-bottom: 24px;"&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; margin-bottom: 6px; width: 224px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div style=" background-color: #F4F4F4; border-radius: 4px; flex-grow: 0; height: 14px; width: 144px;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; line-height:17px; margin-bottom:0; margin-top:8px; overflow:hidden; padding:8px 0 7px; text-align:center; text-overflow:ellipsis; white-space:nowrap;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/C4TDi5frKa5/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" style=" color:#c9c8cd; font-family:Arial,sans-serif; font-size:14px; font-style:normal; font-weight:normal; line-height:17px; text-decoration:none;" target="_blank"&gt;A post shared by The Verge (@verge)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="//platform.instagram.com/en_US/embeds.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ZxqX6J"&gt;While cars in general are embiggening, in some cities a new breed of electric microcars are trending. They’re cheaper to own, easier to park, consume less public space and energy, and maneuver around obstacles that would otherwise block big SUVs and snarl traffic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mbaZ86"&gt;And you know what? Some, like the Microlino, are so much fun that maybe, just maybe, they’ll help reverse the trend of people buying increasingly larger and heavier cars. Assuming they’ve fixed a software issue that bricked my test car at the end of the review (more on that later).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/8-U1UsLRfSat-2CM-NWNkJtJ9G0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25324766/IMG_2073.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Microlino next to an Opel Rocks, aka, the Citroen Ami in other markets. So small.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ot8A9G"&gt;Let me start by saying that I don’t own a car, but I do regularly drive one. I’ve &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2015/12/3/9841104/why-own-a-car-when-you-can-share-one-instead"&gt;long subscribed to a car sharing service&lt;/a&gt; with a dedicated fleet parked in dedicated spots around town, that lets me select the right car for my current need: compact, wagon, or panel van; gas or EV. But not everyone lives in a city that spent the last 50-odd years trying to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23572761/amsterdam-underwater-bike-garage-future-of-transport"&gt;break away from car dependency&lt;/a&gt; to perfect multimodal transport, so the desire to own a large car that can do &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the car things is understandable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mJv0DM"&gt;Yet even here in Amsterdam — a city dominated by bicycles with easy access to good public transportation — there are still lots of privately owned cars suffering from autobesity, just sitting there on the street &lt;a href="https://www.racfoundation.org/research/mobility/spaced-out-perspectives-on-parking"&gt;unused 96 percent of the time&lt;/a&gt;, by some accounts. That’s space that could be used for public walkways, cycleways, benches, cafes, greenery... or about three microcars parked side by side. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/1NhUKCsmubg8eDGuOLGp_h4xDNc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25322671/IMG_2133.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;em&gt;On this day, I added 6.16kWh &lt;/em&gt;— &lt;em&gt;taking it from about 40 percent to 100 percent charge in about three hours. It cost $2 on a nearby public 11kW charger.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="NAiNZK"&gt;The midtier Microlino Dolce I reviewed starts at €20,000 (about $21,700) and is an absolute joy for quick trips to the market or dropping a kid at school while staying warm and dry in bad weather. It has a top speed of 90km/h (55mph) and range of up to 228km (142 miles) for destinations well beyond the city center. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="yaYVyz"&gt;Last weekend, I drove my wife and dog to the sea and back and then returned to the dunes for a trail run the following day before needing to recharge the Microlino, for a real-world range of about 110km. I plugged it in at one of the 12 public 11kW AC chargers in the parking lot with about 20 percent remaining, and returned from my run 90 minutes later to find a 50 percent charge — more than enough for the 30-minute drive home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rhlo23"&gt;The Microlino’s no speed demon, but it’s still an EV and so lightweight that I’d beat unsuspecting taxis off the starting line and “win” the merged lane. The small and responsive steering wheel and super stiff suspension contribute to a go-kart feel when whipping around corners and through traffic circles at I-should-know-better speeds. “It feels like a real car,” is how one owner of a &lt;a href="https://biro.nl/en/model/biro-dressed-small-b2211/"&gt;€15,000 (about $16,300) Biro&lt;/a&gt; — one of the first and most popular electric microcars to seduce Amsterdammers — described driving the Microlino.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid__wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/SBCmv5fx5J1zlbANT0ql3EuqHTE=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25324752/IMG_2555.jpeg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/dKZSxwMvc8pLsaoNzbMt5dxT2gw=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25324760/IMG_2655.jpeg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/G447SrxHW7016W_S7f1_6p30GqA=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25324761/IMG_2210.jpeg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/g8RnCuNEyHE_A-fcba5nB3amevU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25324762/IMG_2034.jpeg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The hinged front makes it very easy to get in and out of the microcar, even in the tightest of spaces.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="s6Fv7w"&gt;It’s not without its faults, however. To start with, there’s a lot of plastic inside the Microlino (but the windows are all glass unlike some microcars). One plastic clip helping to keep a plastic service panel in place snapped off in my brief time with the car, which I received with just 10km on the odometer. The motor has a distinct whine, the phone holder rattles when empty, the wiper motor is noisy, and the fan has two settings: loud or louder. The only thing that isn’t loud is the included portable Bluetooth speaker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="TeBh9W"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12272065"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ncknUD"&gt;I also watched the main display reboot once while driving but without any impact on the motor or controls (thankfully!). And while the front door has a nice soft-close mechanism, the trunk requires a solid slam to catch. The sloped-back roof also exposes the interior to rain when the door is open, and I experienced some drips while driving around curves due to water that must have collected in the door closure. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="o5CRfd"&gt;The “vegan” (fake) leather on the seats and steering wheel were nice touches on my Dolce Edition, as was the intuitive mechanical sunroof, but overall I’d describe the fit and finish of the Microlino Dolce as basic. At least until I drove a top-end Biro and realized just how superior the Microlino was by comparison. A Microlino is a tiny expensive car, whereas a Biro is a tiny expensive golf cart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1sxE3w"&gt;The Microlino did, however, suffer a total failure after sitting on a 11kWh public charger for about four hours. When I returned to what should have been a fully charged car, it wouldn’t power on. After hauling it away on a trailer, Micro identified the issue and assures me it won’t affect future cars. They blamed the problem on a system that protects the car against peak voltage from the charging station, which “was not adjusted correctly after a software update.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RETW4h"&gt;Micro tells me that my poor little guy is fine after the update. Good, but such a failure would have been a huge hassle if I was the vehicle’s owner, and without the priority attention afforded to journalists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="9InneG"&gt;Still, despite the mishap and all my nitpicking, none of the aforementioned issues are enough to dissuade my enthusiasm for the Microlino — it’s &lt;em&gt;that much fun&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="1kNrFc"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12273119"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="T1kkpt"&gt;As much as I enjoyed my week with the Microlino, I’m not yet a convert — there’s simply no faster, more convenient, or healthier way of going door to door than on a bicycle in cities with good cycling infrastructure, despite the rain and cold for which I can dress. And less capable but very appealing microcars like the &lt;a href="https://www.opel.nl/personenwagens/rocks-electric/overzicht.html"&gt;Opel Rocks&lt;/a&gt; (sold as the &lt;a href="https://www.citroen.co.uk/ami"&gt;Citroen Ami&lt;/a&gt; in some markets) can be had for half the price at €8,700 (about $9,470).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NnQYsz"&gt;The Microlino isn’t for everyone. Hell, microcars aren’t even for most people. But they are for anyone who wants a vehicle that’s more nimble, efficient, inexpensive, and fun to drive than a full-sized car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HEYfYm"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fun&lt;/em&gt;... there’s that word again. I can’t help but return to it even if it’s impossible to quantify. But anecdotally, my time with the Microlino delivered more smiles per city kilometer — both inside and outside the car — than &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23735554/vw-id-buzz-review-ququq-camper-e-vanlife"&gt;any car&lt;/a&gt; I’ve ever been in, and I’d wager more than any new car available today, no matter the size or price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="kzlQah"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Thomas Ricker / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24093189/microlino-review-microcar-specs-price"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24093189/microlino-review-microcar-specs-price</id>
    <author>
      <name>Thomas Ricker</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-09T09:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-09T09:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Withings ScanWatch 2 and Light review: simple vibes for the tech-fatigued</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;These watches hit a nice balance between style and function without bombarding you with information.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="3Gn1eI"&gt;These days, there’s been an uptick in people asking me about simple yet stylish smartwatches. Emphasis on simple. Begone fancy health and training features! Stuff the third-party apps! All they want is a device that looks nice, has bare-bones tracking, and doesn’t need frequent charging. Everything else — the Apple Watches, the Samsung Galaxy Watches, the Pixel Watches — comes with too many bells and whistles. Inevitably, the daily charging gets old, and these expensive watches end up collecting dust in a drawer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GvtluA"&gt;If that’s you, the $349.95 Withings ScanWatch 2 or the $249.95 ScanWatch Light is worth a gander. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;div id="FYkqI1"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12271347"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="0AFOzc"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12271350"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="D48zPw"&gt;Get ready for compliments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="vVe2YX"&gt;When I wore these outside, I got stopped a lot by friends, family, co-workers, and the occasional stranger. “That looks really nice,” they all said. “Where did you get it?” That rarely happens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="yeZzii"&gt;Hybrid smartwatches like these are essentially dressier, incognito versions of yesteryear’s fitness bands stuffed inside an analog watch. Recently, on Threads, I saw &lt;a href="https://www.threads.net/@chrisltd/post/C3WblarNsh4"&gt;a spirited discourse&lt;/a&gt; about whether you should wear an Apple Watch to a fancy dinner. Well, if you wore one to a wedding, only the eagle-eyed would notice that it’s a smartwatch.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Overhead view of person wearing Withings ScanWatch 2 and ScanWatch Light" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/_Bpup4VZyOwHt720IUk2BuWzqGo=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25282437/247014_Withings_ScanWatch_2_Light_AKrales_0117.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Similar styles but slightly different vibes. The ScanWatch 2 (white) has an extra dial to track step goal progress.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="lLptBt"&gt;The ScanWatch 2 is elegant, while the Light is sporty. A lot of it boils down to color and materials. The ScanWatch 2 has sapphire crystal and an extra dial for tracking step goal progress. It also opts for neutral colors like Withings’ classic white or black faces. (There’s also a fetching navy option.) The Light opts for Gorilla glass and comes in a fun minty green or a pale blue in addition to the black and white versions. Both have stainless steel cases in either silver or rose gold, with plenty of strap options. Outside of design, the ScanWatch 2 has more sensors and health tracking features, while the Light is a pared-down version that’s $100 cheaper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="hiVylx"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Withings ScanWatch knows when you’re sleeping and when you’re awake, but not why ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/21455863/withings-scanwatch-review-health-sleep-features-price"},{"title":"The best fitness trackers to buy right now ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/22985108/best-fitness-tracker"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="dz1LJX"&gt;I’d describe my style as “aggressively casual,” but neither watch stuck out like a sore thumb with plaids, band T-shirts, and jeans. Both were also easy to dress up for occasions when I had to look like a put-together adult.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="vQCCp4"&gt;I have small wrists, but the 37mm Light was just the right size — and comically tiny whenever I’d compare it to the 49mm &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23878981/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-review-double-tap-precision-finding-siri"&gt;Apple Watch Ultra 2&lt;/a&gt; on my other arm. The 38mm ScanWatch 2 was similar in feel, though that also comes in a larger 42mm model. These are on the smaller side for smartwatches, so if you want something bigger, they might not fit the bill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="MmPQet"&gt;Bare-bones basics for the tech-fatigued&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="ST3MRj"&gt;These are for the folks who say a watch is for telling the frickin’ time... and maybe one or two other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="eepC4R"&gt;That’s because neither watch conveys information, aside from the time, particularly well. All you get is a tiny grayscale OLED display. If you want to read a notification, you have to wait for it to slowly scroll through. Since there’s no touchscreen, you have to use the digital crown to scroll through menus and press it to select something. I’ll put up with it to start a workout, but I’m less inclined to do it for timers or EKG readings. It’s much less tedious than the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23220102/fossil-gen-6-hybrid-review-smartwatches-wearables"&gt;Fossil Gen 6 Hybrid&lt;/a&gt;’s interface, but most days, it was easier to think of this as a regular watch.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Overhead view of person wearing Withings ScanWatch 2" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/8C7lGp8lBspgU_kSUepqJBprFnU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25282438/247014_Withings_ScanWatch_2_Light_AKrales_0122.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;That tiny OLED window isn’t great for conveying information. It’s better for notification triaging.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="Y3tXX6"&gt;As with older fitness bands, this is most useful for triaging notifications and passively tracking basic metrics. “Oh, what’s this buzz? Brad emailed. Brad can wait.” (You can also choose which apps ping you.) Besides, you’ll need to pull out your phone to take calls or view your data anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="szQNdG"&gt;That can be good! If you want to be more present, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24084772/celebrities-no-phone-bieber-sheeran-cruise-cera-ipad"&gt;going low-tech can be a useful tool&lt;/a&gt;. Navigating menus on the ScanWatch is tedious, which means I’m less likely to get distracted by a message. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="AwqmB2"&gt;&lt;q&gt;If you want to be more present, going low-tech can be a useful tool&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="0N1RwG"&gt;Because its only screen is tiny and grayscale, the battery lasts weeks at a time. If you’re mostly using this as an analog watch, those gains multiply. Seriously, I wore each for &lt;em&gt;weeks&lt;/em&gt;. Withings estimates you get about 30 days on a single charge, though I got around 21 to 25 due to heavier usage for testing. I took the ScanWatch 2 on a weeklong business trip, left the charger at home, and it was all good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2jyyL8"&gt;The only problem is you might &lt;em&gt;lose&lt;/em&gt; the charger because you rarely need it. When I moved, the ScanWatch 2’s charger disappeared into the same interdimensional portal that gobbles up all my left socks. You can buy replacements, but unlike other gadgets, &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/please-no-more-proprietary-smartwatch-chargers-1845562196"&gt;all smartwatch makers have their own proprietary chargers&lt;/a&gt;. That means replacements can get pricey ($24.95, in this case). And the two watches don’t even use the &lt;em&gt;same&lt;/em&gt; proprietary charger. I tried seeing if the Light’s charger would work, but it doesn’t. So if you and a family member both use Withings but have different watches, you won’t be able to share. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="hyxHfH"&gt;Big-picture health tracking&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="G1A5p9"&gt;The ScanWatch 2 tracks more data than the Light. In addition to a new temperature sensor, it measures blood oxygen levels and elevation. It also supports atrial fibrillation detection via EKG readings. The Light skips all of that in favor of shaving off $100 from the price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Tl2zDl"&gt;Otherwise, these are similar in function. Both support features like heart rate monitoring and high / low heart rate notifications. GPS tracking for the watches is done through your phone, and both are safe for swims with a 5ATM water resistance rating. And now, in the year 2024, Withings has added &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/23/24080926/withings-finally-adds-cycle-tracking-to-its-app"&gt;period tracking&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Withings ScanWatch Light on its side with the OLED lit up" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/9uWxmwGUq4Cl9hvxf6A-D3wWkno=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25282426/247014_Withings_ScanWatch_2_Light_AKrales_0012.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Light shaves $100 off the price by leaving out more advanced health features like EKGs and body temperature.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="Okd5wv"&gt;Accuracy — including GPS tracking — was decent, but you’re not getting Garmin levels of insight. On my walks and runs, the distances logged were in line with my Ultra 2. I didn’t notice any major discrepancies in my workout or resting heart rates with either watch. Sleep tracking was okay at giving an overall picture, but I found the Oura Ring more accurately reflected nightly interruptions like my cat Pablo waking me up for kibble at 4AM. If you stick to casual activities, these will get the job done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="70MBhn"&gt;Withings’ app is more tailored toward educated wellness than training, which again, is great if all you need are the basics. The app has a clean, minimalist design that’s easy to navigate and is chock-full of educational reading. I just hate the giant notification cards up top. They’re well-intentioned, often including tips on how to use the watch and reminders to hit your goals. But they pile up, aren’t easy to dismiss, and get old after a while. You have the option of subscribing to &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.withings.com%2Fus%2Fen%2Fwithings-plus&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F24085043%2Fwithings-scanwatch-2-scanwatch-light-review-wearables-smartwatch" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Withings Plus&lt;/a&gt;, but casual users don’t really need the extras it provides. As for data syncing, Withings works with Apple’s and Google’s health APIs and with Strava.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left"&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Withings ScanWatch 2 sensor array" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/loUpzSs2QQ2CZ4WxPEgn2QvWLLQ=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25282435/247014_Withings_ScanWatch_2_Light_AKrales_0073.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Withings ScanWatch 2 has more sensors.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Sensor array on ScanWatch Light" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/gX-kJlebV_xA2H1h145nwtuPS4Y=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25282428/247014_Withings_ScanWatch_2_Light_AKrales_0019.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Light has a last-gen heart rate sensor, but it doesn’t make a big difference for casual activity tracking.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="Nj1opa"&gt;Which should you get? It depends on whether you want &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the health features or the Light’s lower price. Personally, I’d save the extra $100. The temperature sensor doesn’t tie in with cycle tracking, and it’s mostly for monitoring your baseline at rest, while sleeping, and during workouts. It’s neat for data nerds, but it doesn’t take a genius to know you’re warmer during intense exercise. SpO2 tracking in consumer wearables also isn’t &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; useful yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="5DTXOu"&gt;Pleasantly retro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="5kwNog"&gt;It was refreshing to test a smartwatch that does less. Wearing the Ultra 2 side by side with the ScanWatch 2 or the ScanWatch Light, I got to see firsthand how many notifications I get every day and how peaceful it can be when you’re more intentional with what gets your attention.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Person wearing the Withings ScanWatch Light" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/T9UR3GNxYjybb-JwMril-nWzxwA=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25282439/247014_Withings_ScanWatch_2_Light_AKrales_0144.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;It’s nice to go low-tech sometimes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="3xTSAM"&gt;But Apple and Google aren’t likely to suddenly change course. Every year, the watches get a little bigger, a little smarter, and a little more packed with new sensors. For better or worse, smartwatches continue to do more, even if plenty of folks would like them to do less. Samsung is changing things up a little with the forthcoming Galaxy Ring — but even that seems to be a bid to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/26/24082729/samsung-has-big-ambitions-for-the-galaxy-ring"&gt;build out its ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;. (And maybe entice you to get a Samsung watch or phone while you’re at it.) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="kX2xUz"&gt;Withings has an opportunity here to keep things simple. There’s a gap in the stylish-but-uncomplicated tracker space. Garmin hybrids are nice, but Garmins are famous for data overload. Smart rings are &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/12/24034978/smart-ring-oura-ring-evie-ring-zepp-helio-ces-2024"&gt;having a moment&lt;/a&gt;, but they’re not ideal if you want &lt;em&gt;some&lt;/em&gt; notification capabilities. The &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23972335/smartwatches-2023-fitbit-google-integration"&gt;Googlefication of Fitbit&lt;/a&gt; is messy as hell. With &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23820207/fitness-bands-less-popular-wearables-smartwatches"&gt;fitness bands going the way of the dodo&lt;/a&gt;, you could do a lot worse than a Withings watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="s6mgZ6"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12272071"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="MGYBI9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lXooG6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24085043/withings-scanwatch-2-scanwatch-light-review-wearables-smartwatch"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24085043/withings-scanwatch-2-scanwatch-light-review-wearables-smartwatch</id>
    <author>
      <name>Victoria Song</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-08T14:11:31-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-08T14:11:31-05:00</updated>
    <title>How to use Alexa’s Drop In feature</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Echo show showing person on screen against an illustrated background." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/7SXkc06Y7G_WzyIihQuBA0w7lh0=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73192449/HT006_alexa_0005.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration by Samar Haddad / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="nWXiv8"&gt;Amazon’s Drop In feature has become a useful tool for contacting people in your household, finding out what your kids are up to (especially when they’re being &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; quiet), and checking in on elderly relatives. It allows you to literally “drop in” using an Alexa-capable device, either just via audio or with audio and video. But since you don’t want anyone dropping in on you unwanted, it’s a good idea to understand how to set it up and how to use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="GLcFAh"&gt;Set up your device for Drop In&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="r9wl2Y"&gt;In order to allow somebody to drop in on an Echo or Fire device (or any Alexa-capable device that allows you to make calls), first you have to enable the Drop In feature on that specific unit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="InBmZh"&gt;Open the Alexa app on your phone and select the &lt;strong&gt;Device&lt;/strong&gt; icon on the bottom of the screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="shTJMX"&gt;You’ll see a list of your devices. Select the one for which you want to enable or disable Drop In.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Eb5zaQ"&gt;Tap the &lt;strong&gt;gear icon&lt;/strong&gt; at the top right of the pop-up window, then scroll down to and select &lt;strong&gt;Communications&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="5ooUKj"&gt;Tap on &lt;strong&gt;Drop In&lt;/strong&gt;. Now you can turn it on for permitted contacts (which means whoever is in your contact list and who has permission to use Drop In), people in your household only, or nobody.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div id="z0XiHI"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12273275"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="iFmdME"&gt;Give someone permission to Drop In&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="XEeu9Q"&gt;If you want somebody outside your household to have the ability to drop in to your device, then you have to mark that contact as a permitted contact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="TFMqSg"&gt;In the Alexa app, go to &lt;strong&gt;More &amp;gt; Communicate&lt;/strong&gt; and tap on the icon resembling two people at the top right.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="HyPtrV"&gt;You’re now on your Contacts screen. If you want to allow an existing contact to drop in, just tap on the person’s name. You can also create a new contact by either selecting the &lt;strong&gt;Add New&lt;/strong&gt; button and then &lt;strong&gt;Add Contact&lt;/strong&gt;, or by tapping the &lt;strong&gt;three dots&lt;/strong&gt; in the upper right corner and then &lt;strong&gt;Add Contact&lt;/strong&gt;. (You can also, if you wish, import all your contacts associated with your device — just tap on &lt;strong&gt;Import&lt;/strong&gt; at the bottom of the screen.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="6tseh8"&gt;Whichever you choose — a new contact or an existing one — scroll down in the individual’s contact page. Under &lt;strong&gt;Permissions&lt;/strong&gt;, you’ll see &lt;strong&gt;Allow Drop In&lt;/strong&gt;, which you can toggle on or off.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="ZMroVs"&gt;Using Drop In&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="ZxdbcJ"&gt;Now that you’re all set up, it’s easy. Just use the command “Alexa, drop in...” with the name of the device you want to call. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="iv4wNf"&gt;To see what’s going on in another room that has an Echo Show named “Kid’s Den,” for example, just say something like “Alexa, drop in on Kid’s Den.” The device in that room will chime and its light, if any, will turn green. You’ll then be able to see and hear what’s going on in the other room through your own device — and if they’ve got a device with a camera, they’ll be able to see and hear what’s going on in yours. (Of course, if either party is using an audio-only device, that will limit the communication to, well, audio.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="QX4yGS"&gt;To stop the connection, say, “Alexa, hang up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Ovsk7b"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update March 8th, 2024, 3:06PM ET: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article has been updated to clarify that Drop In is only available on Echos, Fires, or other Alexa-equipped devices that are capable of making calls.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZoUy6K"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="IsFKpA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24093353/how-to-use-alexas-drop-in-feature"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24093353/how-to-use-alexas-drop-in-feature</id>
    <author>
      <name>Dan Rosenbaum</name>
      <name>Barbara Krasnoff</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-04T11:13:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-04T11:13:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Lenovo Legion Go review: the Swiss Army knife of handhelds</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;It’s not better than a Steam Deck or ROG Ally — but it’s different.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="1HpacE"&gt;Want a handheld gaming PC? I wouldn’t recommend the $700 Lenovo Legion Go over a Steam Deck. Windows 11 isn’t nearly as convenient and portable as Valve’s Steam OS for playing Windows games on the go. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/15/24074354/microsoft-admits-windows-is-a-weak-link-in-handheld-gaming-pcs-and-promises-to-improve"&gt;Even Microsoft knows that&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="iTheX8"&gt;But even if it’s not the best portable game console, it’s a nifty portable PC that can absolutely play games. For the right kind of Windows gadgeteer, the Lenovo Legion Go might narrowly be worth the cash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="zkO3zW"&gt;Though it’s roughly the same price as an Asus ROG Ally, Lenovo’s 8.8-inch portable has&lt;em&gt; all kinds&lt;/em&gt; of tricks up its sleeve. It’s a powerful Windows tablet with a pair of detachable Nintendo Switch-like wireless controllers and a full-width kickstand — the better to play at a table, stand up vertically for reading, or dock to a TV. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/31/23571821/nintendo-switch-joy-con-joystick-drift-button"&gt;Unlike Nintendo’s Joy-Cons&lt;/a&gt;, the Go’s controllers have drift-resistant Hall effect joysticks. Oh, and did I mention one of them can transform into a vertical mouse with the flick of a switch? &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A pistol grip on a controller held sideways to become a vertical mouse. " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/U0snBWEd65qfw3c0e7E3EZs303U=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313927/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_015.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;You hold the mouse like this (mousing surface not pictured).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mbk7Z3"&gt;It also has two USB-C ports, each with 40Gbps of USB4 bandwidth, so you can plug in a keyboard or SSD or even a Thunderbolt 3 external GPU without removing your charger lead. The Steam Deck and ROG Ally only have one USB-C socket each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="qlFCon"&gt;But the Legion Go’s biggest advantage is simple: it has a significantly bigger screen. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="0LEbny"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12267312"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="7tfTtN"&gt;I wouldn’t say it’s the &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; handheld screen: there is absolutely no beating the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23951655/steam-deck-oled-review"&gt;Steam Deck OLED&lt;/a&gt; when it comes to rich color, deep blacks, explosive HDR, and usability in a dim bedroom. Meanwhile, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23719210/asus-rog-ally-review"&gt;the ROG Ally’s&lt;/a&gt; variable refresh rate makes everything smoother; games often feel faster on the Ally even when the Legion Go is technically delivering more frames per second.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3EUC7V"&gt;But Lenovo’s glossy 8.8-inch, 2560 x 1600, 144Hz, 500-nit, and 97 percent DCI-P3 Gorilla Glass 5-covered screen makes a difference. It’s the one that’s big, crisp, and fast enough, it can double as a decent Windows tablet for web browsing, reading, and streaming video. Perhaps more importantly, I don’t feel I’m squinting as much when I play games. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/O10ZFrwZAh4sIXm2zGM86YB2JKI=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313928/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_002.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Windows at 8.8 inches.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="LERw3D"&gt;A year ago, I wrote &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23513517/steam-deck-long-term-test-valve#:~:text=It%E2%80%99s%20a%20shame%2C%20but%20I%E2%80%99ve%20also%20found%20I%20don%E2%80%99t%20miss%20those%20multiplayer%20shooters%20and%20slicers"&gt;how I didn’t actually mind&lt;/a&gt; the Steam Deck’s dearth of competitive multiplayer shooters like &lt;em&gt;Fortnite, Destiny 2, &lt;/em&gt;and &lt;em&gt;PUBG&lt;/em&gt; because I never knew what (or who) hit me on the Deck’s seven-inch, 60Hz screen. Neither the Deck OLED’s 7.3-inch, 90Hz panel nor the ROG Ally’s seven-inch, 120Hz screen fixed that for me. But I could see some people playing them on the 8.8-inch Legion Go — at least if they get used to the slightly awkward controls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Ht4a5W"&gt;I’m not a total fan of how the Legion Go feels in my hands. Because it weighs 1.88 pounds, half a pound more than the ROG Ally and Steam Deck OLED and a full pound more than a Nintendo Switch, I often feel like I need a tighter grip. But when I grip tightly, the not so rounded edges of Lenovo’s flat-faced handheld dig into my palms — and I find myself awkwardly squishing all the extra buttons Lenovo crammed onto the sides and back. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/nzXnMrhpM-Bd-hc7ZMFdyiy2YCg=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313937/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_008.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Big, beefy grips.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ITWdBT"&gt;It feels like Lenovo made a few too many compromises to give you a detachable mouse, a pair of Joy-Cons, a touchpad, and four back buttons simultaneously. The joysticks are fine, the slightly cramped face buttons are fine, the meaty triggers are even nice, but the touchpad is too small, the D-pad and top-firing speakers are meh, and the right controller always has two extra buttons under my middle finger, two more buttons under my index finger, and a button under my pinky that I hadn’t bargained for.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/fvWnfAEiVgDOv1NOdHKb1951vRg=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313936/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_004.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;This small recessed touchpad doesn’t begin to compare to the ones on the Deck. I never found it worth using versus joystick or touchscreen.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="iX0eoy"&gt;There’s a method to Lenovo’s madness: if you detach that controller and rotate it 90 degrees to the left, those buttons line up with your fingertips and thumb to give you a five-button vertical mouse, complete with a 1,800 DPI optical mouse sensor on the Teflon-coated bottom and a tiny scroll wheel around back. It’s neat, and I was pleased to see Lenovo has some pretty decent FPS presets mapped to each button, including the keys you’ll commonly use to crouch, jump, and reload. The mouse defaults to 800 DPI, though you can pick 500, 1,200, and 1,800 as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/vylmCp8oaXEHVJNJiqweDOO2blg=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313943/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_013.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The detachable controller rails don’t extend to the top or bottom of the handheld.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/0zo66ozMjKPrwfy_HIYz_HZilpE=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313941/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_010.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Flip this switch to turn on the mouse mode.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/peYRgHuIlODU6jtwUaLyP4FDRQs=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313945/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_012.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;That’s the left mouse button under my index finger.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/97mYOp8v0DEMKT_ffS7HJKvQ0EE=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313942/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_014.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s the big magnetic mouse skate.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="sr99an"&gt;But it’s not quite as simple as just popping off a Joy-Con and magically having a mouse. I have to yank each controller downward to release them; pop off the joystick cap so it’s not in the way; and slot the controller into a magnetically attached Teflon-bottomed base to give the mouse enough stability that I don’t lose tracking mid-game. Even then, I feel the remainder of the joystick’s protruding nub and its five copper pogo pins digging into my palms. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7a78VI"&gt;I figure the kind of power user who’ll want to navigate Windows on the go might appreciate this part of the gadget, but I’d have happily given it up for a pair of better front-firing speakers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="oPCpcs"&gt;Speaking of power, my Lenovo Legion Go is a bit faster than the competition! Anecdotally, it was the fastest to download games (I saw 750Mbps peak download speeds over Wi-Fi 6), the fastest to charge its 50Wh battery, and the fastest in most of my test bed games — as long as you’re willing to give its AMD Ryzen Z1 Extreme chip a little gas, that is. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="NLouNm"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12268824"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="IzYXhK"&gt;You should know that the chip in a Steam Deck is rather different from the chip in most other handheld gaming PCs. Where the Deck’s “Aerith” and “Sephiroth” were designed for a handheld power envelope of between four and 15 watts, the AMD Z1 Extreme is a shrunken-down laptop chip that targets nine to 30 watts — and as you can see in my chart, it didn’t begin to beat the Steam Deck until I fed it &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; than 15 watts of electricity. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hXqQW5"&gt;The flip side is that, unlike the Steam Deck, you can optionally sacrifice your battery life to the gods of performance, pushing a Legion Go or ROG Ally chip as high as 30 watts for a meaningful boost in speed, and I saw my Legion Go even outperform the ROG Ally when I began to give it that juice. It consistently pulled ahead in &lt;em&gt;Assassin’s Creed Valhalla&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Deus Ex: Mankind Divided&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Returnal&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Shadow of the Tomb Raider&lt;/em&gt; — sometimes by a few frames, sometimes by 10 or 20 percent. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/OO2gR1z0KMKuoPRRvEan7ZKEHC0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313946/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_006.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The fan doesn’t bug me too much, but certain frequencies can be noisy. I do get a teeny bit of whine at low speeds in basic tasks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="JS56Z3"&gt;But even when you’re trying to conserve the Legion Go’s 49.2Wh battery, you can only go so far. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="DKdgl9"&gt;I was able to manage four hours and 41 minutes of &lt;em&gt;Slay the Spire&lt;/em&gt;, one of the least demanding games in my library, but even &lt;em&gt;Dave the Diver&lt;/em&gt; gave me no more than two hours and 27 minutes at a stretch. I got an hour and a half of &lt;em&gt;Shadow of the Tomb Raider&lt;/em&gt;, two hours of &lt;em&gt;Nier: Automata&lt;/em&gt;, and two hours and 10 minutes of &lt;em&gt;Armored Core VI, &lt;/em&gt;all running at a mere 800p or lower resolution. When I tried &lt;em&gt;Ori and the Will of the Wisps&lt;/em&gt; at 1200p, I only got an hour and 39 minutes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="C2U6MX"&gt;For comparison, the Steam Deck OLED lasted an entire extra hour of &lt;em&gt;Nier: Automata&lt;/em&gt;, went 43 minutes longer than the Legion Go in &lt;em&gt;Shadow of the Tomb Raider, &lt;/em&gt;and gave me &lt;em&gt;nearly double&lt;/em&gt; the battery life in &lt;em&gt;Dave the Diver&lt;/em&gt; at four hours and 42 minutes. It tells me I should get nine hours of &lt;em&gt;Slay the Spire&lt;/em&gt;. I should note, my Deck OLED actually lasted seven fewer minutes in &lt;em&gt;Armored Core VI&lt;/em&gt;, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="t9Evoo"&gt;Does the Legion Go at least offer more battery life than the Asus ROG Ally due to its 20 percent larger battery pack? Well… I did get an extra 41 minutes of &lt;em&gt;Dave the Diver&lt;/em&gt; on the Legion Go, but battery life was almost identical in &lt;em&gt;Shadow of the Tomb Raider&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Dirt Rally&lt;/em&gt; and lasted just 16 minutes longer in &lt;em&gt;Armored Core&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/COnWkX3S2NhQ_t5RGy6zj14c9Ws=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313949/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_011.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The screen is quite glossy. It’s fine indoors. It also doesn’t go as dim as the competition: I measured 15 nits at 0 percent brightness, compared to two nits for the Deck and six nits for the Ally.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="NDuihK"&gt;With the Legion Go, the battery always feels like it’s visibly ticking down… and like other Windows handhelds, it ticks even faster when close to empty. You can take a Steam Deck to 3 percent battery before you need to seriously consider saving a game or plugging into the wall. With the Legion Go, even reaching 10 percent puts me in the danger zone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="vKI6om"&gt;I’m happy to say the Legion Go doesn’t lose a lot of battery while it’s completely shut down, but even that’s a bit of a backhanded compliment — because shutting down is the only way I’ve been able to reliably put it away. Many times, I’ll find it wakes itself up right after I put it to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="cGCwYT"&gt;Speaking of platform stability, you should know that the Legion Go’s Legion Space software is still a work in progress, like the Steam Deck and Asus ROG Ally before it, and it’s lagging far behind Valve and a ways behind Asus in terms of features. The ability to remap the gamepad is minimal at best, and you can’t even save mappings for each of your games with Lenovo’s software — you’ll need to rely on Steam or another third-party app. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2hr8Bp"&gt;As I write these words, Lenovo’s still trying to address some &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/LegionGo/comments/1ase28g/legion_go_update_02162024/"&gt;stuttering SD card readers&lt;/a&gt; (something I haven’t experienced myself) and add proper gyro support. The fan’s not loud, but it can be a little whiny, even in its lowest power mode. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/yj5wn_zImccexA9xyZL62Cp_fkU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313950/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_001.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lenovo’s Legion Space is pretty bare-bones, but it’s also relatively optional.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="JPvgDL"&gt;But I have to admit, it’s less buggy than the Asus was at launch, and Lenovo’s being pretty transparent with the community. Lenovo product manager &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/BenM_Legion/submitted/"&gt;Ben Myers drops into the official subreddit and Discord almost every week&lt;/a&gt; to talk about which issues and improvements the engineering team’s working on next, and it’s been good to see it improve! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZhsYyA"&gt;At launch, I might have dinged Lenovo for forcing me to reach down to the base of my thumb to hit Start and Select buttons or manually navigate to a website to download updates. Ditto how you had to connect a power supply before switching the screen’s refresh rate or tape over the power button’s bright LED to avoid light pollution while charging it in a dark bedroom. But Lenovo has places to tweak each of these in software now, plus adjustable fan curves, adjustable sensitivity and deadzones for the joysticks, user-adjustable presets for various power modes, and an FPS limiter. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="OFUxNF"&gt;The biggest thing I want, though, is a way to make all my games launch full-screen. That’s how they work on Steam Deck but not always on Windows, and I’ve run into awkward windowed games more often with the Legion Go than I did with the ROG Ally. In the official subreddit, some people seem to be forcing full-screen in their Steam launch options for individual games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/gH_3b_Y6fzcPS0II5DgxAk6qhaM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313954/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_019.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Legion Go gives me another kind of couch gaming, one that’d be awkward with controllers attached.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="k9jKbe"&gt;I’m not going to rehash &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23719210/asus-rog-ally-review#:~:text=You%20should%20understand"&gt;my whole “Windows is holding back gaming handhelds” argument&lt;/a&gt; here, as not much has changed since I reviewed the Ally. But the Legion Go’s 8.8-inch screen and detachable controllers do help. It’s easier to drag around windows and tap on icons with the larger touch targets that Lenovo’s screen gives me, and it doesn’t hurt that the Gorilla Glass 5-covered panel is smooth, easy to clean, and responsive to touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Z0dCi9"&gt;When I pop off the controllers, I can even reach the virtual keyboard keys without stretching my thumbs if I hold the tablet in portrait mode or invoke Microsoft’s split keyboard (which gives you left and right keyboard halves) in landscape. No more reaching over joysticks! I wouldn’t want to type a &lt;em&gt;Verge&lt;/em&gt; story on this thing, but I’m finding it’s a great size for browsing from the couch. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/mUSr3UkVXa7GH7m-pvgXYU8Umnc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313953/lenovo_legion_go_review_verge_sean_hollister_017.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Windows split keyboard.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="0iSe7i"&gt;I wouldn’t buy a Legion Go, as my Steam Deck suits me better, but I genuinely think Lenovo’s onto something with this form factor. It’s an intriguing cross between a Microsoft Surface and a Nintendo Switch but with gaming chops that surpass both. I wouldn’t be surprised if the next version comes with an optional Surface-like folding keyboard cover. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="RYP6am"&gt;Free advice: put &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/circuitbreaker/2020/6/30/21292182/thinkpad-trackpoint-mouse-nub-button-trackpad-challenges-design-user-input"&gt;a red ThinkPad TrackPoint nub&lt;/a&gt; in the middle of that keyboard if you really want computing nerds to go wild. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ybhiPD"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Sean Hollister / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wcwRxf"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Correction, March 4th: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;We wrote that the Legion Go’s price was $650, but the company’s &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/26/24051844/the-lenovo-legion-go-gets-its-first-price-cut-to-649"&gt;&lt;em&gt;long-lived price cut&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; apparently ended this weekend; it now costs $700 again.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24088011/lenovo-legion-go-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24088011/lenovo-legion-go-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Sean Hollister</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-01T08:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-01T08:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Volkswagen ID.7 review: a superior EV that happens to be a sedan </title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/K7EQSo11n4l9HU94mnieoZ9Gilg=/0x0:3000x2000/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73175267/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__15_.0.jpg" /&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;Volkswagen’s first non-SUV EV to hit American shores is shaping up to be a winner. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="4sq3dq"&gt;SUVs dominate the American landscape. They make up roughly half of all vehicles sold. So, when Volkswagen wanted to begin their post-Dieselgate EV assault on the US, it makes sense that they started with the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22302883/vw-id4-review-volkswagen-ev-specs-range-photos-video"&gt;ID.4&lt;/a&gt;. As SUVs go, it’s on the small side, but an SUV it is nevertheless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WLOky7"&gt;And then… nothing. For years. While European buyers also have the choice of the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2019/9/9/20857217/volkswagen-vw-id3-electric-price-specs-mile-range-frankfurt-motor-show-2019"&gt;ID.3 hatchback&lt;/a&gt; (which we’ll seemingly never get) and the new &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23735554/vw-id-buzz-review-ququq-camper-e-vanlife"&gt;ID Buzz&lt;/a&gt; van, we were stuck waiting. Now, not only is Volkswagen finally bringing us it’s reto-minded EV van, its &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/4/17/23685327/vw-id-7-ev-sedan-photos-specs-range"&gt;long-awaited ID.7 sedan&lt;/a&gt; is also hitting US dealers in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="cbhhfE"&gt;&lt;q&gt;Volkswagen has been quietly planting the seeds of anticipation around this long and luxurious ride&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="CRcJB9"&gt;Volkswagen has been quietly planting the seeds of anticipation around this long and luxurious ride. Though the car won’t arrive at dealers until later this year, I’ve been lucky to spend a few days wheeling around town in a pre-production, German-spec ID.7. After some frigid, winter-weather testing, I’m genuinely impressed with what Volkswagen looks set to deliver, even if this sedan doesn’t offer the most memorable of driving experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ho-T6ht-SzFEY5mTLkFXHDyWGHQ=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307753/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__2_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/82JaXbzBspsOtkXGoaf_RwTGt18=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307756/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__31_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/MDBzjkGJR8w0X5V4fytO4bw6GHU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307754/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__5_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/a7p1SLE-2KQG8jLVsAK-VxYamYM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307758/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__3_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="i7Olgn"&gt;What it is&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="Ug07bu"&gt;The 2024 ID.7 is a sedan of a type that is increasingly uncommon in the United States. Its wheelbase is five inches longer than the generously proportioned Arteon sedan, which is leaving the US market amid an industry-wide sedan decline. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gKLLcT"&gt;As sedans go, while the ID.7 isn’t the most exciting-looking car of the moment, it has a clean, sophisticated look that gives it more presence than the humble ID.4. But there are definitely some stylistic elements borrowed from the 4, most notable being the single sweeping line that forms the shape of the roof, running from the root of the windshield, up the leading A-pillar, above the doors, and back down to the trunk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Vuy4nA"&gt;The overall profile is much the same as the Arteon, but there’s significantly less chrome and fewer details on the ID.7. The biggest change is on the nose. Where the Arteon has a pronounced grille, the electric ID.7, with its reduced cooling needs, just has a small air inlet down low on a largely featureless nose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="oFBg6i"&gt;&lt;q&gt;As sedans go, the ID.7 isn’t the most exciting-looking car of the moment&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="tI7Z1O"&gt;The overall impression is of a sophisticated, stately car, especially in the subtle moonstone gray color you see here. However, I’m told the nose at least will look slightly more aggressive on the eventual US sedan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Y8lFfM"&gt;Now, before we get too far into this, I want to say that I’m calling this a sedan even though it doesn’t have a proper trunk. The ID.7 has a liftback hatch, like the Arteon, and it opens to reveal a healthy 18.7 cubic feet of cargo capacity. That’s about 25 percent more than a Camry, for reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="26dZpt"&gt;The rear seats fold down at the tug of a little lever on either side of the cargo compartment, more than doubling the cargo space to 56 cubic feet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Xep2xF"&gt;Those are solid numbers, but I have bad news for frunk fans: there’s no storage space up there. You can open the hood and gaze upon all the high-voltage equipment, but there isn’t even a token cubby for charging cables. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/AzHaKGm5XD1MkvNW3Lhi04ZyrfY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307783/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__8_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="svMdMl"&gt;I know that will upset some of you, but I’m okay with it. Though EVs don’t have engines, their inverters, chillers, heat pumps, and other components have to go somewhere. Stuffing them under the hood opens up the layout of the rest of the car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ICVTxR"&gt;And that layout is spacious. The rear seats offer enough legroom for a power forward. Even the tallest of folks can stretch out, gaze up through the panoramic sunroof, and luxuriate with the seat heaters pumping. Those rear seats are plenty comfortable, even offering a modicum of lateral support. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RHOZrl"&gt;But, beyond that, rear seat appointments are few: just a couple of USB-C ports to keep devices juiced and some deep door pockets for water bottles or &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23513517/steam-deck-long-term-test-valve"&gt;Steam Decks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="eFXlhe"&gt;There’s a lot of storage up front, too, including a floating center console with room below for moderate-sized purses or puppies. The forward section of the armrest has a sliding cover that exposes cupholders, a wireless charger, and another pair of USB-C ports. The aft portion has a deep, wide cavity, perfect for placing whatever you want to forget about. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="aL4lB4"&gt;Front seats are even more inviting than the rears. Deep, plush, and sueded with “Art Velours” and Artex microfibers, they are not only wonderful to occupy but, with the perforations and blue piping, quite pleasing to look at. Front seats are heated and cooled, and there’s even a massage function. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/7iUbph966diUBbCZTtf5Y2AIEdY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307759/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__6_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/1iTJwBIsKRBOIp1u9kMQ-V8gXf0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307765/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__7_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="CJJa5O"&gt;Curing cold feet with machine learning&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="rbUAnM"&gt;Though good, there’s nothing particularly novel about the ID.7’s seats. However, Volkswagen has paired them with some logic to create an in-car experience that’s remarkably sensitive to your needs. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="6EOdbV"&gt;Like so many cars today, the ID.7 has a pseudo-intelligent voice assistant that you can summon by name. VW calls this one Ida, but you can rename it to whatever you like. The voice assistant handles everything from navigation duties, like entering addresses or finding your closest Starbucks, to modifying in-car settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="MPFC64"&gt;The exciting stuff is what the voice assistant and the ID.7 ‘s HVAC system can do. You can say, “Hello, Ida, my feet are cold,” and it’ll direct warm air to flow down low in the cabin. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4pZsWK"&gt;We saw this first in the ID.4, but in the ID.7, Volkswagen takes it to another level thanks to the car’s digital vents. Say, “I’m cold,” and if you’re the only one in the car, the HVAC system will automatically center all the vents on you for maximum tootsie toasting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="u75rd1"&gt;There are some other neat tricks, like a seat mode called “Dry Boost” that combines heat and ventilation. It’s meant to be a quick fix for when things are getting a bit swampy — you know, down there. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="UfMCBW"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The overall impression is of a sophisticated, stately car&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="IrDFe1"&gt;What you can’t control via voice is handled by the 15-inch touchscreen that sits proud in the center of the dashboard. The ID.7 presents a bright, clean, customizable interface that you’ll probably just replace with Android Auto or Apple CarPlay anyway (both wireless). But when it comes to the basics of quickly accessing heating controls or changing car settings, it’s all quick and easy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="tH5lrc"&gt;Volkswagen’s software interface has come a long way since the laggy mess that launched in the ID.4 years ago. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="UtdsEj"&gt;More controls are found on the steering wheel, and unfortunately, they are of the capacitive touch type. Volkswagen deployed these on the ID.4 to generally negative reviews, and I was glad to see that the upcoming Golf has returned to actual buttons. Not so here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Y7Nf6Y"&gt;I also lament the lack of a physical volume knob, but I fear I’m increasingly in the minority with that complaint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/TsIHtk_J3e4ZHr8UmmucFrA2hyg=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307766/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__20_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/LbVf2b0VBtEnWgQ_LD5QhVZGDIU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307768/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__21_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/6JIq_PeJQ03gLJXq3qNvqv_uR5Q=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307770/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__25_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/XcRj2dyVs98g4SFVhyz35XDJQCY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307769/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__22_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="S1gFuc"&gt;Heads up, AR forward&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="PP2iOS"&gt;Despite its proportions, the ID.7 has a diminutive little gauge cluster behind the steering wheel, similar to the ID.4 or the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22265570/mustang-mach-e-review-electric-ford-ev-photos-video"&gt;Ford Mustang Mach-E&lt;/a&gt;. Still, it conveys everything you need about speed and vehicle status. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Hs0ejX"&gt;But there’s need and then there’s want, and you’ll want to check out the generously sized, augmented reality heads-up display. Projected onto the windscreen is another slender gauge cluster, which shows more information about active safety systems and state of charge. It’s a bit duplicative of the gauge cluster, making me wonder whether the latter is necessary, but the bigger tricks happen higher on the glass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NhDPei"&gt;Wander too far out of the lane, and the HUD paints a flashing orange line on the road as a sort of visual cue to stop meandering and get your ass back in line. It’ll also help with navigation cues and other active safety warnings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="rQLj8T"&gt;&lt;q&gt;You’ll want to check out the generously sized, augmented reality heads-up display&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="BlB2ja"&gt;It’s not quite as advanced as the HUD found in the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/11/22375877/mercedes-benz-eqs-ev-s-class-specs-hands-on"&gt;Mercedes-Benz EQS&lt;/a&gt; sedan, but that thing costs about twice as much as this probably will, so I’ll cut it some slack. I do love seeing advanced tech coming down to more attainable cars like this. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="UQxZTy"&gt;Sadly, I could not sample the navigation functionality. This German car came to me without local map data, which meant the car’s navigation screen was nothing more than a big, white box. It had no roads, no points of interest, not even Starbucks. So, I was unable to test out the augmented reality nav in the ID.7. But, having used these systems on other cars in the past, I can tell you that having a giant arrow floating in space, literally pointing the way home, makes it a lot harder to miss your turn. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="BAyYdg"&gt;And, if that’s not enough, the ID.7 continues the row of LEDs along the windshield that are also featured on the ID.4. They’ll flash and blink to let you know of upcoming turns and wayward pedestrians. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/1GI80fC3NV83QvwXuT1fygM_Y0o=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307775/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__10_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="7kzo91"&gt;Relax and cruise&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="gKgqfq"&gt;The Volkswagen ID.7 is a luxurious car in many ways, and that’s also how I’d classify the driving dynamic. Or, I should say, the lack of dynamic. The model I drove was the rear-wheel drive trim that will match the first cars coming to the US later this year, with 282 horsepower and 402 pound-feet of torque. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wbXY3E"&gt;Those would be acceptable numbers in most sedans, but remember, this is a long EV with a big battery pack. It is a heavy machine, and that combination results in solid but hardly neck-snapping acceleration. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="OmuZjL"&gt;If you’re the sort who needs more power, a dual-motor all-wheel drive flavor is said to be coming in time. But, honestly, I didn’t need or want the ID.7 to be a rocket ship. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="65y9W3"&gt;Plenty of other EVs are fighting for kidney-bursting acceleration honors. I’d rather see more manufacturers focus on ride quality and comfort. The ID.7 excels in that department. It is floaty over bumps, taking a few moments to settle after cruising over railroad tracks, but it nonchalantly absorbs the incessant frost heaves and asphalt cracks that criss-cross upstate NY roads this time of year. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="lVKu6V"&gt;&lt;q&gt;I didn’t need or want the ID.7 to be a rocket ship&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="LWzTHj"&gt;Sure, the steering is sluggish, the brake pedal long and soft, and the throttle relaxed even in sport mode, but none of that bothered me. I was too busy enjoying the ride — and the excellent Harman Kardon sound system. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="cZ0N68"&gt;I know, you’re all wondering about the range. I can tell you that I averaged 2.8 miles per kilowatt-hour, which equates to a theoretical 230 miles from the 82kWh battery pack we’ll get in the U.S. However, I did most of my testing during a winter storm, with temperatures below freezing. There were also quite a few acceleration tests along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rkpOuZ"&gt;In other words, the worst-case scenario. Volkswagen says to expect 386 miles on the European WLTP test. We can’t say for sure without a completed EPA test, but 320 miles should be a reasonable estimate for the US model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gU4XYX"&gt;We also can’t say pricing for sure yet, and that’s a shame because it’s hard to recommend a product if you don’t know how much it’ll cost. Looking at the ID.4 and where the European ID.7 falls, I’d guess at a low-to-mid $50,000 price. For a long, comfortable sedan with luxury aspirations plus the practicality of a hatchback, that would make the ID.7 a proper value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NnQoFN"&gt;In terms of the most popular EVs on the road, that would price the ID.7 closer to the Tesla Model 3 than the Model S, despite it offering practicality and comfort in excess of the latter. It won’t offer the speed, of course, and will surely come up short on range, but in my eye, once you’re over 300 miles on a charge, the difference is largely academic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/9HaaIzHfZOPtCLkLp_K_I1OqL0c=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25307776/2025_VW_ID7_First_Drive__11_.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="a0w8eG"&gt;The question, though, is whether there’s truly a market for this thing here. While the ID.4 hasn’t exactly taken the world by storm, it has been gaining momentum for Volkswagen in the US market. Sales of the EV were &lt;a href="https://media.vw.com/en-us/releases/1776"&gt;up more than 80 percent last year&lt;/a&gt;, making up more than 10 percent of VW’s overall sales here. VW had a strong year in general, with sales up 40 percent last quarter and 10 percent for the full year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="f53QIV"&gt;So there is increasing interest in VW’s EVs, but sedans aren’t exactly in hot demand right now. The Arteon was never a strong seller, and it’s hard to imagine the ID.7 finding blow-out success following so closely in its footsteps.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="FRK896"&gt;The ID.7 is damn good, and it makes for a very compelling alternative to the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23702900/hyundai-ioniq-6-review-ev-specs-photos-price"&gt;Hyundai Ioniq 6&lt;/a&gt; on the low end or a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/1/27/22252832/tesla-model-s-redesign-plaid-mile-range-interior-refresh"&gt;Tesla Model S&lt;/a&gt; on the higher end. If the price is right, I’ll take one of these over either. But I have a sinking feeling that once the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23735554/vw-id-buzz-review-ququq-camper-e-vanlife"&gt;ID.Buzz finally drops&lt;/a&gt;, that’s the only VW anyone’s going to be talking about. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="KTYGkg"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Tim Stevens / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/1/24084671/volkswagen-id7-review-ev-sedan-specs-price-photos"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/1/24084671/volkswagen-id7-review-ev-sedan-specs-price-photos</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tim Stevens</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-29T18:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-29T18:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Sennheiser Momentum True Wireless 4 review: redemption never sounded so good</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;The company has always delivered on audio quality, but after stumbling with some bugs and hardware issues on the Momentum True Wireless 3 earbuds, Sennheiser is focusing on the little things — and it shows.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="RaC3Y2"&gt;It only took a few days with Sennheiser’s new Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds for it to become plainly obvious that they’re a class above &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23059336/sennheiser-momentum-true-wireless-3-earbuds-review"&gt;the company’s previous model&lt;/a&gt; in nearly every way. The design and overall sound signature haven’t undergone major changes. But through a number of under-the-hood tweaks and other more subtle improvements, Sennheiser has taken aim at the connection issues, software bugs, and quality control concerns that &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sennheiser/comments/140jzrn/buyer_beware_momentum_true_wireless_3/"&gt;hindered the potential&lt;/a&gt; of its third-gen buds — to the point where some buyers had said, “Never again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="nVBnkY"&gt;At $299.95, they’re now $50 pricier, but these remain among the best-sounding wireless earbuds you’ll find. And they’re packed with forward-looking features that will keep them relevant for several years to come. Intriguingly, the Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds also buck a major trend in their category by shipping without any kind of spatial audio tricks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="oJtvPb"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12266002"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zH7eSa"&gt;This is Sennheiser, so let’s just get right to the sound. If you’re coming from the Momentum True Wireless 3, the listening experience of these earbuds will be familiar. The detail, warmth, and impressive soundstage that Sennheiser fans have come to expect are all accounted for. In “I Remember Everything” by Zach Bryan and Kacey Musgraves, the acoustic guitar has just the right amount of crunch and timbre, and the MTW4 bring out the strengths in each of their voices. Jumping over to the 2023 remix of the Beatles’ red album, you’ll find plenty of rumble in the bass during tracks like “I Saw Her Standing There” — without any treble harshness on the earliest recordings. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="OYkd6O"&gt;In a word, the sound profile is &lt;em&gt;precise, &lt;/em&gt;and you’ll rarely ever be left wanting for more (or less) of anything. I favor these over Sony’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23803374/sony-wf-1000xm5-earbuds-review"&gt;WF-1000XM5&lt;/a&gt;, Apple’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23365910/apple-airpods-pro-second-generation-review"&gt;AirPods Pro&lt;/a&gt;, and Samsung’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23312192/samsung-galaxy-buds-2-pro-review"&gt;Galaxy Buds 2 Pro&lt;/a&gt;. They’re neck and neck with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23820445/technics-eah-az80-earbuds-review"&gt;Technics’ AZ80 earbuds&lt;/a&gt;, another favorite of mine. Sennheiser gives you full control over the EQ, and a “sound personalization” feature can create a custom audio profile that’s tuned to your unique hearing characteristics. I largely kept the earbuds in their default mode and wasn’t disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="kviZk8"&gt;Sennheiser’s adaptive noise cancellation analyzes your environment to apply the right level of ANC on the fly, and while it can’t match up with class leader Bose, it was more than enough to help me tune out a crowded subway car and enjoy my music. Similarly, the company’s transparency mode isn’t at the level of Apple, but it sounds pleasingly natural and serves its purpose just fine. Through the company’s mobile app, you can also set location-specific “zone” preferences, so if you want regular ANC at your favorite coffee shop but need some transparency mixed in at the office, you can do that. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds in copper." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3bt47eP4_VRdKCAHOwTvlPfDWyQ=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311363/DSC_0469_Enhanced_NR.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Copper joins the previous gray / black and silver / white color choices.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ld6ZuS"&gt;Aside from a new copper color option, the Momentum True Wireless 4 look identical to the Momentum True Wireless 3 earbuds. You now get a fourth (extra-small) set of silicone ear tips, and Sennheiser still includes three sets of stabilizer arcs in the box for an extra-secure fit. But there are much bigger changes within the buds themselves, including a redesigned antenna and a fully overhauled wireless / Bluetooth technology stack that, in my experience, has made them work reliably and &lt;em&gt;consistently&lt;/em&gt;. They’re fast to connect to my phone, and the frustrations I had with the Sennheiser Smart Control app on iOS and Android occasionally failing to recognize the earbuds are completely gone. Sennheiser also intelligently prioritizes whichever bud is closest to your phone to maintain the connection between the two, meaning there’s a much lower chance of brief audio dropouts. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A closeup photo of Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds in a person’s ear." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/9OGzPrA1n-eNGOOs6k5tah_iJnU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311763/IMG_0082.JPG"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sennheiser includes four sizes of ear tips and three sets of silicone arcs.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="5HAKgv"&gt;The company has made a substantial effort to futureproof these $300 buds for the next several years: they’re Bluetooth 5.4-compliant, and a firmware update due in early spring will enable LE Audio and Auracast. More relevant for those hell-bent on the best audio quality is that the MTW4 feature Qualcomm’s Snapdragon Sound technology. That’ll prove beneficial if you own a recent flagship-level Android phone with a Qualcomm processor inside because you’ll be able to stream what Sennheiser claims is “flawless bit-by-bit” lossless audio from your phone to the earbuds — as long as your chosen music service offers it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="Hk8nFI"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12266169"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="hLZhHU"&gt;Even outside of that, Sennheiser supports a litany of Bluetooth codecs, including SBC, AAC, AptX, AptX Adaptive, and LC3. There’s a dedicated settings screen where you can select what level of quality you want, with the tradeoffs being connection stability and faster battery consumption the higher you go. And gamers can activate a low-latency setting that makes the MTW4 a good match for a Nintendo Switch or Steam Deck in addition to the usual mobile gaming use cases.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A screenshot of audio quality settings in Sennheiser’s Smart Control app." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/VT8gLF1k_P7UnJ9rWW_nobnXsGM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311499/Screenshot_20240227_153051.png"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;These options are present even in the iOS Smart Control app — despite iPhones being unable to take advantage of them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="OTBhdx"&gt;Practically none of this higher-fidelity listening applies to iPhone users since Apple continues to stick with its long-preferred AAC codec. But these earbuds sound fantastic no matter which device you link them with. I’ve come to believe that an earbud’s tuning and the drivers inside can be more important than supporting a grab bag of codecs, and Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 are a prime example of that. They also conveniently include multipoint support, so you can pair them with two devices at the same time if you need to multitask between your phone and laptop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds in copper." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/hq2ZqB_0C9F1o8GRSmLEpPgbbF4=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311366/DSC_0454_2.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Android users will get the best audio fidelity from the MTW4.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="M0X0wF"&gt;Just as interesting are the features that have purposefully been left out: these earbuds place zero emphasis on spatial audio. They don’t include any head-tracking gimmicks. It seems like Sennheiser knows its audience well enough to have decided that it can safely skip the spatial audio / Atmos trend for another generation without disappointing too many people, and I’d wager that the company is right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="sp0ZEI"&gt;Battery life has been extended and can now reach up to seven hours of continuous playback with noise cancellation on or 7.5 hours with it off. Add in the case — yes, it supports wireless charging — and you get around 30 hours of overall listening time. If you want to ensure the longevity of your earbuds, I’d recommend a new battery protection setting that only lets them charge up to 80 percent. We’ve seen similar measures applied to smartphones, but considering that it’s nigh impossible to replace the batteries in wireless earbuds, I’m glad Sennheiser is at least trying to stretch out their overall lifespan. They’re also built to be tougher, now with an IP54 rating that lends them some protection from dust on top of the continued water resistance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds in copper." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/MSb9dtyB8lXIiZF0P0APxfpBjow=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311365/DSC_0463.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds (above) and the Technics AZ80 earbuds (below).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="loZscl"&gt;Sennheiser has also put work into making these earbuds better for voice calls. They include a six-microphone array that runs through the company’s latest AI voice processing algorithms to help separate your voice from any background clatter. My instinct is always to grab a wired set of buds (or just use the earpiece) for any calls that really matter, but these definitely outperform the company’s past efforts when it comes to voice isolation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gFmrHG"&gt;It’s too early to definitively say that Sennheiser got it right this time, but that’s what my gut’s been telling me while testing the Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds. Their sound remains exceptional, the glitches and defects from previous models are nowhere to be seen, and they’re stuffed full of the very latest Bluetooth capabilities you’ll find in 2024. I’ll be keeping an eye on &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sennheiser/"&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt; and other social channels to make sure nothing goes awry hardware-wise. But if you were left with a bad taste in your mouth by the MTW3, this feels like a redemption arc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="yNAD13"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12266010"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="uiTUkn"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24086715/sennheiser-momentum-true-wireless-4-earbuds-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24086715/sennheiser-momentum-true-wireless-4-earbuds-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Chris Welch</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-26T09:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-26T09:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>AMD Radeon RX 7900 GRE review: $549 competition for Nvidia </title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;AMD’s latest GPU targets Nvidia’s RTX 4070.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="3uclbt"&gt;AMD is launching its Radeon RX 7900 GRE worldwide today in a bid to compete with Nvidia’s RTX 4070. This new-ish GPU is priced at the same $549 as the RTX 4070, but it offers better performance and 16GB of VRAM instead of just 12GB. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="knJDeJ"&gt;The RX 700 GRE was previously limited to the Chinese market, designed primarily with 1440p gaming in mind. Now, AMD is opening it up worldwide in a bid to offer some solid competition to the RTX 4070. The RX 7900 GRE is around 11 percent faster than the RTX 4070 at 1440p, making it yet another option to pair with the latest high-speed 1440p OLED monitors currently hitting shelves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="OSJ4CT"&gt;The $549 RX 7900 GRE arrives just weeks after Nvidia cut the pricing of the RTX 4070 after it launched the $599 RTX 4070 Super. AMD’s RX 7900 GRE even trades blows in some games with Nvidia’s RTX 4070 Super, so this card will undoubtedly put price pressure on Nvidia’s $549 RTX 4070 and even AMD’s own $499 RX 7800 XT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="XuVLkJ"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12262605"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="rLR04r"&gt;Hardware&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="n3Ybjg"&gt;AMD is leaning on its board partner designs for the RX 7900 GRE. I’ve been testing XFX’s model, which is based on AMD’s reference design. The card has a triple-fan layout that’s incredibly long at 13.2 inches. Yes, that’s longer than an RTX 4090, so definitely check to make sure your case can squeeze it in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HKCUMe"&gt;The total board power is 260 watts for the Radeon RX 7900 GRE, 60 watts more than the total board power of Nvidia’s RTX 4070. AMD recommends a 700-watt power supply for this card, which is again more than the 650-watt recommendation for both the RTX 4070 and 4070 Super.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/bHhrnXcfyBv15L_JbtWb1FDovjQ=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25305197/twarren_rx7900gre2.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The RX 7900 GRE has three DisplayPorts and a single HDMI.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="Z0aYgp"&gt;The RX 7900 GRE comes with three DisplayPort 2.1 outputs and a single HDMI 2.1 port at the rear. While this GPU won’t output the types of high frame rates at 4K that you’ll need to take advantage of DisplayPort 2.1 at 4K (up to 480Hz) with HDR enabled, it’s still good to see that AMD continues to futureproof its Radeon cards. Nvidia only offers DisplayPort 1.4 on its 40-series GPUs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="SjrvjL"&gt;AMD is also sticking with the tried-and-true eight-pin connectors here. You don’t have to worry about the latest 12VHPWR power connector or clunky adapters, as there are two eight-pin connectors on the RX 7900 GRE. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="VhhHNJ"&gt;One of the best hardware aspects of AMD’s RX 7900 GRE is the 16GB of VRAM. It operates at 18Gbps, slower than the 21Gbps on both the RTX 4070 and RTX 4070 Super. But AMD has opted for a 256-bit memory bus on the RX 7900 GRE, so the memory bandwidth is 576GB/s instead of the 504GB/s found on the RTX 4070 / 4070 Super. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="7J9pSi"&gt;1440p benchmarks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="bN6MYw"&gt;For 1440p testing, I paired the RX 7900 GRE with AMD’s latest Ryzen 7 7800X3D processor and Samsung’s 32-inch G7 monitor. This monitor can support up to 240Hz, so it’s ideal for high refresh rate 1440p gaming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="fmWwU2"&gt;I put the RX 7900 GRE head-to-head with the RTX 4070 and a collection of other Radeon and GeForce cards. I’ve tested a variety of games at high or ultra settings, and the RX 7900 GRE was able to reach 100fps or beyond in most — making this an ideal 1440p GPU.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HSMklG"&gt;The RX 7900 GRE is around 11 percent faster than Nvidia’s RTX 4070 at 1440p. It only loses out in ray-tracing performance in &lt;em&gt;Watch Dogs: Legion&lt;/em&gt; because there isn’t support for AMD’s FSR upscaling tech in this particular title. Otherwise, the 7900 GRE comfortably beats Nvidia’s RTX 4070.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="JHQKyX"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12262600"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="pRqN8M"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12224381"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="DZrJ2I"&gt;Even in &lt;em&gt;Metro Exodus Enhanced&lt;/em&gt;, running at both ultra and extreme settings, the RX 7900 GRE easily beats out the RTX 4070 and even comes close to matching the RTX 4070 Super. &lt;em&gt;Metro Exodus Enhanced&lt;/em&gt; is demanding even by modern standards, particularly at these high settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="cvyVNq"&gt;Overall, though, the RX 7900 GRE loses to the RTX 4070 Super in most titles, but it’s a really close gap considering you’re paying $50 extra for Nvidia’s latest GPU. That extra $50 is probably worth it if you’re interested in using DLSS or any ray-traced games, as AMD’s latest FSR 3 tech is still only supported in a handful of games and DLSS is still far better than FSR 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/gA5SsMCrdHdRj5Oh9HLm53tJFFE=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25305196/twarren_rx7900gre1.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;AMD has stuck with the regular eight-pin power connectors.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="OYPa8o"&gt;4K benchmarks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="vkuo3e"&gt;I paired the RX 7900 GRE with Acer’s 31.5-inch Nitro XV2 monitor that’s capable of refresh rates up to 144Hz. The RX 7900 GRE isn’t a card I’d recommend for 4K gaming, but with the 16GB of VRAM on board, it can offer some entry-level 4K support if you’re willing to drop the settings down a notch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rVKRNQ"&gt;On average, the RX 7900 GRE is 14 percent faster than Nvidia’s RTX 4070 at 4K. That’s a comfortable gap, and it makes it more tempting for 4K, especially if you’ve already got a 1440p monitor and you’re thinking of going 4K soon. Nvidia’s RTX 4070 Super certainly closes the gap on the RX 7900 GRE at 4K, though, winning in most tests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="XlkEmS"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12262602"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="M4UJrz"&gt;AMD has FSR 3 to improve the 4K frame rates, by using a combination of temporal upscaling and frame generation. While there aren’t enough games that support this yet, AMD has also launched Fluid Motion Frames, which brings frame generation to all DirectX 11 and 12 games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TblghH"&gt;We haven’t had enough time to incorporate Fluid Motion Frames (AFMF) testing into our full benchmarks for the RX 7900 GRE, but some early testing in &lt;em&gt;Forza Horizon 5&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Assassin's Creed Mirage&lt;/em&gt; showed great promise for improved frame rates at both 1440p and 4K. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="TdG6OC"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12262603"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="gxDAKz"&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="GgsfXs"&gt;The RX 7900 GRE is a great 1440p card for $549. It comfortably beats Nvidia’s RTX 4070 at the same price and even comes close to the $599 RTX 4070 Super. The 16GB of VRAM even gives you room for 4K gaming at lower settings or just the ease of mind that you’re not going to suffer any issues if you crank up the graphics settings, even at 1440p.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="SP0bmo"&gt;We’ve already seen games like &lt;em&gt;Diablo IV&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;The Last of Us Part I&lt;/em&gt; push past 12GB of VRAM usage at 1440p, so there are bound to be more this year and beyond. That makes 16GB of VRAM at this performance target much more essential unless you’re happy to drop the graphics settings slightly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EkZKYF"&gt;The RX 7900 GRE does show that Nvidia’s RTX 4070 and even AMD’s Radeon RX 7800 XT are a little overpriced. AMD is launching the RX 7900 GRE worldwide in the same way it does with many of its other cards, with cards available from Acer, ASRock, Asus, Gigabyte, PowerColor, Sapphire, and XFX. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="WHScHh"&gt;If the $549 pricing holds, then it’s bound to put pressure on Nvidia to respond because the combination of Fluid Motion Frames and the RX 7900 GRE’s 1440p performance is a very tempting combo for anyone looking to upgrade to 1440p.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="qXcoe1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Tom Warren / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24083386/amd-radeon-rx-7900-gre-review-benchmarks-price"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24083386/amd-radeon-rx-7900-gre-review-benchmarks-price</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
