<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Headphone Reviews</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-02-29T18:00:00-05:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/headphone-review/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/headphone-review" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-29T18:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-29T18:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Sennheiser Momentum True Wireless 4 review: redemption never sounded so good</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;The company has always delivered on audio quality, but after stumbling with some bugs and hardware issues on the Momentum True Wireless 3 earbuds, Sennheiser is focusing on the little things — and it shows.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="RaC3Y2"&gt;It only took a few days with Sennheiser’s new Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds for it to become plainly obvious that they’re a class above &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23059336/sennheiser-momentum-true-wireless-3-earbuds-review"&gt;the company’s previous model&lt;/a&gt; in nearly every way. The design and overall sound signature haven’t undergone major changes. But through a number of under-the-hood tweaks and other more subtle improvements, Sennheiser has taken aim at the connection issues, software bugs, and quality control concerns that &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sennheiser/comments/140jzrn/buyer_beware_momentum_true_wireless_3/"&gt;hindered the potential&lt;/a&gt; of its third-gen buds — to the point where some buyers had said, “Never again.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="nVBnkY"&gt;At $299.95, they’re now $50 pricier, but these remain among the best-sounding wireless earbuds you’ll find. And they’re packed with forward-looking features that will keep them relevant for several years to come. Intriguingly, the Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds also buck a major trend in their category by shipping without any kind of spatial audio tricks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="oJtvPb"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12266002"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zH7eSa"&gt;This is Sennheiser, so let’s just get right to the sound. If you’re coming from the Momentum True Wireless 3, the listening experience of these earbuds will be familiar. The detail, warmth, and impressive soundstage that Sennheiser fans have come to expect are all accounted for. In “I Remember Everything” by Zach Bryan and Kacey Musgraves, the acoustic guitar has just the right amount of crunch and timbre, and the MTW4 bring out the strengths in each of their voices. Jumping over to the 2023 remix of the Beatles’ red album, you’ll find plenty of rumble in the bass during tracks like “I Saw Her Standing There” — without any treble harshness on the earliest recordings. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="OYkd6O"&gt;In a word, the sound profile is &lt;em&gt;precise, &lt;/em&gt;and you’ll rarely ever be left wanting for more (or less) of anything. I favor these over Sony’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23803374/sony-wf-1000xm5-earbuds-review"&gt;WF-1000XM5&lt;/a&gt;, Apple’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23365910/apple-airpods-pro-second-generation-review"&gt;AirPods Pro&lt;/a&gt;, and Samsung’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23312192/samsung-galaxy-buds-2-pro-review"&gt;Galaxy Buds 2 Pro&lt;/a&gt;. They’re neck and neck with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23820445/technics-eah-az80-earbuds-review"&gt;Technics’ AZ80 earbuds&lt;/a&gt;, another favorite of mine. Sennheiser gives you full control over the EQ, and a “sound personalization” feature can create a custom audio profile that’s tuned to your unique hearing characteristics. I largely kept the earbuds in their default mode and wasn’t disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="kviZk8"&gt;Sennheiser’s adaptive noise cancellation analyzes your environment to apply the right level of ANC on the fly, and while it can’t match up with class leader Bose, it was more than enough to help me tune out a crowded subway car and enjoy my music. Similarly, the company’s transparency mode isn’t at the level of Apple, but it sounds pleasingly natural and serves its purpose just fine. Through the company’s mobile app, you can also set location-specific “zone” preferences, so if you want regular ANC at your favorite coffee shop but need some transparency mixed in at the office, you can do that. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds in copper." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3bt47eP4_VRdKCAHOwTvlPfDWyQ=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311363/DSC_0469_Enhanced_NR.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Copper joins the previous gray / black and silver / white color choices.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ld6ZuS"&gt;Aside from a new copper color option, the Momentum True Wireless 4 look identical to the Momentum True Wireless 3 earbuds. You now get a fourth (extra-small) set of silicone ear tips, and Sennheiser still includes three sets of stabilizer arcs in the box for an extra-secure fit. But there are much bigger changes within the buds themselves, including a redesigned antenna and a fully overhauled wireless / Bluetooth technology stack that, in my experience, has made them work reliably and &lt;em&gt;consistently&lt;/em&gt;. They’re fast to connect to my phone, and the frustrations I had with the Sennheiser Smart Control app on iOS and Android occasionally failing to recognize the earbuds are completely gone. Sennheiser also intelligently prioritizes whichever bud is closest to your phone to maintain the connection between the two, meaning there’s a much lower chance of brief audio dropouts. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A closeup photo of Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds in a person’s ear." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/9OGzPrA1n-eNGOOs6k5tah_iJnU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311763/IMG_0082.JPG"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sennheiser includes four sizes of ear tips and three sets of silicone arcs.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="5HAKgv"&gt;The company has made a substantial effort to futureproof these $300 buds for the next several years: they’re Bluetooth 5.4-compliant, and a firmware update due in early spring will enable LE Audio and Auracast. More relevant for those hell-bent on the best audio quality is that the MTW4 feature Qualcomm’s Snapdragon Sound technology. That’ll prove beneficial if you own a recent flagship-level Android phone with a Qualcomm processor inside because you’ll be able to stream what Sennheiser claims is “flawless bit-by-bit” lossless audio from your phone to the earbuds — as long as your chosen music service offers it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="Hk8nFI"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12266169"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="hLZhHU"&gt;Even outside of that, Sennheiser supports a litany of Bluetooth codecs, including SBC, AAC, AptX, AptX Adaptive, and LC3. There’s a dedicated settings screen where you can select what level of quality you want, with the tradeoffs being connection stability and faster battery consumption the higher you go. And gamers can activate a low-latency setting that makes the MTW4 a good match for a Nintendo Switch or Steam Deck in addition to the usual mobile gaming use cases.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A screenshot of audio quality settings in Sennheiser’s Smart Control app." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/VT8gLF1k_P7UnJ9rWW_nobnXsGM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311499/Screenshot_20240227_153051.png"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;These options are present even in the iOS Smart Control app — despite iPhones being unable to take advantage of them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="OTBhdx"&gt;Practically none of this higher-fidelity listening applies to iPhone users since Apple continues to stick with its long-preferred AAC codec. But these earbuds sound fantastic no matter which device you link them with. I’ve come to believe that an earbud’s tuning and the drivers inside can be more important than supporting a grab bag of codecs, and Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 are a prime example of that. They also conveniently include multipoint support, so you can pair them with two devices at the same time if you need to multitask between your phone and laptop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds in copper." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/hq2ZqB_0C9F1o8GRSmLEpPgbbF4=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311366/DSC_0454_2.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Android users will get the best audio fidelity from the MTW4.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="M0X0wF"&gt;Just as interesting are the features that have purposefully been left out: these earbuds place zero emphasis on spatial audio. They don’t include any head-tracking gimmicks. It seems like Sennheiser knows its audience well enough to have decided that it can safely skip the spatial audio / Atmos trend for another generation without disappointing too many people, and I’d wager that the company is right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="sp0ZEI"&gt;Battery life has been extended and can now reach up to seven hours of continuous playback with noise cancellation on or 7.5 hours with it off. Add in the case — yes, it supports wireless charging — and you get around 30 hours of overall listening time. If you want to ensure the longevity of your earbuds, I’d recommend a new battery protection setting that only lets them charge up to 80 percent. We’ve seen similar measures applied to smartphones, but considering that it’s nigh impossible to replace the batteries in wireless earbuds, I’m glad Sennheiser is at least trying to stretch out their overall lifespan. They’re also built to be tougher, now with an IP54 rating that lends them some protection from dust on top of the continued water resistance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds in copper." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/MSb9dtyB8lXIiZF0P0APxfpBjow=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25311365/DSC_0463.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds (above) and the Technics AZ80 earbuds (below).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="loZscl"&gt;Sennheiser has also put work into making these earbuds better for voice calls. They include a six-microphone array that runs through the company’s latest AI voice processing algorithms to help separate your voice from any background clatter. My instinct is always to grab a wired set of buds (or just use the earpiece) for any calls that really matter, but these definitely outperform the company’s past efforts when it comes to voice isolation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gFmrHG"&gt;It’s too early to definitively say that Sennheiser got it right this time, but that’s what my gut’s been telling me while testing the Momentum True Wireless 4 earbuds. Their sound remains exceptional, the glitches and defects from previous models are nowhere to be seen, and they’re stuffed full of the very latest Bluetooth capabilities you’ll find in 2024. I’ll be keeping an eye on &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sennheiser/"&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt; and other social channels to make sure nothing goes awry hardware-wise. But if you were left with a bad taste in your mouth by the MTW3, this feels like a redemption arc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="yNAD13"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12266010"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="uiTUkn"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24086715/sennheiser-momentum-true-wireless-4-earbuds-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24086715/sennheiser-momentum-true-wireless-4-earbuds-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Chris Welch</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-15T09:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-15T09:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Bose’s Ultra Open Earbuds are its boldest, most unique earbuds yet</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;With a design that clings to your outer ear, these earbuds are unlike anything the company has made before — and Bose hopes they’ll find more success than its unconventional products of the past.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="gMJhuU"&gt;Bose’s goal in developing the new Ultra Open Earbuds was to create a pair of earbuds that you can truly wear all day. With a design that attaches to the &lt;em&gt;side&lt;/em&gt; of your ears instead of going inside them, they’re anything but conventional. Bose released some impressive new products last year, but in the grand scheme of things, they were all fairly iterative. The Ultra Open Earbuds represent the biggest swing the company has taken in a long time. Will they go down as another short-term experiment like the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2018/5/4/17311570/bose-soundwear-companion-review-neck-speaker-bluetooth"&gt;SoundWear Companion&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/12/23998261/bose-frames-smart-glasses-discontinued-wearables"&gt;Bose Frames&lt;/a&gt;? Or, as Bose certainly hopes, are these a peek at the future of wearable tech? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GiKWhv"&gt;I don’t think there’s a simple answer. These unorthodox earbuds won’t be for everyone, and their premium $299 price immediately puts them out of range for many shoppers. Speaking for myself, someone who is happy to plug up his ear canals with high-quality buds in the name of sublime audio, I’m not the target market. The Ultra Open Earbuds are for people who want to maintain awareness of their surroundings at all times; their design fundamentally means you will &lt;em&gt;always&lt;/em&gt; hear external noise — and you’ll hear it naturally, at full volume. Whether you’re riding a bike, out for a run, working in an environment where regular earbuds aren’t practical, or just find the whole in-ear concept to be uncomfortable, these allow you to go about your day, stay fully alert, and jam along to a soundtrack the whole time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="pVVNzt"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12252903"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="HSjmoh"&gt;Having covered earbuds for many years now, I’ve learned that &lt;em&gt;many&lt;/em&gt; people simply don’t enjoy the feeling of earbuds sealing off their ears. It’s why Apple’s standard hard plastic &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22744686/apple-airpods-third-gen-review"&gt;AirPods&lt;/a&gt; remain so popular. It’s why you see companies like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/21356260/samsung-galaxy-buds-live-review-wireless-earbuds-beans-design-specs-price"&gt;Samsung&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22933521/sony-linkbuds-earbuds-review-features-specs"&gt;Sony&lt;/a&gt;, and many others selling a one-size-fits-most product alongside their silicone tip-style buds. It’s one of the key reasons that bone conduction headphones exist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="C4XO3R"&gt;There’s no bone conduction at play here, though. Like the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22351451/bose-frames-tempo-audio-sunglasses-review-features"&gt;Frames&lt;/a&gt; before them, the Ultra Open Earbuds use Bose’s OpenAudio technology to direct sound toward your ears while keeping your canals completely unobstructed and minimizing annoying audio leakage to those around you. This freedom comes with inherent tradeoffs. The Ultra Open Earbuds lack noise cancellation altogether, for one, and their bass response just isn’t going to be on par with traditional in-ear competitors. There’s no overcoming physics and a good seal. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Bose’s Ultra Open Earbuds." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/RlABLY1SZamsVp-SqXvUQtfA-lk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25286101/DSCF6430.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The case looks very conventional, but the earbuds inside definitely don’t.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="JIb6AI"&gt;These look nothing like previous Bose earbuds. They’re intended to resemble a fashion accessory just as much as they are tech. For this reason, the company purposefully didn’t put its logo on the brushed metallic outer surface. And the fit is unlike anything I’ve ever tried. After removing them from the very normal charging case, your first thought will probably be, “Uh, how do I put these on?” I did a little experiment, handing them to a few friends and leaving them to try to figure it out. Spoiler: they needed some guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="O5PkNg"&gt;Here’s the gist: the battery barrel sits behind your ear, and a flexible silicone band connects that to the “earbud” part, which wraps around your ear cartilage and just sort of rests somewhere on your ear’s antihelix. It’s not always obvious when you’ve got the right fit, which… is not a thing I often say about earbuds. You’ll find yourself checking a mirror (or your phone’s selfie camera) to see if the positioning is right. Bose told me that the sound can change slightly depending on where the Ultra Open Earbuds are positioned, but you want to shoot for the diagonal look seen in these review photos and the company’s press materials. Once they’re on, you control the buds by pressing the clicky round button at the top of each battery barrel, which feels natural in no time — and thankfully never jostles the earbuds loose. The silicone-coated flex arm is durable enough to withstand bending and even some twisting, and the earbuds are rated IPX4 for water resistance, so don’t worry about sweat or rain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid__wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid c-image-grid__odd"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Bose’s Ultra Open Earbuds." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/F28VTINjjs2wy6KV_gzP8d9ZO_w=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25286096/DSCF6437_2.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Bose’s Ultra Open Earbuds." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/XtbjpMW4OUes_iwspmZ-oW4wOpY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25286099/DSCF6448_Enhanced_NR_2.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Bose’s Ultra Open Earbuds." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/n0u0LlDwi05GCE5dla6J5xy12QY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25286097/DSCF6442.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This silicone flex arm keeps the buds on your ears without applying too much pressure.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="bbf2OO"&gt;As with everything, the overall look will be divisive, but Bose’s approach has its benefits. For one, the Ultra Open Earbuds are very comfortable. You shouldn’t think of these as &lt;em&gt;clipping&lt;/em&gt; onto your ears since that implies they apply unpleasant pressure. Can you feel them? Sure. But even after wearing them for five or six hours, any discomfort or ear fatigue was negligible. The grip of the flex arm is light enough that I sometimes forget they’re there, yet I can still forcefully shake my head without them falling off. The grip is definitely secure enough for running and other exercise. The lower ear positioning also means you can wear glasses, hats, and (some) jewelry without their getting in the way. That said, it’s important to recognize that all ears are different, and these might not be the best match for everyone. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Bose’s Ultra Open Earbuds." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ZW973gXT9UHZiZ3VdcuL5a6nk2A=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25286104/DSCF6456.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;You won’t get any noise cancellation from the Ultra Open Earbuds, and that’s by design.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="86tNzp"&gt;The Ultra Open Earbuds generally sound how I expected them to. And that’s to say that they’re clear, nicely detailed, and consistently pleasant to listen to. But you’re never going to be doing critical listening with buds like these. Bose is beaming sound at your ears with impressive precision, but that’s no substitute for ordinary earbuds that can deliver music with a fuller frequency range and greater depth and power at the low end. It’s extremely challenging to bring oomph to your tunes in a form factor like this, so bass is easily the leading weakness of these earbuds. I’m not saying it’s completely MIA, but you need to adjust your expectations and be okay forgoing the majority of the boom and rumble in your music. Some people won’t mind the sacrifice, but I routinely noticed it while testing the Ultra Open Earbuds. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Bose’s Ultra Open Earbuds." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/5zpsStXmvRQsvIEiCqcDoYPZaeM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25286105/DSCF6464_Enhanced_NR.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Since they don’t go in your ears, you can always hear what’s happening around you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="dm1MAn"&gt;I’ve learned that the biggest appeal of the Ultra Open Earbuds can also turn detrimental. It turns out that when given the choice, I don’t particularly love hearing the world at full volume when I’m wearing &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; pair of earbuds. New York City can be a truly overwhelming cacophony of construction, ear-piercing subway car screeching, and general commotion. In those scenarios, I actually prefer the smart transparency modes of many modern earbuds that can detect sudden upticks in ambient noise and reduce some of that harshness. Bose itself does this with its other earbuds, whereas the Ultra Open Earbuds leave you fully exposed to the clamor no matter how loud it becomes — sometimes for better, sometimes for worse. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="IraEFJ"&gt;An optional, off-by-default Auto Volume feature in the Bose Music app will make the earbuds automatically raise and lower their loudness based on your surroundings. If you’re in a noisy coffee shop, you’ll notice the volume go up a bit, and it’ll drop back down once you arrive home or sit down at the office. This setting never tries to drown out your environment; it aims to keep your private soundtrack on an even keel with whatever else might be happening. Call quality was generally good, but again, if you’re caught in a loud spot, it’s going to be difficult to hear whoever’s on the other side. This downside is familiar to anyone who uses AirPods, Sony’s LinkBuds, and other open-style buds, but those don’t cost nearly as much. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2KAFxe"&gt;Bose includes the same Immersive Audio (spatial audio) processing here that first came to its other “Ultra” &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23920591/bose-quietcomfort-ultra-headphones-review"&gt;headphones&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23883649/bose-quietcomfort-ultra-earbuds-review"&gt;earbuds&lt;/a&gt; last year. The story is the same: Immersive Audio sounds neat on a random song every so often. But I mostly left it off since it’s a major drag on battery life, dropping the earbuds from 7.5 hours of continuous listening down to 4.5. The charging case carries another 19.5 hours worth of juice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Bose’s Ultra Open Earbuds." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/EDso-pcihZGI-S9sDObL2dwWJp0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25286095/DSCF6454_Enhanced_NR.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bose aimed to develop earbuds that blend fashion and wearable tech.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="4aMIrJ"&gt;I can’t ding Bose for the lack of noise cancellation in an open-air product like this, but the absence of something as basic as wireless charging (unless you pay for an additional case) is frustrating. There’s no multipoint either, a feature that’s becoming table stakes for flagship earbuds and one that would be quite useful on a product you’re supposed to wear all day long. Many people are constantly juggling multiple devices, and Bose needs to do better at accommodating that. The company says multipoint will arrive via a software update later this year, and I’ll update this review when it does. In the meantime, you can assign the shortcut feature of either earbud’s button to “switch source” to quickly hop between previously paired devices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="g8REMo"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12253898"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="DYl90W"&gt;Stepping back, I can appreciate Bose’s ambition and desire to break away from the pack. It’s a gamble, and the Ultra Open Earbuds are undeniably unique. The fit takes some getting used to, but if you can live without thick bass, they deliver on their purpose of blending your music and daily life. Even so, I can’t shake the feeling that a severe price mismatch is at play here. $300 is hard to swallow for earbuds that, by their core design, are several rungs below the traditional in-ear competition if you’re going purely by audio fidelity. The bass presence of the Ultra Open Earbuds just isn’t on that level. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="TVdBT1"&gt;I don’t doubt that creating a wholly new earbud form factor required comprehensive research and engineering. In fact, I &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; it did, so stay tuned for more on that in the future. But if Bose wants the Ultra Open Earbuds to avoid the same fate as its other promising but niche gadgets — I still miss &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2018/5/4/17311570/bose-soundwear-companion-review-neck-speaker-bluetooth"&gt;that damn neck speaker&lt;/a&gt; — it should probably rethink the value proposition before it’s too late. I think there’s a real audience for these, but the concept is too out of the ordinary to ask for so much until that’s proven out. Otherwise, this big swing won’t make much of an impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="LyA0Eu"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24073019/bose-ultra-open-earbuds-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24073019/bose-ultra-open-earbuds-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Chris Welch</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-07T13:30:31-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-07T13:30:31-05:00</updated>
    <title>The best noise-canceling headphones to buy right now</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A pair of Sony WH-1000XM5 headphones, in black, resting flat on a wood table beside a laptop." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/1Yi9sFXnZ3b-FYYS4HNbyWq5zLc=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/67126629/DSCF7916.15.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sony’s WH-1000XM5 headphones have an all-new design.&lt;/em&gt; | Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;Get some peace and quiet with any of our top picks for noise-canceling headphones. Sony’s still the best overall, but there are reasons to go elsewhere, too.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="ViD2Nn"&gt;Whether you’re wearing them for the morning commute, while traveling, or if you’re simply trying to find some peace and quiet while working at home, noise-canceling headphones are a more essential piece of kit nowadays than ever before. And you’ve got a slew of great options to pick from; it’s hard to make a bad choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="YLU1nQ"&gt;There are the longtime heavyweights like Bose and Sony to pick from. Apple has quickly carved into the market with the luxurious AirPods Max. And if you’ve got an ear that demands the best audio quality, headphones from Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins and Sennheiser might appeal to you more than the mainstream contenders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="h38rrp"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The best wireless earbuds to buy right now","url":"https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="PodG2w"&gt;Not everyone loves the feel of earbuds, and there are scenarios where over-ear and on-ear headphones are just simpler or make more sense than wireless buds — particularly if lengthy battery life matters to you. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZsZx0q"&gt;No matter how you’re using them, the criteria for picking the best noise-canceling headphones haven’t changed. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="UHCr0z"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:11961389"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="lg7KKW"&gt;The “best” headphones for you will differ based on which of those factors you prioritize and care about most, but our overall pick for the best noise-canceling headphones remains&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23067645/sony-wh-1000xm5-noise-canceling-headphones-review"&gt;Sony’s WH-1000XM5&lt;/a&gt;. They offer a combination of sound quality, comfort, and great noise cancellation that’s hard to beat. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="svlFMO"&gt;
&lt;script src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.sbnation.com/csk/uploads/verge-toc.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;script&gt;

//this line summons a table of contents. use as follows!

//initiateTOC takes the arguments "header", "subheader", "collapsible"

//for whatever header type ("h2", "h3" etc) you want to be the main header, type it in quotes in the function call. 

//if you don't want subheads, set to false in the function call (no quotes)

//collapsible is a true/false toggle

//if you want a specific, unlinked title just add a string at the end in double quotes, e.g. false, "h3", false, "This is the title"

//see graham if you have any questions/issues

// note that all the header types are off by one: an h1 in the CMS is an h2 in the actual code. If you just want h2 and h3 to show up in the TOC you need to call them h3 and h4. 


window.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', (event) =&gt; {
	initiateTOC("h2", "h3", false, "The best noise-canceling headphones")
});


&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.sbnation.com/csk/uploads/verge-toc.css"&gt;


&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component verge-table-of-contents border-franklin border" id="toc-main"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="e21VnC"&gt;The best wireless headphones for most people&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="ezDvSM"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11301812" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="kX8D2c"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 30 hours / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audio codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; LDAC, AAC, SBC &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connectors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;: USB-C (charging), 3.5mm headphone jack (audio)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="49SoTG"&gt;Sony’s WH-1000XM5s have a completely different design from their predecessors. The changes result in greater comfort when you’re wearing them on your head for extended periods of time — like on a flight or if you’re at the office.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="QjKN0Y"&gt;Noise cancellation has been further improved from the already-stellar performance of the M4s, putting Sony at the front of the pack compared to all major competitors. Sound quality is more detailed and balanced than the older 1000XM4s; the low end is still punchy but tighter and less boomy than before. The M5s offer the best voice call performance in the 1000X series to date, and they can connect to two devices simultaneously, so you can stay clued in to what’s happening on your phone when you’re working away on your laptop or tablet. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A man wearing Sony’s black WH-1000XM5 noise-canceling headphones outside." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/GslmlesWh5-DskItliRBP5LhFRs=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23454336/DSCF7813.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sony’s WH-1000XM5 are the best overall choice for noise-canceling headphones.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="8iloOp"&gt;Sony’s headphones also include unique features like “speak to chat,” which automatically pauses your music and pipes in ambient audio whenever you start talking. Or you can hold one hand over the right ear cup to activate quick attention mode, which is convenient when grabbing a coffee or listening to airport announcements. And like other high-end headphones, the 1000XM5s can detect when they’ve been removed from your ears for auto-pause. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lzOHO3"&gt;The main downside of the WH-1000XM5s is that at $399.99, they’re more expensive than prior models. That’s a big reason to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/21356313/sony-1000xm4-noise-canceling-headphones-review-price-specs-features"&gt;consider the 1000XM4s&lt;/a&gt;, which were our previous top pick for noise-canceling headphones. They remain part of Sony’s lineup and can often be found on sale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="3O4UId"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23067645/sony-wh-1000xm5-noise-canceling-headphones-review"&gt;Read my full review of Sony’s WH-1000XM5.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="zwdkfG"&gt;The best noise-canceling headphones for travel&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="85omEe"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12174609" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="FUO87b"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 24 hours / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audio codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; aptX Adaptive, AAC, SBC &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connectors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;: USB-C (charging), 2.5mm headphone jack (audio)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZZQ58k"&gt;Bose’s QuietComfort Ultra Headphones are basically a blend of the company’s prior Noise Canceling Headphones 700 and QuietComfort 45s that borrow the best traits from both — while throwing in a new “immersive audio” listening mode. Like past Bose cans, they’re very light and comfortable on your head, even when worn for long stretches of time. Best of all, unlike the Noise Canceling Headphones 700, these can be folded to make them easier to travel with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uZDlqa"&gt;Their 24-hour battery life is more than adequate, and Bose has added support for the aptX Adaptive Bluetooth codec for improved audio fidelity on Android devices. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Bose’s QuietComfort Ultra Headphones." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/99dspD37YAt2zVk4BQTayJ4Wdow=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25008886/DSCF3709.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="xTkhOA"&gt;The immersive audio feature works well on some songs, but less so on others. It’s worth experimenting with, but even if you leave it off entirely, you’re left with best-in-class noise cancelation, pleasing sound, and a useful “aware” transparency mode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="7w2pUJ"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23920591/bose-quietcomfort-ultra-headphones-review"&gt;Read my full review of Bose’s QuietComfort Ultra Headphones.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="b7jGRn"&gt;The best wireless headphones for iPhone owners&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="bYPzk0"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10361602" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="PZZytm"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 20 hours / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audio codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AAC, SBC &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connectors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;: Lightning (audio and charging)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AXEBd8"&gt;There was definitely some sticker shock when Apple introduced a $549 set of noise-canceling headphones. The AirPods Max cost significantly more money than any of our other recommendations. But Apple’s build quality is on another level: these trade the plastic you’ll find in many noise-canceling headphones for steel and aluminum, and the ear cups are a breathable mesh fabric. They’re hefty headphones, there’s no denying that. But aside from Apple refusing to include a headphone cable in the box, there’s nothing about the AirPods Max that feels cheap. And I appreciate the simplicity of using the digital crown for controls instead of relying on hit-or-miss gestures like taps and swipes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2d4O3y"&gt;The most important part is that the AirPods Max deliver audio quality that’s up there with the best high-end Bluetooth headphones. They have an immersive, wide soundstage, fantastic dynamics, and you’ll find yourself hopping around your music library just to hear what they bring out in your favorite songs. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Apple’s AirPods Max headphones." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/qWRYAZEz9UZUwVKhcMv8_13XOJE=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24775818/DSCF2505_Enhanced_NR.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The AirPods Max have a stylish design and very premium build quality.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="Quv0fw"&gt;Apple’s noise cancellation is on par with Sony and Bose, and no one does transparency mode better; at times, it can make you think you’re not wearing headphones at all. Extra features like Spatial Audio (surround sound for movies and TV shows) and automatic switching between Apple gadgets help make it a bit easier to swallow that daunting price.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="jVlWWZ"&gt;But the AirPods Max do have faults. The carrying case is abysmal, battery life is only average for the category, and just like regular AirPods, they’re designed with Apple’s ecosystem in mind. It gets much harder to justify dropping $550 on them if you live outside the iPhone and Mac universe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="dge2ZO"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22177494/apple-airpods-max-headphones-review-price-features"&gt;Read my full review of the AirPods Max.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="yj00sX"&gt;The best-sounding wireless headphones&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="Wgtz7c"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12246003" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="okO8Go"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 30 hours / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audio codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; aptX Adaptive, aptX HD, aptX, AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connectors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;: USB-C (audio and charging)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rqLSMi"&gt;If sound quality is priority number one, then Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins has you covered with the PX7 S2e headphones. They exhibit superb, detailed sound quality that some people prefer to the AirPods Max. The Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins cans are true to the company’s legacy and style, with a fine-crafted design that exudes quality. And the newer “e” variant has an revamped digital signal processing that can bring out the best audio quality from streaming music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4WwWhD"&gt;I prefer their physical buttons over the tap/swipe ear cup gestures of Sony’s 1000XM5s. With 30 hours of battery life, they’re more than competitive with mainstream, less expensive picks. And the sound profile is delightfully warm and will bring out the most from your favorite music. The main downside of the PX7 S2e is that there’s no traditional 3.5mm or 2.5mm output for a headphone cable. You can still listen wired over USB-C, however.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="bsPogG"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23187234/bowers-wilkins-px7-s2-noise-canceling-headphones-review"&gt;Read my full review of the Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins PX7 S2.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="9TcpSo"&gt;The noise-canceling headphones with the best battery life&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="5RI5Zy"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11636778" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="gQDBWN"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 60 hours / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audio codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; aptX Adaptive, aptX, AAC, SBC / Connectors: USB-C (audio and charging), 2.5mm headphone jack (audio)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="r7fSPB"&gt;60 hours. They can last for up to &lt;em&gt;60 hours&lt;/em&gt; on a single charge. That’s really all you need to know about the Sennheiser Momentum 4 headphones if you’re looking for an endurance champ. But they also sound terrific and prove extremely comfortable over long listening periods. This combination doesn’t come cheap, but you can find some good occasional deals on them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="SGZqkd"&gt;Sennheiser’s Momentum 4 Wireless headphones edge out Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins on comfort thanks to their lighter design, and the noise cancellation is slightly better. Next to the Sonys and QC45s, it doesn’t get much cozier. These are headphones you can wear for multiple hours without any fatigue or pressure on your ears. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="The Sennheiser Momentum 3 and Sennheiser Momentum 4 headphones facing each other while lying on a couch." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/9zHvLFyE83yhJ7wktT7z8-M-8zY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23930400/DSCF8573.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;They lack the vintage style of prior Sennheiser cans (like the Momentum 3s, left), but the Momentum 4s are far more comfortable.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="YwbK4c"&gt;Sennheiser’s sound signature is a bit more expressive and puts more emphasis on bass than B&amp;amp;W, but that upper treble range still comes through crystal clear. My only real nitpick with the Sennheisers is that they tend to occasionally power on inside the case for no obvious reason and automatically connect to my phone. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="MSmJ28"&gt;Both the B&amp;amp;W and Sennheiser headphones support multipoint connectivity and a range of Bluetooth codecs including SBC, AAC, aptX, and aptX Adaptive. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="MX154l"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23297129/sennheiser-momentum-4-wireless-headphones-review"&gt;Read my full review of Sennheiser’s Momentum 4 Wireless.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="DO2V4l"&gt;The best noise-canceling headphones for style&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="wsAWSF"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10361724" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="P2UCzu"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 60 hours / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audio codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; aptX Adaptive, aptX HD, aptX, AAC, SBC &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connectors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;: USB-C (charging), 3.5mm headphone jack (audio)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="F7quUY"&gt;Marshall’s wireless headphones have proven surprisingly popular, and the company’s most expensive pair is also its best yet. The Monitor II ANC headphones are priced at $320, which puts them on the same playing field as Bose, Sony, and other tech companies that have been making premium noise-canceling cans for many years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ht7uR3"&gt;Marshall falls short of those brands in sound quality and ANC, but the Monitor IIs still provide warm, textured sound and perform decently at cutting down on ambient noise. But they definitely stand out from the pack in looks, with a design that speaks to the company’s heritage. The headphones fold up for easy carrying, and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/circuitbreaker/2018/10/24/18018074/marshall-joystick-headphone-button-control-audio-bluetooth-wireless"&gt;Marshall’s signature gold joystick&lt;/a&gt; makes the Monitor IIs simple to control. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wFNLUi"&gt;They can also last up to 30 hours with NC enabled or up to a staggering 45 hours if you’re already someplace quiet and can do without the feature. That impressive longevity beats our primary picks. A lack of AAC codec support at this price stings, but I’ve enjoyed the Monitor IIs every time I’ve put them on. They’re more than just an amp brand stamped onto an average pair of headphones. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="R2Fwrx"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update, February 7th 1:30PM ET:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; The buying guide was updated to add the Bose QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds and Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins PX7 S2e headphones.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/21345733/best-noise-canceling-headphones"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/21345733/best-noise-canceling-headphones</id>
    <author>
      <name>Chris Welch</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-31T10:30:55-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-31T10:30:55-05:00</updated>
    <title>The best wireless earbuds to buy right now</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A photo of Sony’s WF-1000XM5 earbuds." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/e6t1Ea8VCnt9pPlNtEqC2_bCfCc=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/67005648/DSCF2232.22.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;The best from Apple, Bose, Samsung, Sony, Beats, Google, and more.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="m88Abd"&gt;It’s hard to buy a bad pair of wireless earbuds these days, and with constant discounts and deals wherever you look, now is as good of a time as any to splurge on the pair you’ve been eyeing. The market has come a long way since the early era of true wireless earbuds when we had to deal with mediocre sound quality and unreliable performance, all for the sake of ditching cables. Things are much different now. After several product generations of learned lessons, companies like Sony, Apple, Samsung, and others are releasing their most impressive earbuds to date. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="H0HzJg"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The best noise-canceling headphones to buy right now","url":"https://www.theverge.com/21345733/best-noise-canceling-headphones"},{"title":"The best workout earbuds you can buy right now","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23413809/best-workout-fitness-running-earbuds"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="Bdn1ZK"&gt;You can get phenomenal noise cancellation and sound quality in the premium tier of earbuds if you’re willing to spend big. But those aren’t always the most important criteria for everyone: maybe you’re looking for the perfect fitness earbuds or for a set that works just as well for Zoom calls as for playing your favorite playlists and podcasts. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="LJz8zl"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:11846666"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="Qaw7pU"&gt;Tech companies are increasingly making their earbuds &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22627099/samsung-galaxy-buds-2-apple-airpods-pro-ecosystem-lock-in-features-companion-app"&gt;work best with their own products&lt;/a&gt; through exclusive features and functionality, so that’s another thing to consider as you shop around. If you want a perk like head-tracking spatial audio, you’ll need to use AirPods with an iPhone, Samsung buds with a Samsung phone, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="JkELVs"&gt;
&lt;script src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.sbnation.com/csk/uploads/verge-toc.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;script&gt;

//this line summons a table of contents. use as follows!

//initiateTOC takes the arguments "header", "subheader", "collapsible"

//for whatever header type ("h2", "h3" etc) you want to be the main header, type it in quotes in the function call

//if you don't want subheads, set to false in the function call (no quotes)

//collapsible is a true/false toggle

//see graham if you have any questions/issues

window.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', (event) =&gt; {
	initiateTOC("h2", "h3", false, "Best wireless earbuds of 2024")
});

&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.sbnation.com/csk/uploads/verge-toc.css"&gt;

&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component verge-table-of-contents border-franklin border" id="toc-main"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr class="p-entry-hr" id="zlQO6t"&gt;
&lt;h2 id="NRILW6"&gt;The best overall wireless earbuds&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="tjTWnE"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12000289" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="a4eSWh"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 8 hours (ANC on) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX4 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; LDAC, AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Android, iOS, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Foam (XS, S, M, L)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="iRpJZT"&gt;Just like their predecessors, Sony’s new WF-1000XM5 earbuds have again topped our recommendations for the overall best noise-canceling earbuds. Thanks to their larger drivers, the audio quality is more detailed and dynamic than before while still retaining the warmth and clarity that made the 1000XM4s so enjoyable. Sony has also further improved its ANC and is nearing the same territory as Bose’s QC Earbuds II. These earbuds do a terrific job of eliminating background noise. Battery life can stretch to eight hours of continuous listening with noise cancellation turned on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="SHOmBh"&gt;Some people found the WF-1000XM4s to be bulky and uncomfortable, so this time around, Sony has managed to shrink the 1000XM5s by 25 percent. Like before, the company includes foam-style tips that expand in your ears to create an excellent seal — and now there’s a fourth (extra small) set of tips in the box.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Sony’s WF-1000XM5 earbuds." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/-Qgl4G_EqefK2KNdOmsOoXIyhiQ=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24805959/DSCF2249_Enhanced_NR.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The WF-1000XM5s are smaller and more comfortable than their M4 predecessors.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="de0Fag"&gt;On Android phones, the 1000XM5s support Sony’s LDAC codec for higher-quality music playback. And they’re capable of dynamic head tracking spatial audio through supported video apps like Netflix. But even if you’re not using LDAC (or have an iPhone), these are up there with the very best audio-focused premium earbuds like Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless 2 — with substantially better noise cancellation to boot. They’re also capable of multipoint Bluetooth, so you can pair with two devices at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="T49ehN"&gt;It’s worth noting that there were many reports of battery issues with the 1000XM4s over time as those earbuds aged, but Sony claims to have rectified that problem with the new model by tweaking the charging algorithm. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="SUJOO3"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23803374/sony-wf-1000xm5-earbuds-review"&gt;Read my full Sony WF-1000XM5 review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="d26N53"&gt;The best budget earbuds under $100&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="lrZewS"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10844228" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="QluRxu"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;7&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;hours / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX55 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Android, iOS, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Silicone (S, M, L)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xyCMjr"&gt;Sometimes all you need are the fundamentals, and that’s where &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22676362/jabra-elite-3-wireless-earbuds-review"&gt;Jabra’s Elite 3 earbuds&lt;/a&gt; manage to rise above the crowded field of sub-$100 competition. Their sound puts some emphasis on the bass but still manages to come through nicely balanced overall with very good clarity for this price range.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="F63F5J"&gt;The earbuds last for up to seven hours of continuous playback, and the compact case holds three additional charges. Their large physical buttons are easy to use, and the earbuds are rated IP55 for dust and water resistance. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A pair of Jabra’s Elite 3 wireless earbuds sitting on a table near a phone." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Lx1n1-UXCTGwKwbgPg4-95FUU5g=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/22854826/DSCF5585_Edited.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Jabra Elite 3 are the best wireless earbuds under $100.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="YdhZzT"&gt;The Elite 3s lack the multipoint feature that Jabra has long been known for — that’s the main sacrifice you make for the price — but in an improvement from past models, either earbud can be used standalone in mono mode. And they’re extremely comfortable to wear for long stretches. You don’t get features like active noise cancellation or wireless charging (though Jabra does include a so-so transparency mode), but the Elite 3s perform reliably with a strong Bluetooth signal. They’re a terrific value for the money. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="cu7Iwi"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22676362/jabra-elite-3-wireless-earbuds-review"&gt;Read my full Jabra Elite 3 review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="UWDcU8"&gt;The best noise-canceling earbuds&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="EGS3sY"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12085566" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="aYyqbo"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;hours (ANC on) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX4 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AAC, SBC, aptX Adaptive / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Android, iOS, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Silicone (S, M, L)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="PnBxID"&gt;Bose’s QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds are the most powerful noise-canceling earbuds on the market. Of all our top picks, these do the best job at offering peace and quiet from the cacophony of daily life and putting you in a private bubble with your music playlists or favorite podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Bose’s QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/FO99fbhFzIUSCx5CCDayEcw24so=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24939904/DSCF3082_Enhanced_NR.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bose’s QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds offer the best noise cancellation you’ll find from any wireless buds.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zicZdh"&gt;The QC Ultra Earbuds are extremely similar to 2022’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23353777/bose-quietcomfort-earbuds-2-review"&gt;QC Earbuds II&lt;/a&gt; in terms of design, fit, and sound. Audio quality is rich and dynamic, delivering more bass thump than, say, Apple’s AirPods Pro. And by switching to a two-piece ear tip / stabilizer fitting process, Bose’s latest flagship buds should fit a wider range of ears more comfortably. The Ultras introduce a new immersive audio, Bose’s take on spatial audio, &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="9kRlVK"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23883649/bose-quietcomfort-ultra-earbuds-review"&gt;Read my full Bose QuietComfort Ultra Earbuds review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="09JCVi"&gt;The best earbuds for sports and working out&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="wSabJY"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10844241" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="k7iRU4"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;hours (ANC on) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX4 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Android, iOS, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Silicone (S, M, L)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xk3ZRx"&gt;The long-reigning champ of fitness earbuds, the Powerbeats Pro, have finally been defeated. And fittingly, they’ve been outdone by Beats’ latest earbuds. The &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22753158/beats-fit-pro-earbuds-review-apple"&gt;Beats Fit Pro&lt;/a&gt; trade the ear hooks of the Powerbeats for a new wing tip design that keeps them securely locked in your ears during even the most vigorous workouts. As a result, these earbuds have a much smaller form factor — and their carrying case is mercifully far more manageable. The way these earbuds magnetically latch into the case also means you don’t have to worry about one or both buds failing to charge in the case, which was a common annoyance with the Powerbeats Pro.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="XPJTnP"&gt;Unlike the Powerbeats Pro, the Fit Pros include active noise cancellation. And they’re on par with the AirPods Pro in that department, so you’ll be able to exercise without distraction. When you do want to stay alert to your surroundings, the transparency mode is also as natural-sounding and clear as on the AirPod Pros. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of two pairs of Beats Fit Pro earbuds on a marble surface." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/FsxJwPiXSnqd8rZcgxUVwdU9Fjw=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/22975670/DSCF6022_Edited.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Beats Fit Pro are the best earbuds for running and working out.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="sfx8aI"&gt;The earbuds are rated IPX4 for water resistance. While that’s not as robust as some other fitness-focused buds, it should be sufficient to survive sweat and outdoor runs in various conditions. The Fit Pros have easy-to-use physical button controls, and although they lack the dedicated volume rocker of the Powerbeats Pro, you’ve got the option to remap a long-press of each earbud to adjust volume instead of toggling noise cancellation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="W7gkOl"&gt;If you’re an iPhone owner, the Fit Pros offer Apple-only features like dynamic head tracking for spatial audio, auto device switching, Find My integration, and more. For Android users, Beats has an app that will let you adjust settings and see the battery status of the earbuds and case, among other functions. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="orqrNZ"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22753158/beats-fit-pro-earbuds-review-apple"&gt;Read my full Beats Fit Pro review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="MzRNQU"&gt;The best earbuds for iPhone owners&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="CykT00"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11535686" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="lz2YvX"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;hours (ANC on) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX4 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; iOS, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Silicone (XS, S, M, L)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lLBDNk"&gt;For those invested in Apple’s ecosystem, the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23365910/apple-airpods-pro-second-generation-review"&gt;second-generation AirPods Pro&lt;/a&gt; combine an appealing mix of top-notch noise cancellation and refined sound compared to the original pair. As always, they also include numerous features (spatial audio, audio sharing, automatic syncing across iCloud devices, etc.) that make them an ideal companion to the company’s other devices. They’re also the only AirPods that come with different sizes of ear tips for a customizable fit — now including an extra small option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Apple’s second-generation AirPods Pro pictured on an airplane tray table beside an iPhone 14." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/GSJ0GBNc-zefQaiwE8hpMSfz6xA=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24040645/226285_AIRPODS_PRO_2_cwelch_0001.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The second-gen AirPods Pro remain the best choice for people who own Apple devices.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="kqPPhS"&gt;The AirPods Pro have a compact case that supports wireless charging. Setting them up is as simple as holding the open case near your iPhone. The earbuds are lightweight and fit snugly in most ears. Their force sensor pinch controls are easy to get down, and with the second-gen model, Apple added swipe-based volume controls. The AirPods Pro have traditionally ranked among the best wireless earbuds when it comes to voice call quality, and the second-gen earbuds don’t disappoint. Their ANC is improved over the original model and now right up there with Sony, and transparency mode has gained the ability to quickly damper sudden, loud noises that might happen around you. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mxfus6"&gt;Where the AirPods stand out is with their Apple-only features like head tracking for spatial audio, automatic device switching, extensive Find My support, and so on. The charging case now features a built-in speaker and a U1 chip for pinpoint location tracking. The second-gen AirPods Pro have better sound and noise canceling capabilities than the originals and retain their deep integration with Apple’s hardware ecosystem. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="J28XlG"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23365910/apple-airpods-pro-second-generation-review"&gt;Read my full Apple AirPods Pro (second generation) review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="UDK4Rq"&gt;The best earbuds for Samsung Galaxy phone owners&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="yhyMDq"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11535696" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="J4vdR4"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;hours (ANC on) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX7 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Samsung seamless, AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Android, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Silicone (S, M, L)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="FuVr9O"&gt;Samsung’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23312192/samsung-galaxy-buds-2-pro-review"&gt;Galaxy Buds 2 Pro&lt;/a&gt; sound terrific, and that’s &lt;em&gt;before&lt;/em&gt; you take advantage of the optional 24-bit audio support. Compared to the first Pros, these have a smaller, lighter design that doesn’t protrude from your ears, and the audio quality is second only to the Sennheisers among our favorite earbud picks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A pair of Samsung’s new Galaxy Buds 2 Pro sitting on top of a phone." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/mdpFHvx_mDsRpynk1bWmHYhhyys=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23956546/DSCF8720.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Samsung’s Galaxy Buds 2 Pro have fantastic sound quality and a very comfortable fit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="2LdugR"&gt;Like the AirPods Pro with Apple devices, the Buds 2 Pro offer Samsung-only tricks like head tracking for spatial audio, auto device switching between Samsung devices, and so on. The compact charging case supports wireless charging, and the Buds 2 Pro have a worry-free IPX7 rating against water and sweat, making them even more durable than the AirPods. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="PZokuE"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23312192/samsung-galaxy-buds-2-pro-review"&gt;Read my full Samsung Galaxy Buds 2 Pro review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="NUGgdY"&gt;The best earbuds for Google Pixel phone owners&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="STV1YX"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11455601" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="63RCEq"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;7&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;hours (ANC on) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX4 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Android, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Silicone (S, M, L)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="h1zCNL"&gt;Google finally nailed wireless earbuds with the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23281445/google-pixel-buds-pro-noise-canceling-earbuds-review"&gt;Pixel Buds Pro&lt;/a&gt;. Thanks to their impressive noise cancellation, good sound quality, and comfortable fit, they greatly improve upon the flawed second-generation Pixel Buds. Most important of all, they don’t exhibit any of the connectivity issues and audio dropouts that plagued Google’s earlier buds. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dLjPV8"&gt;Instead, the Pixel Buds Pro deliver a consistently great listening experience with lengthy battery life to go along with it. They also include multipoint Bluetooth support, so you can pair Google’s flagship earbuds with two devices at the same time. It’s a hugely convenient feature that Apple, Bose, Samsung, and Sony have yet to bring to their respective earbuds. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Google’s Pixel Buds Pro in a woman’s ear." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Yxw0bn-3geLOvXwBR-YKto_qxg4=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23905444/DSCF8473.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’ve got a Google phone, the Pixel Buds Pro are a great choice.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="7E0MSq"&gt;Pixel phone owners get bonuses like easier settings (the Pixel Buds controls are built right into the native phone settings), and thanks to a recent software update, these earbuds &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/4/23538743/google-pixel-spatial-audio-buds-pro-january-update"&gt;now support head tracking spatial audio&lt;/a&gt;. That’s a nice option to have for enhanced immersion when watching movies and other entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="KrjFep"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23281445/google-pixel-buds-pro-noise-canceling-earbuds-review"&gt;Read my full Google Pixel Buds Pro review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="dv7Dfx"&gt;The best earbuds if you own both Apple and Android devices&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="g4BMxs"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11905736" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="gnSVpx"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;6 hours (ANC on) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX4 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Android, iOS, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Silicone (XS, S, M, L)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="QrcOpK"&gt;Beats’ Studio Buds Plus are an upgraded, better performing revision of the Studio Buds released in 2021. This time the company has made the noise cancellation more powerful while also improving the quality of the transparency mode and extending battery life. If you’re going for style points, it doesn’t get much cooler than the translucent color option. These earbuds are very tiny and rank up with the best in terms of overall comfort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of Beats’ translucent Studio Buds Plus earbuds." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/NthRTBe52y-raSKP6EsXUetysUY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24662272/DSCF0775_Enhanced_NR.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The translucent color option has a very ‘90s vibe.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="Hz4D2j"&gt;What’s interesting about the Studio Buds Plus is that they use a proprietary chip that allows them to support native software features on both iOS and Android. Plenty of earbuds offer companion apps on each platform, but in the case of the Beats, they work with both Apple’s Find My and Google’s Find My Device. You also get simple one-tap pairing no matter which OS you’re using. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7goUHx"&gt;The drawback to this dual-ecosystem life is that Apple customers don’t get &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; the usual bells and whistles that come with AirPods or even the Beats Fit Pro; you lose out on audio sharing, head tracking spatial audio, and other tricks. Wireless charging and an ear detection sensor (for auto-pause when a bud is removed) are also MIA, which stings a bit considering the price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="N3Z6oA"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23725921/beats-studio-buds-plus-earbuds-review-translucent-clear"&gt;Read my full Beats Studio Buds Plus review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="ziSHXY"&gt;The best earbuds for sound quality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="EPGa3l"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11295816" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="qYzoZg"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;7&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;hours (ANC on) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX4 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AptX Adaptive, AptX, AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Android, iOS, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Silicone (S, M, L)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="pJYhX6"&gt;The third generation of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23059336/sennheiser-momentum-true-wireless-3-earbuds-review"&gt;Sennheiser’s Momentum True Wireless&lt;/a&gt; earbuds deliver tremendous, detailed sound quality that stands above nearly all competitors. They’re a joy to listen to, and even better, they’re now smaller and more comfortable than previous models — with a case that finally supports wireless charging. The active noise cancellation can’t compete with the likes of Apple, Sony, and Bose, but if you care more about lush, intricate sound, the MTW3s won’t disappoint in the slightest. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/LH3G7082dGiEFr5DUG4FaktZPZ4=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23441291/cwelch_220505_5199_0009.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Sennheiser Momentum True Wireless 3 earbuds sound absolutely fantastic.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="yaWD39"&gt;Unlike past iterations, these earbuds come with optional wing tips to help keep them securely locked in your ears. That could prove helpful for running or when hitting the gym. Sennheiser allows for plenty of EQ customization using its mobile app, and the Momentum True Wireless 3s support a range of Bluetooth codecs, including AAC, SBC, AptX, and AptX Adaptive. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="eErhgy"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23059336/sennheiser-momentum-true-wireless-3-earbuds-review"&gt;Read my full Sennheiser Momentum True Wireless 3 review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="pZuYRQ"&gt;The best earbuds for voice calls on iPhone&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="AO0ZgQ"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10844500" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="uGlTga"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;hours / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX4 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; iOS, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; None&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2Yu1aA"&gt;Apple’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22744686/apple-airpods-third-gen-review"&gt;third-generation AirPods&lt;/a&gt; have a new design with shorter stems than the original model. But even with their mics now being farther from your mouth, they still perform very well on calls — and there are bigger improvements to sound quality and fit / comfort that make upgrading to the so-called AirPods 3 worthwhile. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="The third-gen AirPods resting on a laptop on a desk." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/WK-mSuFuVOg5iUNkHQdRI1SwPYA=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/22953803/IMG_0044.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Apple’s AirPods 3 are the best earbuds for voice calls and sound much better than their predecessors.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="lZKllk"&gt;Apple has also added new features that were previously exclusive to the AirPods Pro, like head tracking spatial audio and deeper Find My integration for hunting down your misplaced buds. And the case is now optimized to work with Apple’s MagSafe wireless charging system. The AirPods still have a one-size-fits-most hard plastic form factor, so you’ll want to try them before buying to make sure they’re the right match for your ears. But if they are, these are Apple’s best regular AirPods yet by a wide margin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="PxCkgD"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22744686/apple-airpods-third-gen-review"&gt;Read my full Apple AirPods (third generation) review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="pTcGEr"&gt;The best earbuds for voice calls on Android&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="Ocf412"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11150910" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="iCySqh"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;5.5&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;hours / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX4 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Android, iOS, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Fitting supporters (XS, S, M, L, XL)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8OHWyv"&gt;Sony’s unconventional-looking &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22933521/sony-linkbuds-earbuds-review-features-specs"&gt;LinkBuds&lt;/a&gt; have a donut hole right in the middle of each earbud. This surprisingly comfortable design is meant to allow in outside noise and keep you aware of your surroundings at all times. But it also means that the LinkBuds won’t be for everyone — especially those people who prefer to drown out the world when listening to their music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/yeZR7S10SzSHm1RIGsMkKrMyago=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23241306/9A5F2D63_4916_4C88_8108_219AB41DDB45.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sony’s LinkBuds are the best earbuds for voice calls on Android.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="KW66TB"&gt;But more than their quirky fit, the LinkBuds’ greatest strength is stellar performance on voice calls. Sony reworked its voice isolation algorithms for these earbuds, and as a result, the LinkBuds are several rungs above nearly &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; competitors minus AirPods. If you’re looking for something you can pop into your ears throughout the workday, the LinkBuds don’t disappoint. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="a96V38"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22933521/sony-linkbuds-earbuds-review-features-specs"&gt;Read my full review of the Sony LinkBuds.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="OMz1V5"&gt;The best earbuds for standout style&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="sx6MKG"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11846833" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="HN9xEF"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noise cancellation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Battery life: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;4&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;hours (ANC on) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Water resistance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; IPX4 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bluetooth codecs:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; AAC, SBC / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multipoint:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works best with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Android, iOS, Windows, macOS / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ear tips:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Silicone (S, M, L)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="0pKVp1"&gt;Nothing’s second-generation earbuds, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23649968/nothing-ear-2-review-wireless-earbuds"&gt;the Ear 2s&lt;/a&gt;, preserve the stylish look of the originals while making big strides in sound quality and active noise cancellation. With their semi-translucent design and unique charging case, the Ear 2 earbuds are sure to catch some attention when sitting beside earbuds from more established brands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="A photo of the Nothing Ear 2 earbuds with one earbud inside the charging case, and the other outside." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Rsg6xotbe8fhVbDD-wGM4f2g-BY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24516091/236578_Nothing_Ear_2_JPorter_0001.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Jon Porter / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Nothing Ear 2 earbuds look very similar to their predecessors.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="sgpBFG"&gt;The Ear 2 earbuds also add multipoint connectivity, a feature that the first pair lacked, to let you pair with two audio sources at the same time. The $149 price has gone up a bit compared to the Ear 1, but at least you don’t have to break the bank for the fresh looks and audio improvements that come with the Ear 2s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="niHQRF"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23649968/nothing-ear-2-review-wireless-earbuds"&gt;Read Jon Porter’s full Nothing Ear 2 review.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p id="IpwnSn"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photography by Chris Welch / The Verge except where specified&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="QSR2yw"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update January 31st, 10:30AM ET: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Updated to reflect current pricing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds</id>
    <author>
      <name>Chris Welch</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
