<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Gift Guides</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-02-23T17:50:25-05:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/gift-guide/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/gift-guide" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-23T17:50:25-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-23T17:50:25-05:00</updated>
    <title>The best tech gifts for under $25</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Nanoleaf Essentials A19 bulb and Essentials Lightstrip in a bedroom scene." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/bx33P4SyQAwE8-9oQyYRge5frkU=/300x0:1920x1080/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/71013267/Essentials_Bedroom_with_Homepod_mini.10.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;There are plenty of great tech gifts that can light up someone’s life for less than $25, from smart bulbs to everyday essentials.&lt;/em&gt; | Image: Nanoleaf&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="YdM8Rv"&gt;Wanting to treat a friend or a loved one to some tech or a cool gadget while on a very lean budget can feel like an impossible task. Most of the everyday devices we use cost multiple hundreds of dollars, so what do you get when you just want a nice birthday or “just because” kind of gift but can’t break the bank? Sure, you could default to something basic like a pair of socks or a scarf, but that gets boring fast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="3nPZ8Q"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The best tech you can gift mom year-round","url":"https://www.theverge.com/22899871/best-gifts-mom-tech-gadgets-ideas-christmas-birthday-mothers-valentines-day"},{"title":"The best tech gifts for under $50","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23161828/best-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="PrhgsO"&gt;Here, we’ve assembled a bunch of cool tech ideas on a budget of just $25 that are worth your money, including &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07LGY5RSG?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;a headphone stand ($19.99)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B07LF1FNRV/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;a quality USB-C cable ($9.99)&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DPVF8DQ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;unique Bluetooth speaker&lt;/a&gt;, and other essentials. Some of these items might not sound very fun or exciting at first, but they’re all helpful gifts that any tech-head can appreciate. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="VLpiEI"&gt;Anker MagGo Qi2 Wireless Charger&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="Nlgtaw"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A charger that’s cheaper and longer than Apple’s charging puck&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="L53aiX"&gt;If you need a gift for someone in the tech bubble and want to cement your spot as the coolest person in their life, try getting them the Anker MagGo Wireless Charger, which is only &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Anker-Magnetic-Certified-Ultra-Fast-Compatible/dp/B0CMH2JVMM?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$21.99 at Amazon&lt;/a&gt;. Qi2 chargers standardize the faster 15W wireless charging speeds that were once limited to MagSafe-certified products. Anker’s version has a five-foot cable for those who felt Apple’s official MagSafe charger was too short. As of writing, only the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/5/23989606/iphone-13-14-qi2-magsafe-compatible-apple-ios-17-2"&gt;iPhone 13 and newer&lt;/a&gt; support Qi2, so you should confirm which phone they have before purchasing one. It’s also worth noting that it doesn’t ship with the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Anker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included/dp/B099F558S1?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;20W adapter&lt;/a&gt; required to unlock its full charging potential, so try to figure out whether your recipient already has one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="dpe58O"&gt;
&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12259869"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="eD9jBF"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The best magnetic chargers to buy for your MagSafe iPhone","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23505846/best-magsafe-magnetic-chargers-apple-iphone"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/BA5hYgEZG5WUYyQrbTqWoGOoXgM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24380598/uni_usb_c_cable_switch_ipad.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Uni&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;A great, lengthy USB-C cable is just too handy to be without. And once you have one you soon find a need for having more than one, like playing while charging your Nintendo Switch or PlayStation DualSense controller.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="xM7GkJ"&gt;Uni USB-C to USB-C cable (10 feet)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="GhXVKn"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A much longer braided cable for laptop charging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="YJQH5z"&gt;Even when someone is working from home, it’s annoying to have a charging cable that’s too short. Most laptops and other devices come with cables that are barely long enough for many everyday situations. This lengthy USB-C cable from Uni gives much more flexibility for even larger laptops that require a lot of wattage. It supports 100W charging — which is enough to satisfy even the newest MacBook Pro models — and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B07LF1FNRV/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;it only costs $19.99 at Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, with frequent discounts dropping it to as low as $7. A cable may not sound like an exciting gift, but I’m sure your loved one will appreciate not being tethered so close to a wall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="KqySJW"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10322420"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="4JqysY"&gt;Rocketbook Core&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="ApMcuu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The perfect gift for the techie scribe in your life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gLsEWR"&gt;Notebooks — the old-school kind, not laptops — have largely taken a back seat to typing, voice dictation, and virtual assistants, but some people still prefer putting pen to actual paper. The Rocketbook Core offers the best of both worlds, though. It’s a reusable notebook that lets you write naturally on any of its 36 pages with the included pen, and you can easily scan the resulting text or drawings into your preferred notes app before wiping the pages clean with a cloth. Rocketbook’s retail price for the 6 x 8.8-inch notebook is $29.99, but you can almost always find it on &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Rocketbook-Innovative-Eco-Friendly-Digitally-Capabilities/dp/B06ZXWVZ3X?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;sale at Amazon for as low as $19.97&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="bkx5OT"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11750751"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="0I3Sq4"&gt;Besign LS10 Aluminum Laptop Stand&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="IWtPs7"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Give the gift of neck relief and better posture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="DBzjv3"&gt;If a friend or loved one cranes their neck when working from home on a laptop, they deserve some relief. Elevating a laptop to eye level is not only healthier for your posture, but it &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22832137/video-call-how-to-look-good-zoom-webex"&gt;makes you look better on video calls&lt;/a&gt;, too. The &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08BKVGY3S?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Besign LS10 laptop stand normally runs $24.99 on Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, but you can typically count on discounts bringing it down to around $20. It has an adjustable hinge design, so it sets up to the height you need and easily folds away when not in use. Plus, with a claimed weight capacity of 13 pounds, it’s strong enough to hold even some hefty full-size laptops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="CHjrGA"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11301607"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="9v5rpL"&gt;Oontz Solo&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="W9mkmd"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A small, affordable speaker that anyone can appreciate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="pudq9N"&gt;Almost everyone loves music, so a portable Bluetooth speaker can be a foolproof gift for someone in your life who is harder to shop for. The triangular Oontz Solo ($19.99 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DPVF8DQ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;) is the miniaturized sibling of the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B010OYASRG?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Angle&lt;/a&gt;, which has gained popularity as an inexpensive speaker that delivers solid tunes. The triangular design gives serious &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yZBVnjXp7GQ"&gt;Sabre Pyramid vibes&lt;/a&gt;, but unlike that chunky monstrosity, the Solo is just 3.9 inches long and weighs just under eight ounces. It retains IPX5 water resistance despite its small stature, making it suitable for some poolside fun, and the battery is rated to last up to 10 hours. It’s also available in several bold shades, including black, red, and blue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="7gjuBM"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12259888"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="HNYCrn"&gt;Apple EarPods&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="RQecaq"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Classic wired earbuds that they won’t feel bad about losing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="U33b1s"&gt;Believe it or not, some people aren’t caught up in the hullabaloo over wireless earbuds. Thankfully, Apple’s EarPods are a great wired alternative that do away with any concerns regarding battery life and connection quality. You can buy three different styles of EarPods corresponding to each major connector, including the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Apple-EarPods-3-5mm-Headphone-Plug/dp/B06X16Z7DZ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;traditional 3.5mm aux ($18.79)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Apple-EarPods-3-5mm-Headphone-Plug/dp/B0CHXC5ZDX?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;USB-C ($17.98)&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Apple-EarPods-3-5mm-Headphone-Plug/dp/B01M0GB8CC?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Lightning ($15.99)&lt;/a&gt;. Auxiliary is still the most common of these three across all manner of audio devices, but smartphone makers (Apple and Samsung, most notably) have been ditching 3.5mm ports, so it may be worth compensating by adding a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Apple-Lightning-Headphone-Jack-Adapter/dp/B01LXJFMGF?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;cheap $7.99 dongle&lt;/a&gt; to the gift bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="zuvc0t"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12016431"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="snIFXN"&gt;iFixit Moray Driver Kit&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="f5NpXU"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For the DIYers in your life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="e9ICnd"&gt;The iFixit Moray Driver Kit is a great gift for any handy person who likes to tinker. The little kit has a magnetized bit driver with a cleverly hidden SIM eject tool, and it connects to one of the included 32 screwdriver bits, which encompass everything from flathead and Phillips to torx, pentalobe, hex, and tri-point. There’s even an iPhone standoff bit for cleanly accessing internal logic boards. For $20 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/iFixit-Moray-Driver-Kit-Smartphones/dp/B08NWKMT8V?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ifixit.com%2Fproducts%2Fmoray-driver-kit&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23156368%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-25" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;direct from iFixit&lt;/a&gt;, you can equip your giftee with just about everything they need to make small repairs or carry out weekend projects (like replacing an aging battery in their phone).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="ORqkQy"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11729732"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="67krkQ"&gt;Black Diamond Astro 300 Headlamp&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="jzXWHd"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make sure your giftee doesn’t go bump in the night&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="JCxceF"&gt;The great age of engineering we’re enjoying lets us indulge our geeky side without sacrificing style, so the Black Diamond Astro 300 (&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09NQKNBC6?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$19.95 at Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.rei.com%2Fproduct%2F202772%2Fblack-diamond-astro-300-headlamp&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23156368%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-25" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;REI&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.blackdiamondequipment.com%2Fen_US%2Fproduct%2Fastro-300%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23156368%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-25" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Black Diamond&lt;/a&gt;) might give your recipient pause at first blush. The water-resistant headlamp is a safer pick if you know they’re into activities like hiking, but there are several other scenarios in which it might come in handy, like during blackouts or unforeseen night maintenance. At maximum brightness, the 300-lumen lamp is strong enough to provide light for up to 55 meters, and it draws that power from just three AAA batteries. (You can also buy an &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Black-Diamond-Equipment-Battery-Charger/dp/B09TNNDDF3?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;optional $29.95 rechargeable battery&lt;/a&gt; for added convenience).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="qlxI8v"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11140362"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="36q89c"&gt;Bluetooth Aux Receiver&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="m7mfeI"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Help someone with an older car feel a bit more modern&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="OlugPG"&gt;It’s well-established these days that cars are turning into tech appliances on wheels. To many folks, horsepower and drivetrain play second fiddle to Apple CarPlay and Android Auto. But for people still sticking to their older cars that lack all of these modern conveniences, a simple tool like a Bluetooth adapter can make all the difference in improving a commute or enjoying a lengthy road trip. This &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B09G97XMKR?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Bluetooth Aux Receiver that’s often on sale for just&lt;strong&gt; $16.99&lt;/strong&gt; at Amazon&lt;/a&gt; may look about as basic as they come, but it plugs into a 3.5mm aux jack and connects via Bluetooth 5.0 to up to two devices. It’s a simple, no-frills way to enjoy all your music and podcasts on the road as well as take hands-free phone calls for added safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="Jgb8Gi"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11174513"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="The Asicen retractable 3-in-1 charging cable plugged into a phone and laptop." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/HYZi4WVqRRSyA-kksMLa9Tpe0_w=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23649630/asicen_retractable_cable.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Asicen&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Asicen’s 3-in-1 charging cable is one of the handiest cables around, uniting iPhone and Android users with one multi-prong connector.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="0fvb95"&gt;Asicen 3-in-1 Retractable Charging Cable&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="p147Ed"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ve never had a more convenient cable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="O6HL9c"&gt;This gift idea is off the charts when it comes to the “I didn’t know I needed this, but now I can’t live without it” factor. These retractable 3-in-1 charging cables have Lightning, USB-C, and Micro USB connectors, allowing you to connect to just about any device in any location. They’re perfect for the car, especially if two or more people have to share a lone USB port for both Android Auto and Apple CarPlay duties. They also help keep your desk tidy if you only once in a while need to charge a wireless mouse or keyboard and want a cable at the ready. All that functionality starts at just &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Retractable-Multiple-Charging-Charger-Connector/dp/B07PFHBZ91?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$12.35&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;at Amazon for a pair with a five percent coupon. This gift idea is perfect for uniting any household divided between Apple fans and Android users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="koAmxe"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11174555"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="hRDh2l"&gt;Onn Google TV 4K Streaming Box&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="KU9TgI"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A great upgrade for someone who doesn’t have a smart TV&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1ddkpQ"&gt;If there’s someone in your life who needs rescuing from the scarcity of channels available over the air — or they simply have an older TV with outdated apps — try gifting them the &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2Fonn-Google-TV-4K-Streaming-Box-New-2023-4K-UHD-resolution%2F2835618394%2F&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Onn Google TV 4K Streaming Box ($19.88)&lt;/a&gt;. It provides the full Google TV experience, and it comes with 8GB of storage so you can install any of the free and premium streaming apps available (of which there are thousands). The included remote has a dedicated button for calling up Google Assistant, too, which makes it easy to find shows and movies using your voice. It also has Chromecast built in, so if you somehow can’t find what you want natively, you can always cast it from your phone. They’ll miss out on Dolby Vision and Dolby Atmos, but there’s still basic HDR support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="QeLTPU"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12248294"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="YtP2DP"&gt;Beam Electronics phone car mount&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="4uSy0B"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A phone is still better than most car head units out there&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="SPiMx8"&gt;Look, even with Apple CarPlay and Android Auto, most car head units still kinda suck. Having a phone mounted to the dashboard via an air vent is helpful for just about anyone. This basic car mount by Beam Electronics is easy to set up and simple to operate, and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Beam-Electronics-Smartphone-Car-Mount/dp/B073R68TSH?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;it costs just &lt;strong&gt;$19.99&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; at Amazon. Even if someone has a jumbo-sized phone, they can throw it on the cradle, clamp it in, and go. It won’t slide out of the holder even during some spirited driving, but it easily releases with the push of a button on the back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="659cVW"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11301629"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="bAqREk"&gt;KZ ES4 wired earbuds&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="t9XF87"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Give the gift of Luddism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="IViwl4"&gt;Yes, we live in the age of true wireless earbuds. But even an ultra-budget pair of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23130957/oneplus-nord-buds-budget-earbuds-review"&gt;OnePlus Nord Buds&lt;/a&gt; are still outside our range of $25. What &lt;em&gt;is &lt;/em&gt;in our range is the KZ ES4, which are currently &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Headphones-Yinyoo-Resolution-Comfortable-nomic/dp/B07D3QGXKQ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;on sale for just &lt;strong&gt;$20.99&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in blue, black, and green on Amazon. The 3.5mm wired earbuds have detachable cables and a see-through design that looks unique compared to just about any other earbuds out there. These are some excellent and interesting earbuds for the money and perfect for anyone who values spending quality time with their music without the bulk of big, expensive headphones. They make an appropriate gift for anyone who appreciates something with some quirky vibes, though be sure they have a phone that still has a headphone jack or that they’re still an &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/5/14/23071036/ipod-memories-20-years-discontinued-mini-shuffle-classic"&gt;iPod holdout&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="1GDQhR"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11024687"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="ZJY15f"&gt;JLab Go Air Pop&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="n060pR"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Okay, maybe you can get some wireless earbuds for under $25 that don’t suck&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gG8c7y"&gt;The platform-agnostic JLab Go Air Pop may offer the bare minimum when it comes to wireless earbuds, but you’d also be surprised how decent a $20 pair of wireless earbuds can sound. They’re a lot better than the AirPods knockoffs at your local dollar store, and you can often &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09HN594TL?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;get them on Amazon in various colors starting at just $19.99&lt;/a&gt;. Now, it may not be a great idea to gift these to someone who has their eyes set on a pair of AirPods or something with active noise cancellation, but their IPX4 water resistance and eight hours of battery life — or 32 hours with the included charging case — help make a compelling case. Even if they already own better earbuds, your recipient can tuck them away as an emergency backup pair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="SAUvtD"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11729693"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="1W3uhP"&gt;Apple AirTags or Tile Mate location trackers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="hWC5UL"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For the forgetful ones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RmPS1p"&gt;If someone you know is the type that might misplace their most valued everyday items, like their wallet or keys, a location tracker might just be a lifesaver for them. Now, there are some options to consider for this gift. Generally speaking, if they use an iPhone, then Apple’s AirTags are a great option, while the Tile Mate is a safe bet for both Android and iOS users. However, while the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Apple-MX532AM-A-AirTag/dp/B0933BVK6T/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;AirTags regularly dip under our budget price at $24, when on sale, they normally go for $29&lt;/a&gt;. The Tile Mate is the safer buy if you don’t know what phone your gift recipient uses, and it’s not uncommon to see them on sale for as low as $17.99 (normally $24.99) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Tile-Bluetooth-Battery-Water-Resistant-Compatible/dp/B09C29FR4G/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://shop-links.co/ciYXRrH1tjp" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://goto.target.com/c/482924/81938/2092?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.target.com%2Fp%2Ftile-mate-2022-white%2F-%2FA-82685355%23lnk%3Dsametab&amp;amp;subid1=vergeevergreenunder25giftguide" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Target&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="6oPd1N"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"AirTags are dangerous — here’s how Apple could fix them","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2022/3/1/22947917/airtags-privacy-security-stalking-solutions"},{"title":"How to track your luggage — or anything else — with AirTags ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23447275/how-to-track-luggage-airtags-apple-lost-bags"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="tBAHgD"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11283981"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="s1KT5k"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11292405"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="2Qgq4l"&gt;A $25 digital gift card for &lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=nOD/rLJHOac&amp;amp;mid=24542&amp;amp;u1=vergegiftsunder25&amp;amp;murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.microsoft.com%2Fen-us%2Fp%2Fxbox-gift-card-digital-code%2FCFQ7TTC0K63H%2F000K" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Xbox&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.playstation.com/en-us/playstation-gift-cards/" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;PlayStation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/digitalgiftcards/selectgiftcard" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Steam&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B01LYOCVZF/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;My Nintendo Shop&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="Tqx2MX"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Give the gift of some quality PC or console games&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5pv2Ax"&gt;We know gift cards often seem like the ultimate cop-out, but gifting digital games or smaller indie titles is not always easy. Yes, most digital game stores allow you to gift specific games to those on your friends list, but that’s only useful if you have an account and know which games they want. Enter the gift card, which lets them purchase what they want themselves. They’ll surely remember who helped finance their hundreds of hours of enjoyment to come. Bonus points if you &lt;em&gt;do &lt;/em&gt;know what game they want and you decorate a card or email message for them accordingly. Now that’s some expert-level gifting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="4YiggN"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11024379"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="4pduWL"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11301671"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="2BYoZ4"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11728148"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="g8uzKd"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11728158"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="D19UUA"&gt;8BitDo Bluetooth Retro Receiver&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="VrbmhJ"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For retro gamers who prefer the style and comfort of newer controllers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="vWPszn"&gt;The 8BitDo Bluetooth Retro Receiver might be the perfect gift if you know someone still sticking it out with the PlayStation 1 or PlayStation 2. On sale for &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CCYML6M8/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$23.75 at Amazon&lt;/a&gt; with a 5% coupon, the accessory connects to the controller port on either console and natively reads input from many compatible Bluetooth controllers, including most 8BitDo controllers, Sony’s DualShock and DualSense models, and newer Xbox wireless controllers. You can use it as a Bluetooth receiver for Windows PCs, too, thanks to a USB-C port. 8BitDo also offers similar products for the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Bluetooth-Compatible-Controller-Switch-Controllers-Nintendo/dp/B01K1T9CZS?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Super Nintendo&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/8Bitdo-Retro-Bluetooth-Receiver-Original-Genesis/dp/B07MSWGSJY?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Sega Genesis&lt;/a&gt;, but beware that those no longer support Xbox controllers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="uvRHey"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12151713"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="PKrOJ1"&gt;Samsung microSD card&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="ue8FMU"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perfect for expanding the storage of a Nintendo Switch or Steam Deck&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="43eXn0"&gt;If someone you know plays a lot of games on a Nintendo Switch or Steam Deck, a microSD card is a tiny gift that can make a huge difference. Many Samsung microSD cards go on sale frequently, and you can easily catch them on sale for under $25. Right now, for instance, you can nab a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0C1PT9XXS?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;128GB card at Amazon for $12.99&lt;/a&gt; or a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0C1PPWTWT?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;256GB card for $22.99&lt;/a&gt;, both of which can level up the amount of built-in storage found on Nintendo’s fancier Switch OLED and the base Steam Deck, allowing many more games to be installed at once — especially if you play lots of small indie titles. And don’t fret on the performance front; as our own &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/authors/sean-hollister" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Sean Hollister&lt;/a&gt; pointed out in his &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23513517/steam-deck-long-term-test-valve" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;re-review of the Steam Deck&lt;/a&gt;, there’s barely a noticeable difference in performance between playing games off your console’s internal storage and playing them off an optional microSD card (save for some slightly slower install times).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="hDKC7m"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11559040"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="ttRKLe"&gt;Joby GripTight One GorillaPod Stand&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="vs1e5P"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A simple tripod for phone photography and videos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8SR6oN"&gt;Sometimes planting your phone somewhere with a tripod is far superior for capturing a group selfie or a quality landscape photo. Fortunately, the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/GripTight-ONE-GorillaPod-Stand-Smartphones/dp/B01NGTBA3E?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Joby GripTight One is often on sale for around $20&lt;/a&gt; and comes with an adjustable clamp mount. It can even be used as a short selfie stick or simple stabilizer when taking video. It’s a great gift for anyone curious about doing more with their phone when it comes to taking pictures or just making things easier for recording TikTok videos while they talk to the camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="rNojsr"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11301750"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="DXoXNg"&gt;Elago Apple Watch stand&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="D4YE7S"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A charming little mount for your Apple Watch charger&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="6zwoNm"&gt;While there are many Apple Watch charging solutions out there, they’re usually a bit pricey and not at all cute. This Elago stand is absolutely adorable, as once you thread your Apple Watch charging puck into it, your watch turns into a mini Macintosh computer, iMac, GameBoy, or iPod Classic (okay, not really, but it &lt;em&gt;looks &lt;/em&gt;a bit like one while in nightstand mode). These little stands range from $12.99 to $15.99 on &lt;a href="https://www.elago.com/collections/watch-stand-f" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Elago’s site&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/elago-Nightstand-Original-Design-Pending/dp/B01MYNE2BM?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, and they make a charming novelty of a gift for anyone who loves some vintage tech nostalgia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="3GwcaG"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11301757"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="ZWvxJy"&gt;Anker 511 Charger (30W)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="GT3yID"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Save someone from their old 5W wall warts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="cYvCc7"&gt;Know someone who is still using a 5W USB-A charger that’s nearly old enough to get a learner’s permit? Here’s how you can help and be a considerate friend or family member who saves them from it. Anker’s 511 Chargers are incredibly tiny but output up to 30 watts for enough headroom to fast charge most phones — including the latest iPhone models. They cost just $22.99 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0B42T3Y48?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; (or less, given the frequent discounts they receive) and even come in some fun colors like green and lavender, in addition to white and black. Just be sure that any old chargers they replace get recycled properly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="pjB18m"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11064323"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="fWslvM"&gt;Nanoleaf Essentials Matter smart bulbs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="RuHfW1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart light bulbs: how most of us get into smart homes and automation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1yaC2B"&gt;Nanoleaf’s fun lighting panels are great for transforming a home office or chill space, but for more basic needs, the company’s Matter-over-Thread bulbs will do the job just fine. They’re $19.99 each at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Nanoleaf-Essentials-Smart-Thread-Bluetooth/dp/B0C1JBLYDZ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fnanoleaf.me%2Fen-US%2Fproducts%2Fessentials%2Fbulbs%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23156368%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-25" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Nanoleaf&lt;/a&gt;, and you can often find the A19 bulbs on sale for $14.99. They get nice and bright at 1,100 lumens, they allow for tons of scenes and settings, and you can easily choose from millions of vibrant colors. The Nanoleaf app required to manage them isn’t great, and the bulbs still suffer the same &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23997548/matter-smart-home-2023-platforms" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;growing pains as other Matter-ready devices&lt;/a&gt;, but Nanoleaf offers an affordable, manageable smart lighting platform that works great if your needs are simpler.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="JuQYFh"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11967087"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="TqB9X0"&gt;Meross Smart Wi-Fi Plug Mini (MSS110)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="aRKrxk"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Help someone dip their toes into smart home automation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="cIdMlD"&gt;The Meross Smart Wi-Fi Plug Mini (MSS110) — which is only $19 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Reliable-Support-HomeKit-Assistant-Control/dp/B084JML1WN?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; thanks to an on-page coupon — is our top budget recommendation when it comes to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23899810/best-smart-plugs" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;smart plugs&lt;/a&gt;. Just plug one in and set it up, and you’ll be able to remotely control whichever devices you plug into it. It’s compatible with Apple Home, Google Home, Amazon Alexa, and Samsung SmartThings, allowing you to schedule timers or control it with your voice using the smart platform you prefer. There’s no Matter support to help it communicate better with other smart home devices, but that’s a fair trade given its low price point.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="TjRncC"&gt;
&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12257853"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="mJQRiA"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Smart switches or smart bulbs? How to choose the right smart lighting for your home","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23156554/smart-bulbs-switch-lighting-guide-how-to"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="AP3JTA"&gt;Ugreen USB-C 6-in-1 Hub&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="wF2ojq"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All the ports&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="cnHRj3"&gt;Got a friend who is having a tough time in dongle town? This inexpensive &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/UGREEN-Adapter-MacBook-Chromebook-Aluminum/dp/B07RV1ZCWJ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;USB-C hub from Ugreen has most things covered, and it’s only $19.99&lt;/a&gt; on sale at Amazon. No matter if they need a USB 3.0 port or HDMI-out, it’s all here. There are even SD and microSD card slots, which you don’t always get with USB hubs at this price. It’s a great option for someone who owns a MacBook Air or another laptop that’s light on connectivity options, though advanced users may prefer a hub that has a passthrough USB-C charging port as well, which will cost more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mLqGvh"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11728206"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="lcJzFD"&gt;A desktop headphone stand or under-desk headphone mount&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="Rpd7ZH"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the over-under on a headphone fan loving this gift?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WNBlI8"&gt;We all love a great pair of noise-canceling headphones or a gaming headset, but even if they’re wireless, they certainly take up a lot of space. A headphone stand or mount is a great gift for anyone who spends a lot of time at their desk and wants to keep things tidy (or if you encourage them to keep things tidy and they really should be listening to you). Here are two appealing options for them to either show off their headphones when not using them or keep them tucked away and out of sight. The Neetto Dual Headphones Stand prominently displays two full-size headphones on a desk with a central tray for more organization, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07LGY5RSG?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;and it costs just &lt;strong&gt;$19.99&lt;/strong&gt; at Amazon&lt;/a&gt;. Another option is the Anchor Pro hanger (&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07F21RGT9?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$15.95 at Amazon&lt;/a&gt;), which can hold two pairs of headphones and uses 3M adhesive to easily attach it to the underside of your desk. Take your pick and help someone keep their cool audio gear neat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="EcMXjP"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The best noise-canceling headphones to buy right now","url":"https://www.theverge.com/21345733/best-noise-canceling-headphones"},{"title":"The best wired or wireless gaming headsets to buy","url":"https://www.theverge.com/21549510/best-gaming-headset-wired-wireless-features-specs-price-sound-microphone-test-buy"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="zgAkPJ"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11301860"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="Tu6dMY"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11301873"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="QCZuQe"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="newsletter" data-anthem-component-data='{"slug":"deals"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p id="0Ceoto"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update February 23rd, 5:30PM ET:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; We’ve updated this gift guide with several new picks and updated pricing for some of our favorites that are still available.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/23156368/best-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-25"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/23156368/best-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-25</id>
    <author>
      <name>Quentyn Kennemer</name>
      <name>Antonio G. Di Benedetto</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-13T10:30:32-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-13T10:30:32-05:00</updated>
    <title>The Verge’s 2024 Valentine’s Day gift guide </title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo collage of Apple AirPods and a Polaroid camera in two bright red heart-shaped lollipops." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/nT0CmmzsxSkOrP-vY-jsIcd-JCg=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73103497/246957_VDAY_GIFTGUIDE_CVirginia.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Cath Virginia / The Verge | Photos by Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;We’re here to help you save time with an assortment of unique gifts that are sweeter than any candy bar.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="hW0yQx"&gt;It’s all too easy to get caught up in our daily lives and forget to remind those we love just how much we care. And while Valentine’s Day can certainly be cringe, it also encourages us to do just that. After all, gifting a heartfelt present to your loved one can be one of the more thoughtful ways to show your appreciation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="BLv4i3"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Here are 22 last-minute gifts you can still grab ahead of Valentine’s Day","url":"https://www.theverge.com/24063707/valentines-day-gifts-best-last-minute-tech-digital-ideas-earbuds-streaming"},{"title":"The best tech gifts for under $50","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23161828/best-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="GXLn9F"&gt;Of course, we’re aware that finding the right gift can take time, which is why we’ve done the hard work for you. The creative minds at &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; gathered together to come up with a long list of Valentine’s Day gift ideas, all of which are more thoughtful than your generic teddy bear or box of chocolate. We’ve included a few sentimental picks — &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.etsy.com%2Flisting%2F975117613%2Fmemory-film-keychain-1-10-photos&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F24048257%2Fvalentines-day-2024-gift-ideas-boyfriend-girlfriend-couples-husband-wife-partner" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;personalized keychain, anyone?&lt;/a&gt; — as well as gadgets and goodies centered on &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Fitbit-Exercise-Equipment-6-Months-Membership/dp/B0CC62ZG1M/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;fitness&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1086940/Baldurs_Gate_3/"&gt;gaming&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00G2XGC88?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;cooking&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Buddha-Board-Mini-2-Inch-Black/dp/B000LUYQ22?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;art&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Kindle-Scribe-the-first-Kindle-for-reading-writing-journaling-and-sketching/dp/B09BS26B8B?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;literature&lt;/a&gt;. Hopefully, you’ll find something special for everybody on your list — whether it’s your partner, friend, parent, child, or someone else close to your heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="hj9Jgm"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12230899"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="7eX4bc"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24048257/valentines-day-2024-gift-ideas-boyfriend-girlfriend-couples-husband-wife-partner"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24048257/valentines-day-2024-gift-ideas-boyfriend-girlfriend-couples-husband-wife-partner</id>
    <author>
      <name>Verge Staff</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-26T11:29:58-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-26T11:29:58-05:00</updated>
    <title>The best tech gifts for under $50</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Twinkly Candies strung up behind a TV radiating colorful lights" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/8ar84NW_-lhcgMC9B32mijpuwLk=/0x209:1318x1088/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/71987547/twinkycandies.15.png" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Twinkly’s smart string lights can make any room look dreamy for less than $50.&lt;/em&gt; | Image: Twinkly&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="ev25qd"&gt;If “budget-friendly” and “high-quality” sound like oxymorons to you, you’re in for a surprise. As it turns out, you&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;can buy many great gifts without completely draining your savings account, which makes it easy to pick up a present for your anniversary, a birthday party, or one of the many other gift-giving occasions strewn throughout the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="UhsGAe"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The best tech gifts for under $25","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23156368/best-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-25"},{"title":"Cheap stuff that doesn’t suck","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23837448/cheap-gadgets-tools-tech-accessories-wearables"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="UgPPeK"&gt;Finding the right gift can still be tough, though, even when there is a sea of inexpensive items for under $50 to choose from. That’s why we’ve put together a selection of techy gift ideas, ranging from &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhphotovideo.com%2Fc%2Fproduct%2F1626075-REG%2Fkodak_da00239_m35_35mm_camera_with.html&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;disposable cameras&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Skullcandy-True-Wireless-Ear-Earbuds/dp/B09VM2TBZF?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;wireless earbuds&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Blink-Mini-White-1Cam/dp/B07X6C9RMF/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;home security gadgets&lt;/a&gt;. We’ve also highlighted an array of last-minute gifts that are more unique than your run-of-the-mill gift card — including &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdkeys.com%2Fxbox-live%2F3-month-xbox-game-pass-ultimate-xbox-one-pc&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;game passes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/hz/audible/mlp/membership/premiumplus/monthly?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;audiobook subscriptions&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="M5POLB"&gt;Take a look, and see how many fun gifts you can buy for very little.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="rQutFJ"&gt;Twinkly Candies&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="r7qih1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twinkly’s magical string lights are perfect for any occasion &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HPv0Ne"&gt;Twinkly’s USB-C string lights can add a touch of magic to any living space. The colorful smart lights feature LEDs you can control individually, allowing you to create some gorgeous, customizable visual effects. They also support Amazon Alexa and Google Assistant,  sync with music, and offer all sorts of scenes, making them a fun present for kids or adults looking to set the mood on date night. They come in a variety of shapes as well — including stars, hearts, pearls, and candles — which makes them a great piece of decor for Valentine’s Day, Christmas, Independence Day, and all kinds of special occasions. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="j2MyFd"&gt;Right now, you can buy Twinkly’s 100-LED string lights for $37.49 (about $13 off) directly from &lt;a href="https://twinkly.com/en-us/products/candies-stars"&gt;Twinkly&lt;/a&gt;. They’re also available at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Twinkly-Pearl-String-spacing-Transparent/dp/B0BV2HPTLM?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; for $44.99 ($5 off) or at &lt;a href="https://howl.me/cluPI5iMCCs"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt; for their full retail price.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="YV1biO"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12233007"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="sM2BIf"&gt;Echo Dot (fifth-gen)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="vit3A8"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An all-in-one smart speaker and virtual assistant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="I6u6lI"&gt;In a way, gifting &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23426830/echo-dot-with-clock-2022-fifth-gen-review"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon’s fifth-gen Echo Dot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;is like gifting multiple items at once. The spherical device makes for a great-sounding speaker, one that can fill a room surprisingly well despite its small footprint. At the same time, the latest model doubles as an Eero mesh Wi-Fi extender and a virtual assistant your loved ones can use to set alarms, check the weather, and control other smart home devices. Right now, you can pick up the fifth-gen smart speaker for $49.99 (its full retail price) at  &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09B8V1LZ3/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://howl.me/cluWi7N2yHA"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://homedepot.sjv.io/c/482924/456723/8154?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.homedepot.com%2Fp%2FAmazon-Echo-Dot-5th-Gen-2022-Release-Smart-Speaker-with-Alexa-Charcoal-B09B8V1LZ3%2F323260667&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;The Home Depot&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="RoKKgd"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23426830/echo-dot-with-clock-2022-fifth-gen-review"&gt;Read our Echo Dot (fifth-gen) review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id="JfAtzN"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11769105"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="title"&gt;Amazfit Band 7 &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="gjVMio"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A feature-rich fitness tracker that offers a lot of bang for your buck&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1jRVaU"&gt;You don’t have to fork out hundreds of dollars on the latest Fitbit or Apple Watch just to get a good fitness tracker. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23652417/amazfit-band-7-review-budget-fitness-tracker"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazfit’s Band 7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;is a good budget-friendly alternative, one that offers a lot of value for the price. Not only does it accurately track all your basic health metrics, but it also boasts abnormal heart rate notifications, stress tracking, and other features typically reserved for more expensive trackers. The comfy wearable also offers other perks that are rare at this price point, including support for Amazon Alexa, an OLED display, and a staggering 18 days of battery life. You can buy it for $44.99 ($5 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Amazfit-Fitness-Tracker-Monitoring-Resistant/dp/B09Z6CRHJ6?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/cjzVM4vDBEy?u1=vergedeals080323"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, or for $49.99 at &lt;a href="https://goto.target.com/c/482924/81938/2092?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.target.com%2Fp%2Famazfit-band-7-smartwatch-black%2F-%2FA-87154319&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Target&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="lwuIAo"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23652417/amazfit-band-7-review-budget-fitness-tracker"&gt;Read our Amazfit Band 7 review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id="QwSkRo"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11861731"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="GcfGYd"&gt;Skullcandy Jib True 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="hbL8Q8"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A pair of wireless earbuds that integrate with Tile&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="DBPvzz"&gt;A great pair of wireless earbuds are the perfect gift for music lovers, and &lt;strong&gt;Skullcandy’s newer Jib True 2 &lt;/strong&gt;boast a nice combination of features for the price. Both earbuds work independently and feature a surprising amount of passive noise cancellation along with an IPX4 water resistance rating that helps ensure they can withstand a jaunt at the gym or the occasional downpour. Each earbud also features integrated Tile tracking, which allows you to locate the earbuds via the Tile app on your phone if you happen to misplace them. Regularly $39.99, right now you can buy the Jib True 2 in several colors at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Skullcandy-True-Wireless-Ear-Earbuds/dp/B09VM2TBZF?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; starting at $28.17. You can also buy them for their full retail price from &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.skullcandy.com%2Fjib-true-2-wireless-earbuds%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Skullcandy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="x6J9k3"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11737065"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="IfkbJ7"&gt;Side By Side Premium Pouch Organizer&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="XW18Cb"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A spacious organizer for all your gadget needs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="yaHLNe"&gt;A bag for keeping cords organized is a helpful gift for any gadget lover who is often on the go. &lt;strong&gt;Side By Side’s slim, padded offering&lt;/strong&gt; is easy to stow in a larger bag or backpack, yet it’s spacious enough to fit everything from extension cords and power bricks to earbuds, microSD cards, and a range of assorted adapters. It’s currently available at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B07C52NLJR/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; for $35.95 ($5 off) when you clip the on-page coupon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="PAfUGp"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11993425"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="VFyI5o"&gt;Chromecast with Google TV (4K)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="ROGi9N"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A streaming device that’s loaded with Rotten Tomatoes ratings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3Yamdg"&gt;A streaming device like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/21495609/google-chromecast-2020-review-streaming-remote-control"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google’s excellent Chromecast with Google TV (4K)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a welcome present, no matter the occasion. That’s because it grants your giftee access to every major streaming service while offering support for Dolby Atmos, Dolby Vision, and a wide array of apps. Unlike its rivals, however, the gadget also curates recommendations from a variety of streaming services and provides Rotten Tomatoes scores, helping your loved one quickly find something worthwhile to binge-watch. You currently can buy Google’s 4K-ready Chromecast for $49.99 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Google-Nest-GA01919-GA01919-US-Chromecast/dp/B08KRV7S22?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://howl.me/ckipkgocIW9?u1=vergedeals080323"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://store.google.com/us/config/chromecast_google_tv?hl=en-US"&gt;Google’s online storefront&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="BYWrZk"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/21495609/google-chromecast-2020-review-streaming-remote-control"&gt;Read our Chromecast with Google TV (4K) review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id="cmwP9K"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11284196"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Google Chromecast with remote" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/yYId8H1rcUOtJXTihIXBFayx0oA=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/21924713/DSCF2108.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo: Chris Welch / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Chromecast with Google TV (4K) is among our favorite streaming devices, one that comes bundled with a remote.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="w4uuoP"&gt;Logitech K380 Bluetooth Keyboard&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="9tMwk4"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A keyboard they can use to type on their tablet or phone&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="f8H4E8"&gt;Does your giftee often type on their tablet or (like me) send texts littered with typos because their smartphone screen is too small? Then &lt;strong&gt;Logitech’s K380 Bluetooth Keyboard&lt;/strong&gt; is a useful gift they’ll forever be grateful for. The compact, wireless keyboard can switch between up to three devices at a time and offers a broad range of compatibility, allowing for a more comfortable typing experience whether you use an Apple operating system, Windows, Android, or ChromeOS. It’s currently available for $39.99 from &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0B8M9NM56/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://imp.i140643.net/c/482924/546180/9160?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.logitech.com%2Fen-us%2Fproducts%2Fkeyboards%2Fk380-multi-device.920-007558.html&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Logitech&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="r99Ttv"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11861737"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="u3wUN8"&gt;Kodak M35 35mm film camera&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="EaOXwK"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A “disposable” camera that’s reusable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="s8YXEv"&gt;There’s something charming about low-tech gadgets like disposable cameras. &lt;strong&gt;Kodak’s pocket-size M35&lt;/strong&gt; offers all of the charms single-use cameras do except for one thing: it can&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;be reused again and again with 35mm rolls of film. The M35 serves as a nice introduction to analog photography and is a creative present your giftee will love, especially if they’re the nostalgic, sentimental sort. It typically retails for around $28, but you can currently &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhphotovideo.com%2Fc%2Fproduct%2F1626075-REG%2Fkodak_da00239_m35_35mm_camera_with.html&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;buy it at B&amp;amp;H Photo for $22.49&lt;/a&gt;. You can also get it starting at around the same price at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09DYJ6DZW/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; from a third-party seller, though it still ships via Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="kq26j5"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11743847"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="5FXX0u"&gt;Original Tamagotchi &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="dAx3P3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A tiny, virtual pet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="UPB4av"&gt;Speaking of old-school gadgets, the &lt;strong&gt;Original Tamagotchi &lt;/strong&gt;makes for another great gift. The popular ’90s toy has made a comeback in recent years, but this time around, it comes in more designs and an assortment of fun colors, ranging from blue to tie-dye. As a quick refresher, the Tamagotchi is a virtual pet you raise like a child in a tiny device, one you can attach to your bags or a keychain. It makes for a fun gift for kids but also one for older millennials who still yearn for the good ol’ days. Right now, you can buy a wide range of models for around $19 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B09ZH3NSLG?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/cluU5OTLeyc"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="zZ6afJ"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11853646"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="NP0u5E"&gt;An Xbox, PlayStation, or Nintendo Switch gaming subscription &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="XYG8dq"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because why gift one game when you can gift hundreds?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="k3djbR"&gt;Sure, you could gift the gamer in your life a game for under $50, but a pass to one of the more prominent gaming subscriptions offers a lot more value for your money. &lt;strong&gt;Xbox Game Pass Ultimate&lt;/strong&gt; grants you access to exclusive discounts, online multiplayer, and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/25/23999612/xbox-games-game-pass-2023-best-roundup"&gt;more than 100 games&lt;/a&gt; for PC and Xbox consoles, ranging from older titles like &lt;em&gt;Doom&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23833189/starfield-news-announcements-trailers-microsoft-bethesda-xbox-pc"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Starfield&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23864117/sea-of-stars-review-rpg"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sea of Stars&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. A &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07TFP7JFH?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;one-month digital subscription typically costs $15.99&lt;/a&gt;, though you can currently buy a three-month pass for &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdkeys.com%2Fxbox-live%2F3-month-xbox-game-pass-ultimate-xbox-one-pc&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$31.69 from CDKeys&lt;/a&gt;. You can also buy it for $44.99 ($5 off)  at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Xbox-Game-Pass-Ultimate-Membership/dp/B07TGNFVWV?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="BtSgBW"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11289044"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="vnFb9H"&gt;Alternatively, you could gift a subscription to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/6/13/23166206/sony-new-playstation-plus-tiers-essential-extra-premium-live-us"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PlayStation Plus Essential&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; if their primary console is a PlayStation 4 or PS5. Every month, they’ll be able to download free PlayStation titles while enjoying access to online multiplayer, exclusive discounts, and 100GB of cloud storage for saved games. PlayStation Plus Essential costs &lt;a href="https://www.playstation.com/en-us/ps-plus/#subscriptions"&gt;$9.99 a month&lt;/a&gt;, though you can currently pick up a three-month subscription for $24.99 from &lt;a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/IP9101-PPSA06916_00-PLUS1T03M0000000/"&gt;PlayStation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="Ltzv5H"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11736996"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="W1PKbn"&gt;Finally, for gamers who prefer playing on the Nintendo Switch, there’s the &lt;strong&gt;Nintendo Switch Online membership&lt;/strong&gt;. The digital subscription grants members access to over 70 titles from Nintendo’s catalog of classic NES and SNES games. That’s in addition to letting subscribers play online with friends and the ability to back up game data online. You can buy a one-year subscription for $19.99 from &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07FV64QLX/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://howl.me/ckippXwZ6Cx?u1=vergedeals080323"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=nOD%2FrLJHOac&amp;amp;mid=24348&amp;amp;u1=verge&amp;amp;murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gamestop.com%2Fgift-cards%2Fdigital-subscriptions%2Fproducts%2Fnintendo-switch-online-12-month-individual-membership%2F176406.html" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;GameStop&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="p3HyTe"&gt;If you don’t mind forking out extra, there’s also the &lt;strong&gt;Nintendo Switch Online + Expansion Pack&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;which costs $49.99 per year. It offers the same benefits as the Nintendo Switch Online membership but also grants access to Game Boy Advance, Sega Genesis, and Nintendo 64 titles, not to mention DLC content for select games (including &lt;em&gt;Mario Kart 8 Deluxe &lt;/em&gt;and &lt;em&gt;Animal Crossing: New Horizons&lt;/em&gt;). Right now, you can pick up a subscription from &lt;a href="https://ec.nintendo.com/US/en/membership/"&gt;Nintendo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Nintendo-Expansion-12-month-Individual-Membership/dp/B09WJY877B?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://shop-links.co/ci9wkiuEsjD" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="LytfKt"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11290059"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="2As6lM"&gt;Anker 313 Magnetic Wireless Charger&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="gZIw9f"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A MagSafe-ready charger that’s cheaper than Apple’s official puck&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WdNfem"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anker’s 313 Magnetic Wireless Charger&lt;/strong&gt; is one of our favorite &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23505846/best-magsafe-magnetic-chargers-apple-iphone" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;magnetic chargers and a useful gift&lt;/a&gt; to buy if your loved one uses an iPhone. It’s tiny and lightweight, so they can easily throw it in their bag while on the go, and it comes bundled with a five-foot USB-C cable. It also charges up to 7.5 watts, which is enough to fully juice a phone overnight or give it a quick top-up while out and about. Normally $25.99, right now it’s available for $19.99 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Anker-Magnetic-Wireless-Charger-PowerWave/dp/B095NQTNLZ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=nOD%2FrLJHOac&amp;amp;mid=44583&amp;amp;u1=verge&amp;amp;murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.newegg.com%2Fanker-5-feet-wireless-charger%2Fp%2F359-00D8-00281" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Newegg&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="LI1M3I"&gt;Alternatively, if your loved one owns an Android phone, there’s &lt;strong&gt;Belkin’s BoostCharge Wireless Charging Stand&lt;/strong&gt;. It’s capable of providing Qi-enabled devices with up to 10 watts of power but also doubles as a stand, allowing your giftee to view notifications with ease. You can currently buy it for $34.99 at &lt;a href="https://howl.me/ckiprBduJcS?u1=vergedeals080323" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.belkin.com%2Fwireless-charging-stand-10w%2FP-WIB001.html&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;direct from Belkin&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="GfYsye"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11737025"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="APsLTG"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11750890"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="h9eFja"&gt;Tecware Phantom L&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="sCzDgW"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A colorful mechanical keyboard that offers a lot of features for the price&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="258QPz"&gt;If you want to level up your gaming setup or add some fun to your typing experience,  the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23034287/best-mechanical-gaming-keyboards" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tecware Phantom L&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; can help you do just that. The budget-friendly, low-profile tenkeyless gaming keyboard features some nice perks for the price, including adjustable per-key RGB lighting. You can also buy it with linear, tactile, or clicky switches, and the keyboard even comes with a hot-swappable printed circuit board. Granted, it’s only compatible with Outemu low-profile switches and it’s not as easy to swap out as higher-end models, but that’s still a nice perk for the price. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uOdN2s"&gt;Normally $49.99, right now you can buy the Tecware Phantom L for just $27 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Tecware-Phantom-Profile-Mechanical-Keyboard/dp/B0856W4MSR?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon &lt;/a&gt;when you clip the on-page coupon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="7iPUwD"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12233291"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="hAaboc"&gt;Chipofy USB-C Cable&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="7QcvUV"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A powerful charging cable with its own wattage display&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="yuMDNV"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/1/28/22907150/usb-c-pd-cable-power-meter-100-watt-power-delivery" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chipofy’s USB-C charging cable&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a quirky charging accessory that gadget lovers will particularly appreciate. Unlike most cables, Chipofy’s 6.6-foot offering comes with a built-in LED display that allows you to keep tabs on just how quickly you’re charging your devices. What’s more, the 100W cable is powerful enough to juice laptops, as well as smartphones, gaming consoles like the Nintendo Switch, and even drones. Right now, you can buy the cable for $16.19 instead of $17.99 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09KLYBS5H/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; thanks to an on-page coupon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="8dOXqw"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/1/28/22907150/usb-c-pd-cable-power-meter-100-watt-power-delivery" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Read our hands-on impressions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id="sieGTK"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11320228"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="aPQ82n"&gt;Case-Mate 30W Fuel USB-C Charger&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="ADvSoe"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A fun-yet-fast USB-C charger&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="MhPzAA"&gt;Okay, one more charger, we swear. If you want to gift something that’s a little more playful, there’s Case-Mate’s Fuel USB-C Charger. With its translucent shell, it looks a little like an old-school iMac from the ’90s, especially since it comes in blue, orange, and a variety of vibrant colors. It’s more than just pretty, though. The portable, single-port charger is capable of delivering 30 watts of power, so your giftee will be able to quickly charge their smartphone, tablet, or a handheld console like the Nintendo Switch. At the moment, you can buy the charger for $30 from &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fcase-mate.com%2Fproducts%2Ffuel-30w-usb-c-wall-charger-electric-blue&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Case-Mate&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://goto.target.com/c/482924/81938/2092?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.target.com%2Fp%2Ffuel-brites-30w-usb-c-pd-compact-gan-power-adapter-vibrant-orange%2F-%2FA-87659145&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Target&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="sE3blb"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11861741"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="WdxBJv"&gt;JBL Go 3&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="VyUVYa"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A tiny waterproof speaker that’s perfect for blasting music at the beach (or in the shower)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="IXoEGo"&gt;If your giftee is an avid beachgoer or someone who is always on the move, the &lt;strong&gt;JBL Go 3 &lt;/strong&gt;is worth considering. The waterproof Bluetooth speaker is tiny enough that you can easily slip it into your backpack or pocket before heading out the door, and it comes with a loop that allows you to quickly attach it to a bag. Plus, it offers up to 10 hours of battery life on a single charge and comes in a vibrant red colorway, camo, and a variety of other fun hues that should stand out no matter where you set it. The JBL Go 3 is available for around $49.95 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/JBL-Bluetooth-Built-Waterproof-Dustproof/dp/B08LC4JWJ9/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/cluW4owqVjS" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="VpNACk"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11749272"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="BRDfkH"&gt;Apple AirTag / Tile Pro&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="z0n8bW"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A location tracker so they can speed through baggage claim faster&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8CrDuK"&gt;Whether your loved one is a frequent traveler or just the forgetful sort, they’ll appreciate a Bluetooth tracker. It’ll help them keep tabs on everything from keys to suitcases, allowing them to spot luggage and leave baggage claim a lot faster. Both an &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/22/22396693/apple-airtag-location-tracker-hands-on-find-my-privacy-safety" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AirTag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/10/12/22716868/tile-mate-pro-slim-sticker-trackers-update-range-volume-water-resistance" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tile Pro&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are good options; however, Apple’s location tracker may be better for those deeply embedded in Apple’s ecosystem, given how well it pairs with the iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="a0Gi1l"&gt;Right now, you can buy an AirTag for $27.99 ($2 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Apple-MX532AM-A-AirTag/dp/B0933BVK6T?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FApple-AirTag%2F475634131&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart&lt;/a&gt;, or for its full retail price at &lt;a href="https://howl.me/ckipu43KQwq?u1=vergedeals080323" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;. Keep in mind, however, that your giftee will need to spend extra on an AirTag loop if they want to attach it to their keys or bag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gdN62k"&gt;Alternatively, if you have no idea what type of phone your giftee uses, it may be a better idea to pick up a Tile Pro. It performs many of the same functions and comes with user-replaceable batteries, but unlike AirTags, it works with both Android and iOS. Right now, you can buy the latest model for $30.99 ($4 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Tile-Powerful-Bluetooth-Water-Resistant-Compatible/dp/B09B2WLRWX?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/ckh7usavjJE?u1=vergedeals080323" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;. It’s also available for its full retail price from &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.tile.com%2Fproduct%2Fblack-pro&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Tile&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="0Gdehb"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/22/22396693/apple-airtag-location-tracker-hands-on-find-my-privacy-safety" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Read our AirTag review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id="gHruyr"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11744003"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="rb5QM1"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11993372"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="AirTags" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/qPeprEY3uZnYIrPxafC5-14_lS8=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/22461387/vpavic_4547_20210421_0074.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo: Vjeran Pavic / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;AirTags can help your loved ones easily keep track of their belongings — no matter where they are.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="qn5kh4"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The best Bluetooth speakers to buy right now","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23022617/best-bluetooth-speakers"},{"title":"The best Nintendo Switch controllers to buy right now","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23350899/nintendo-switch-controllers-best-wireless-joy-con-gamepad"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="rilePL"&gt;8BitDo Pro 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="UVa2Ne"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A terrific Nintendo Switch controller that works with other devices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ntWqGm"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8BitDo’s Pro 2&lt;/strong&gt; is an excellent Nintendo Switch controller, one your giftee can also connect to their PC or smartphone via Bluetooth. The Pro-like controller makes gaming just a little more fun and comfortable thanks to features like hand grips, which is something even Nintendo’s more expensive Pro Controller lacks. While it doesn’t offer support for Nintendo’s HD rumble or Amiibos, it does provide a handful of other useful features, including customizable back paddles and relatively fast charging thanks to USB-C. You can currently buy it for $49.99 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/8Bitdo-Bluetooth-Controller-Android-Raspberry-Classic/dp/B08XY86472?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/ckipw3yznDg?u1=vergedeals080323" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="uY1J7Y"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22364301/8bitdo-pro-2-controller-review-switch-back-buttons" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Read our 8BitDo Pro 2 review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id="AA28vi"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11749263"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="whFAak"&gt;Nanoleaf Essentials Matter smart bulb&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="5N0sa1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A smart bulb so they don’t have to pause their movie to turn off the light&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hZnAlq"&gt;When you’re curled up on the couch watching a movie, the last thing you want to do is get up and turn off the light. With a&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23706841/nanoleaf-essentials-matter-smart-bulbs-review" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nanoleaf Essentials Matter smart bulb&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, however, your loved ones won’t have to. The Bluetooth-enabled smart bulbs support Matter and Thread, rendering them compatible with a wide range of smart home platforms, so all they need to do is use their voice to turn the lights off. When they do want them on, the 1,100-lumen bulbs will brighten up their home with an array of colorful lighting. Right now, you can buy a single bulb for $14.99 ($5 off) from &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Nanoleaf-Essentials-Smart-Thread-Bluetooth/dp/B0C1JBLYDZ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fnanoleaf.me%2Fen-US%2Fproducts%2Fessentials%2Fbulbs%2F%3Fcategory%3DA19-E26%26standard%3Dmatter%26size%3Deach&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Nanoleaf&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="xWB8gi"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23706841/nanoleaf-essentials-matter-smart-bulbs-review" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Read our Nanoleaf Essentials Matter smart bulb review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id="jKvUDe"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11967087"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="Bh0V1z"&gt;Kasa smart plugs &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="UcBFoe"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A plug that can smarten up the devices in your home&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="FTm7i8"&gt;Speaking of turning the lights on with just your voice, &lt;strong&gt;TP-Link’s Kasa smart plugs&lt;/strong&gt; can transform traditional gadgets into smart ones. As a result, your giftee can use their voice to control a wide range of devices, including lamps, fans, and humidifiers. They don’t need to be home to do so, either, since you can set them on a schedule and control them using Kasa’s mobile app for Android and iOS. They’re also compatible with both Amazon Alexa and Google Assistant. Right now, you can buy a four-pack of the hub-less smart plugs for $28.99 ($1 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/TP-Link-Kasa-Smart-Wifi-Plug/dp/B07RCNB2L3/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhphotovideo.com%2Fc%2Fproduct%2F1598882-REG%2Ftp_link_hs103p4_kasa_smart_plug_4_pack.html&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;B&amp;amp;H Photo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="RQBmby"&gt;
&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11749325"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="LXblPn"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Smart switches or smart bulbs? How to choose the right smart lighting for your home","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23156554/smart-bulbs-switch-lighting-guide-how-to"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="jaSNqZ"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="actionbox" data-anthem-component-data='{"title":"Verge Deals on Twitter","description":"Join more than 50,000 followers and keep up with the best daily tech deals with @vergedeals","label":"Follow us!","url":"http://bit.ly/2JzR5Ud"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;h2 id="8awfDA"&gt;Blink Mini indoor security camera&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="3VPM92"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A camera designed to keep an eye on your home when you’re away&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="9ZmWu7"&gt;Speaking of keeping your belongings safe, Blink’s indoor security camera is another gadget that can help put your giftee’s mind at ease. A &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/4/28/21231112/blink-mini-smart-home-camera-security-cam-review" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blink Mini&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; allows your loved one to keep an eye on their home while they’re away and even receive alerts when activity is detected in preselected areas. The wired 1080p camera also allows for two-way audio chat, making it a good option for those who want to keep tabs on their dog or a kid from another room in their home. The Alexa-equipped camera is currently on sale for just $29.99 ($5 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Blink-Mini-White-1Cam/dp/B07X6C9RMF/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://howl.me/ckipz6KF7Ny?u1=vergedeals080323" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://homedepot.sjv.io/c/482924/456723/8154?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.homedepot.com%2Fp%2FBlink-Mini-Indoor-Wired-1080p-Wi-Fi-Security-Camera-in-White-B07X6C9RMF%2F313600685&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;The Home Depot&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="2kaWE6"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/4/28/21231112/blink-mini-smart-home-camera-security-cam-review" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Read our Blink Mini review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id="AX4HZl"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11748964"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="FmuhAN"&gt;An Audible Premium Plus or Kindle Unlimited subscription&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="R8JFAw"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A subscription fit for even the pickiest of bibliophiles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ryVQZI"&gt;Gifting a bookworm something that grants them access to thousands of books is obviously a good idea. A &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/kindle-dbs/hz/subscribe/ku/promotions?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kindle Unlimited subscription&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;costs $11.99 a month and provides access to more than 3 million digital titles, including bestsellers and classics. Alternatively, if your loved one is more into audiobooks than traditional reading, you can gift them a $14.95-a-month &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/hz/audible/mlp/membership/premiumplus/monthly?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audible Premium Plus subscription&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. That way, they’ll be able to enjoy thousands of audiobooks and podcasts as well as one premium audiobook every month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="k98Nyk"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11178510"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="pjhsRu"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11743830"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="qn8Jhb"&gt;Rocketbook Core&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="bPN01z"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A reusable notebook to save them money on paper&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lqFsnM"&gt;If your giftee takes a lot of notes for school or work, Rocketbook’s smart notebooks will surely come in handy. The notebooks are erasable and, thus, reusable, so they don’t have to keep buying (and wasting) paper. Plus, they can use Rocketbook’s companion app to store their notes in all the major cloud-based services, including Google Drive, Slack, and iCloud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xToGLu"&gt;Rocketbook notebooks come with your choice of lined or dot grid paper, or with calendars and other preexisting templates. Right now, for instance, you can buy the 8.5-by-11-inch &lt;strong&gt;Rocketbook Core &lt;/strong&gt;with dot grid pages, a microfiber cloth, and a Pilot Frixion erasable pen for $22.97 ($10 off) at &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FRocketbook-Core-Smart-Spiral-Notebook-Dot-Grid-and-Lined-Pages-32-Pages-8-5-x-11-Black%2F868169745&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart&lt;/a&gt; or for $23.99 at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07ZHZ9VK4?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;. You can also buy it directly from &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fgetrocketbook.com%2Fproducts%2Frocketbook-core&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Rocketbook for $36.99&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="CJPXlp"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11750751"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="7Ovioa"&gt;Razer DeathAdder V2 Mini&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="sR9LbQ"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A mouse that makes gaming (and working) more comfortable &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7H0rty"&gt;If your giftee uses a PC, &lt;strong&gt;Razer’s DeathAdder V2 Mini&lt;/strong&gt; can make gaming (and working) more enjoyable. The wired mouse is the smaller version of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/21252193/best-gaming-mouse" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;one of our favorite models&lt;/a&gt;, which we praised for being exceptionally comfortable and supportive. It shares a similar design with an 8,500 DPI sensor and a relatively straightforward button layout; however, the lightweight gaming mouse only features a single button for switching the DPI as opposed to two. The Mini is currently available for $49.99 from &lt;a href="https://razer.a9yw.net/c/482924/642901/10229?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.razer.com%2Fgaming-mice%2Frazer-deathadder-v2-mini%2FRZ01-03340100-R3U1&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Razer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="I3XdeN"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11559056"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="LCqTa4"&gt;A gift card for Netflix or Disney Plus&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="YHzstl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A gift card that opens the door to endless entertainment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="jFc5jB"&gt;You can’t go wrong with a gift card for one of the major streaming services, which can be used to binge countless hours of entertainment. The most notable is &lt;strong&gt;Netflix&lt;/strong&gt;, which grants access to popular shows and movies like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23971416/squid-game-the-challenge-review-netflix" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Squid Game: The Challenge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Fool Me Once&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23776783/witcher-season-3-volume-1-review-netflix" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Witcher&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;The Crown&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23067333/stranger-things-4-review" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Stranger Things&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; starting at $6.99 a month. Right now, you can buy a digital Netflix gift card at &lt;a href="https://howl.me/ckipDyLWuSc?u1=vergedeals080323" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Netflix-1_NETFLIX_standard-Email-Delivery/dp/B078J21W75/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=nOD%2FrLJHOac&amp;amp;mid=24348&amp;amp;u1=verge&amp;amp;murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gamestop.com%2Fgift-cards%2Fgaming-gift-cards%2Fproducts%2Fnetflix-30%2F146538.html" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;GameStop&lt;/a&gt; or order a physical gift card from &lt;a href="https://howl.me/ckipEjCUm5r?u1=vergedeals080323" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="bqQmMC"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11285519"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="98bFZG"&gt;Alternatively, you can gift multiple streaming services in the form of a &lt;strong&gt;Disney Bundle &lt;/strong&gt;subscription. The three-in-one package caters to a wide range of interests, from family-friendly content like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23620519/the-mandalorian-season-3-premiere-the-apostate" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Mandalorian&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;to sports, as it includes Disney Plus, Hulu, and ESPN Plus. The ad-supported plan starts at $14.99 a month, and you can subscribe &lt;a href="https://disneyplus.bn5x.net/c/482924/564546/9358?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.disneyplus.com%2Fwelcome%2Fdisney-hulu-espn-bundle&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="9tlPy1"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11738755"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="adWIIc"&gt;ElevationLab’s under-desk headphone mount&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="N4KY7x"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A dual hanger that declutters your desk quickly and easily&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RB4xFM"&gt;Noise-canceling headphones can help you focus while working, but their sheer size can clutter your desk and make it harder to concentrate when you’re not using them. &lt;strong&gt;ElevationLab’s Anchor Pro&lt;/strong&gt; takes care of that problem by acting as a headphone “hanger” that attaches underneath your desk and keeps cables out of the way. The handy contraption is sturdy enough that it can feasibly hold two gaming headsets or pairs of headphones, no matter their size or weight, with a hook that’s also suitable for hanging your keys. Right now, you can buy the Anchor Pro for $11.95 ($4 off) on &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00P31BMHG?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; or for its full retail price &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.elevationlab.com%2Fproducts%2Fthe-anchor-pro&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;directly from ElevationLab&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="u85Xvs"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11750719"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="M1fXiz"&gt;Epicka Universal Travel Adapter&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="wYFBgy"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A speedy travel adapter you can use in more than 150 countries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="sn2mVa"&gt;Whether your giftee travels a lot for work or play, they’ll need some kind of adapter to juice up their phone, laptop, hair dryer, and other electronics. &lt;strong&gt;Epicka’s Universal Travel Adapter One&lt;/strong&gt; is a terrific option, one they can use in the UK, China, and more than 150 other countries. It charges devices pretty quickly, too, and comes with a single USB-C port and four standard USB-A ports. Right now, you can grab the adapter for $22.99 ($2 off) from &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/EPICKA-Universal-Travel-Adapter-Power/dp/B078S3M2NX?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.epickatech.com%2Fproducts%2Fepicka-international-travel-adapter&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23161828%2Fbest-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Epicka&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="7uf8Ci"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11919311"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="dMTXJE"&gt;Shark Cordless Pet Perfect Hand Vacuum&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="K7EZCZ"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A tiny but mighty vacuum that sucks up hairballs in seconds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AXfizE"&gt;For all their charms, pets come with one fatal flaw: they shed a lot of hair. If your giftee has a dog or cat, the &lt;strong&gt;Shark Cordless Pet Perfect Hand Vacuum&lt;/strong&gt; is a gift that’ll make their lives a little less messy. The powerful vacuum sucks up hairballs quickly and efficiently, yet it’s light enough that you can easily carry it anywhere in your home. Right now, you can buy the handheld vac for $44.88 (about $15 off) at &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FShark-Cordless-Pet-Perfect-Handheld-Vacuum-SV75Z%2F15706090&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="Juhdxy"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11113863"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="q8sRYG"&gt;Pinecil&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="2wJnmM"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An adjustable soldering iron outfitted with USB-C&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="045z9C"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23541478/pinecil-best-cheap-soldering-iron-open-source" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pinecil&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;is a good gift for makers and DIYers, one that will help them repair and upgrade all kinds of electronics, from keyboards to speakers. The portable soldering iron heats up in seconds and comes with a few perks old-school soldering irons lack, including a built-in OLED display so you can see the temperature and software that allows you to fine-tune the temp to your exact specifications. It also features USB-C support for fast charging. Right now, you can buy it for $25.99 ($10 off) from &lt;a href="https://pine64.com/product/pinecil-smart-mini-portable-soldering-iron/" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Pine64&lt;/a&gt; and for $39.99 on &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/PINECIL-Smart-Mini-Portable-Soldering/dp/B096X6SG13?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="Aja49P"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11993470"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="YPAAQb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="AJO2RU"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="dGkmji"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lHeGRw"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rh7ttJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wmLeJG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gSqNJn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="XXZwWF"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="C9p6rG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1CtDYH"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WYGE7o"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="H1CHcp"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/23161828/best-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/23161828/best-cheap-tech-gadgets-under-50</id>
    <author>
      <name>Sheena Vasani</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2023-12-22T19:55:10-05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-22T19:55:10-05:00</updated>
    <title>The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of hands holding various products on a brightly colored background of stars." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/a9DFjTwteBiMbEI8chPLU5J-fiw=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/72838629/236830_MAIN_Gift_Guide_LEDE_STILL_CVirginia.0.jpg" /&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;A selection of great tech and non-tech gifts aimed at the tinkerer, the creative, and the kid in all of us.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div id="WdfKT3"&gt;
&lt;script src="https://unpkg.com/react@18/umd/react.development.js" crossorigin=""&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
    &lt;script src="https://unpkg.com/react-dom@18/umd/react-dom.development.js" crossorigin=""&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src="https://unpkg.com/babel-standalone@6/babel.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;script type="text/babel"&gt;

function LedeVideo(props) {
	return (
		&lt;div className="video-wrapper"&gt;
			&lt;div className="video-inner"&gt;
				&lt;video src={props.source} muted loop autoPlay playsInline poster={props.poster}&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;cite className="font-polysans-mono text-12"&gt;{props.credit}&lt;/cite&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	)
}


	
	const containers = document.querySelectorAll(".w-full figure.w-full");
        containers.forEach(container =&gt; {const root = ReactDOM.createRoot(container);
    root.render(&lt;LedeVideo source="https://volume-assets.voxmedia.com/production/63bdad25149d2d19ad19c3705aa66f5f/236830_MAIN_Gift_Guide_LEDE_1_CVirginia.mp4" poster="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25045462/236830_MAIN_Gift_Guide_LEDE_STILL_CVirginia.jpg" credit="Photo Illustration by Amelia Holowaty Krales and Cath Virginia / The Verge" /&gt;)})
	

&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
.duet--article--lede-image.w-full {
  position: relative;
  padding-top: 62.5%;
  margin-bottom: 20px;
}

.duet--article--lede-image.w-full img, .duet--article--lede-image.w-full span {
  display: none !important;
}

.duet--article--lede-image.w-full .video-wrapper {
  position: absolute;
  inset: 0;
}

.duet--article--lede-image.w-full .video-inner {
  width: 100%;
  height: 100%;
}

.duet--article--lede-image.w-full .video-wrapper video {
  width: 100%;
  height: 100%;
  object-fit: cover;
}

.w-full figure.w-full .video-wrapper cite {
	font-style: normal;
	color: rgb(90, 90, 90);
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="G5xEsS"&gt;The holidays can be, without a doubt, one of the most stressful times of the year. People can be picky when it comes to gifts, wishlists can grow long, and time has a way of slipping between our fingers before we even notice the sudden lack of eggnog on store shelves. It doesn’t have to be that way, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="jJHMpm"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $100","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23951136/gifts-under-100-best-cheap-tech-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $50","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23952179/tech-gifts-under-50-best-cheap-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $25","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23874403/tech-gifts-under-25-best-cheap-ideas-stocking-stuffers-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 gaming and entertainment holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23959483/gaming-entertainment-gifts-ideas-2023-playstation-nintendo-xbox-tv-accessories"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 home tech holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23933231/smart-home-tech-gift-guide-2023-video-doorbells-plugs-robot-vacuums"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 digital gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23958480/digital-gift-ideas-2023-last-minute-subscriptions-unique-memberships-boxes"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for moms","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23955826/holiday-gifts-mom-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for dads","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23947139/holiday-gifts-dad-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for kids","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23964428/kids-teens-gifts-unique-ideas-2023-presents-children-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 PC gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23919557/holiday-gift-ideas-2023-pc-desktop-laptop-wfh-content-creator-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite splurge-worthy gifts for 2023","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23920823/expensive-holiday-gifts-wishes-extravagant-ideas-presents-2023"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zKDO6v"&gt;We at &lt;em&gt;The Verge &lt;/em&gt;believe that gift-giving shouldn’t be all that tough — that is, so long as you have the right cheat sheet. That’s why our ace team of writers and editors has compiled a treasure trove of clever gift ideas spanning multiple price points and personal tastes, from &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09V84WNPK?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;budget-friendly tabletop games&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2Fonn-Google-TV-4K-Streaming-Box-New-2023-4K-UHD-resolution%2F2835618394%2F&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;streaming devices&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://frame.work/products/laptop-diy-13-gen-amd/"&gt;luxury laptops you can easily upgrade&lt;/a&gt;. Some are our go-to tech recs, the beloved gadgets and gizmos our staff relies on daily, while others are aimed at those analog enthusiasts who can be hard to please.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="0dTesa"&gt;Whether you’re shopping for your mom, dad, a friend, or Fido, we’ve got enough ideas to satiate all the loved ones on your holiday wishlist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="lTGcu4"&gt;&lt;div class="m-ad__editorial-athena-placement"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="QcVaU8"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12124350"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="g8S42L"&gt;&lt;div class="m-ad__editorial-athena-placement"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/23939057/holiday-gift-guide-2023-best-ideas-unique-tech-gadgets"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/23939057/holiday-gift-guide-2023-best-ideas-unique-tech-gadgets</id>
    <author>
      <name>Verge Staff</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2023-12-19T20:36:57-05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-19T20:36:57-05:00</updated>
    <title>The Verge’s favorite splurge-worthy gifts for 2023</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of various products against a brightly colored graphic background of stars." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/LeMh_lYwSS716rkGuwdzNMqNLuA=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/72937150/236830_WORTH_THE_SPLURGE_Gift_Guide_Art_CVirginia_LEDE_2040x1360.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo Illustration by Amelia Holowaty Krales and Cath Virginia / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;The sky’s the limit when money is no object, so why waste your hard-earned cash and coin on the everyday essentials? It’s time to dream big.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="st614W"&gt;The best gifts aren’t always the most expensive, but you’re probably not going to disappoint anybody by gifting them their very own &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhphotovideo.com%2Fc%2Fproduct%2F1757890-REG%2Fsamsung_iab_146_4k_iab_series_the_wall.html&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23920823%2Fexpensive-holiday-gifts-wishes-extravagant-ideas-presents-2023" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;146-inch TV&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="MphrcJ"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 Holiday Gift Guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23939057/holiday-gift-guide-2023-best-ideas-unique-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $100","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23951136/gifts-under-100-best-cheap-tech-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $50","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23952179/tech-gifts-under-50-best-cheap-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $25","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23874403/tech-gifts-under-25-best-cheap-ideas-stocking-stuffers-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 PC Gift Guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23919557/holiday-gift-ideas-2023-pc-desktop-laptop-wfh-content-creator-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 digital gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23958480/digital-gift-ideas-2023-last-minute-subscriptions-unique-memberships-boxes"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 gaming and entertainment holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23959483/gaming-entertainment-gifts-ideas-2023-playstation-nintendo-xbox-tv-accessories"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for moms","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23955826/holiday-gifts-mom-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for dads","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23947139/holiday-gifts-dad-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for kids","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23964428/kids-teens-gifts-unique-ideas-2023-presents-children-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 home tech holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23933231/smart-home-tech-gift-guide-2023-video-doorbells-plugs-robot-vacuums"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="dT3cZ0"&gt;For this gift guide, we decided to dream up all the things we’d really love to receive as gifts if money were truly no object. Admittedly, most of the ideas here aren’t exactly affordable —   we’re looking at you, &lt;a href="https://ququq.info/ququq/busbox-4-en/"&gt;VW ID Buzz&lt;/a&gt; — though some aren’t totally out of reach if you’ve got some money to spare. &lt;a href="https://battlebeavercustoms.com/pages/configurator?productid=6685649272905"&gt;Battle Beaver’s customizable PS5 controller&lt;/a&gt; starts around $100, after all, and the &lt;a href="https://store.analogue.co/#pocket"&gt;Analogue Pocket&lt;/a&gt; will only set you back a cool $219.99 (if you can find it).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="V5pwaf"&gt;It’s not all gadgets and gizmos, either. Our dream roundup also includes &lt;a href="https://www.foliosociety.com/usa/a-game-of-thrones.html"&gt;The Folio Society’s stunning collector’s edition of &lt;em&gt;Game of Thrones&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;a super slick &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fstore.steelcase.com%2Ffrank-lloyd-wright-racine-signature-desk%3Fcclcl%3Den_US&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23920823%2Fexpensive-holiday-gifts-wishes-extravagant-ideas-presents-2023" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Frank Lloyd Wright Racine Signature Desk&lt;/a&gt;, and even an &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.intrepidtravel.com%2Fus%2Fantarctica%2Fbest-antarctica-depth-ocean-endeavour-139261&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23920823%2Fexpensive-holiday-gifts-wishes-extravagant-ideas-presents-2023" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;expedition to Antarctica&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5W7tJa"&gt;So if you’ve got a couple thousand just lying around — or aspire to one day — come join us in drooling over the coolest gifts money can buy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="deZxMM"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12100804"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="lSaL9y"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Correction December 20th, 2:23PM ET: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;We previously included an incorrect link and image for the Akari 1AG light sculpture, which we’ve since corrected. We regret the error.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/23920823/expensive-holiday-gifts-wishes-extravagant-ideas-presents-2023"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/23920823/expensive-holiday-gifts-wishes-extravagant-ideas-presents-2023</id>
    <author>
      <name>Verge Staff</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2023-12-19T19:21:31-05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-19T19:21:31-05:00</updated>
    <title>The Verge’s 2023 gaming and entertainment holiday gift guide</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of hands holding various products on a brightly colored background of stars." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Oziq9Th2P1ckSgzRT0ZYrugXX8Y=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/72871362/236830_GAME_AND_ENT_2_Gift_Guide_Artboards_CVirginia_LEDE_2040x1360.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo Illustration by Amelia Holowaty Krales and Cath Virginia / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;Even if someone is the type to buy all the latest big games, we’re certain we can help you find them a unique and adequately geeky gift this holiday.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="k0qvoP"&gt;For better or worse, gamers can be a fickle bunch. That’s why, when it comes to shopping for any purveyor of fine video games and pop culture entertainment, it may be tempting to pull the cord and just go with a gift card. But alas, there are all kinds of unique gifts you can get for someone of the geekier persuasion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="lPZGty"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 Holiday Gift Guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23939057/holiday-gift-guide-2023-best-ideas-unique-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $100","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23951136/gifts-under-100-best-cheap-tech-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $50","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23952179/tech-gifts-under-50-best-cheap-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $25","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23874403/tech-gifts-under-25-best-cheap-ideas-stocking-stuffers-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 PC Gift Guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23919557/holiday-gift-ideas-2023-pc-desktop-laptop-wfh-content-creator-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for dads","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23947139/holiday-gifts-dad-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for moms","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23955826/holiday-gifts-mom-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for kids","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23964428/kids-teens-gifts-unique-ideas-2023-presents-children-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 home tech holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23933231/smart-home-tech-gift-guide-2023-video-doorbells-plugs-robot-vacuums"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 digital gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23958480/digital-gift-ideas-2023-last-minute-subscriptions-unique-memberships-boxes"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite splurge-worthy gifts for 2023","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23920823/expensive-holiday-gifts-wishes-extravagant-ideas-presents-2023"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="6S5tOH"&gt;Admittedly, &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; staff is almost exclusively comprised of nerds who spend countless hours playing games and tracking the latest goings-on in fandom (they even pay us to do some of that here). So we’ve put our heads together and chosen some fun gift ideas you can buy for the most hardcore (and softest-core) of gaming enthusiasts, from &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Video-Game-Year-Year-Year/dp/1419762052/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;an excellent paperback retrospective&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1794680/Vampire_Survivors/"&gt;the greatest video game of all time&lt;/a&gt; (for under $5) to &lt;a href="https://battlebeavercustoms.com/"&gt;custom controllers&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Loki-Season-1-Tom-Hiddleston/dp/B0CG6JJ5B5?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Blu-rays&lt;/a&gt;, and the nostalgia trip that is the &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lego.com%2Fen-us%2Fproduct%2Fpac-man-arcade-10323%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23959483%2Fgaming-entertainment-gifts-ideas-2023-playstation-nintendo-xbox-tv-accessories" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Lego Pac-Man Arcade building kit&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7VLA8G"&gt;So, skip the LameStop gift card this year and get a present that’s sure to be a banger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="QBebrx"&gt;&lt;div class="m-ad__editorial-athena-placement"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="o9lDKj"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12141028"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/23959483/gaming-entertainment-gifts-ideas-2023-playstation-nintendo-xbox-tv-accessories"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/23959483/gaming-entertainment-gifts-ideas-2023-playstation-nintendo-xbox-tv-accessories</id>
    <author>
      <name>Antonio G. Di Benedetto</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2023-12-19T18:38:19-05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-19T18:38:19-05:00</updated>
    <title>The Verge’s 2023 home tech holiday gift guide </title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Hands holding different products on a graphic background of brightly colored stars." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/E-LpdUcMKJSz2TPCi6T59dz2TjI=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/72842014/236830_HOME_TECH_Gift_Guide_Artboards_CVirginia_LEDE_2040x1360.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo Illustration by Amelia Holowaty Krales and Cath Virginia / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;From color-changing lights to gadgets that’ll take care of dinner for you and your pets, here are some of our favorite smart home gifts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="qGBWib"&gt;Our homes are where we spend a good chunk of our lives, so we might as well make them feel like somewhere worth living. Given where we live can influence everything from our mood to our productivity, a gift for the home is thus an investment, one that can go a long way toward helping your loved one live a better life. But that’s only if it’s the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; gift. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="n3wMFJ"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23939057/holiday-gift-guide-2023-best-ideas-unique-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 gaming and entertainment holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23959483/gaming-entertainment-gifts-ideas-2023-playstation-nintendo-xbox-tv-accessories"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 PC gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23919557/holiday-gift-ideas-2023-pc-desktop-laptop-wfh-content-creator-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $100","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23951136/gifts-under-100-best-cheap-tech-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $50","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23952179/tech-gifts-under-50-best-cheap-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $25","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23874403/tech-gifts-under-25-best-cheap-ideas-stocking-stuffers-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 digital gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23958480/digital-gift-ideas-2023-last-minute-subscriptions-unique-memberships-boxes"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for moms","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23955826/holiday-gifts-mom-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for dads","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23947139/holiday-gifts-dad-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for kids","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23964428/kids-teens-gifts-unique-ideas-2023-presents-children-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite splurge-worthy gifts for 2023","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23920823/expensive-holiday-gifts-wishes-extravagant-ideas-presents-2023"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="OxoV2w"&gt;Some presents can turn a house into a home, while others merely add to the clutter. Thankfully, we at &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; know a lot about smart home tech, and we’ve rounded up a selection of gifts that can truly add value to your loved one’s life. We’ve included &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Patented-Oscillating-Obstacle-Avoidance-Cleaning/dp/B09M8LG59J?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;robovacs&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/PetSafe-Automatic-Smartphone-24-Cups-Enabled/dp/B07NR47N2Q?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;pet feeders&lt;/a&gt;, and gadgets they can program to take care of everyday tasks on their behalf as well as &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Govee-Cabinet-Assistant-SmartThings-Upgraded/dp/B0BWLHHV8M?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;color-changing lights&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ikea.com%2Fus%2Fen%2Fp%2Fsymfonisk-picture-frame-with-wi-fi-speaker-black-smart-40487320%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23933231%2Fsmart-home-tech-gift-guide-2023-video-doorbells-plugs-robot-vacuums" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;art-inspired speakers&lt;/a&gt;, and other items that’ll make their home feel more pleasant to live in. We’ve also pulled together some cool gifts that aren’t gadgets — including &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/1607749726?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;books&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Tsukiusagishirushi-Slim-Pot-1-2L-Black/dp/B0007CM3EC?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;kettles&lt;/a&gt;, and a &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.venusetfleur.com%2Fcollections%2Fshop-all-eternity-flowers%2Fproducts%2Fmini-round-white-classic&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23933231%2Fsmart-home-tech-gift-guide-2023-video-doorbells-plugs-robot-vacuums" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;rose&lt;/a&gt; that can last up to a year — because, hey, everybody needs a break from tech every now and again. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="GlZCJA"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12113904"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zuz9Uo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/23933231/smart-home-tech-gift-guide-2023-video-doorbells-plugs-robot-vacuums"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/23933231/smart-home-tech-gift-guide-2023-video-doorbells-plugs-robot-vacuums</id>
    <author>
      <name>Sheena Vasani</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2023-12-19T17:51:52-05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-19T17:51:52-05:00</updated>
    <title>The Verge’s 2023 PC gift guide</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of hands holding various products against a brightly colored graphic background of stars." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/NKp7YtAgU_mcPIzB9I2SJBfnyLU=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/72825088/236830_PC_Gift_Guide_Art_CVirginia_LEDE_2040x1360.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo Illustration by Amelia Holowaty Krales and Cath Virginia / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;The best tech gifts for those who spend way too much time sitting at a laptop or desktop PC — whether for work or leisure.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="i7w1rf"&gt;Even though smartphones are the main computers in most of our lives, there’s no beating a proper PC when it comes to productivity, gaming, and content creation. Fortunately, if someone in your life is the type to sit at a desktop or laptop for hours on end, we’ve collected some great recommendations for fun, helpful gifts you can get that person this holiday season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AUbPb5"&gt;Our gift ideas range from a sleek monitor light that can help with eye strain (&lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Flumecube.com%2Fproducts%2Fmonitor-light-bar&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23919557%2Fholiday-gift-ideas-2023-pc-desktop-laptop-wfh-content-creator-tech-gadgets" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$79.99&lt;/a&gt;) to arguably the best PC game of the year (&lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1086940/Baldurs_Gate_3/"&gt;$59.99&lt;/a&gt;), one that offers hundreds of hours of immersive roleplaying. We’ve even got some excellent accouterments to level up your desk setup in both the functionality and aesthetics departments, like the Logitech G Pro X Superlight 2 mouse (&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Logitech-Superlight-Lightspeed-Lightweight-Programmable/dp/B09NBWQDKX?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$153.80&lt;/a&gt;) and a jumbo-size desk pad (&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Genuine-Leather-Protector-Non-Slip-Waterproof/dp/B08C33135F?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$84.50&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="68G6d7"&gt;So take a gander and let us help you find a great gift for that picky nerd in your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="hb4Q6b"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23939057/holiday-gift-guide-2023-best-ideas-unique-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 gaming and entertainment holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23959483/gaming-entertainment-gifts-ideas-2023-playstation-nintendo-xbox-tv-accessories"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 home tech holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23933231/smart-home-tech-gift-guide-2023-video-doorbells-plugs-robot-vacuums"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 digital gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23958480/digital-gift-ideas-2023-last-minute-subscriptions-unique-memberships-boxes"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for moms","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23955826/holiday-gifts-mom-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for dads","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23947139/holiday-gifts-dad-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for kids","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23964428/kids-teens-gifts-unique-ideas-2023-presents-children-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite splurge-worthy gifts for 2023","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23920823/expensive-holiday-gifts-wishes-extravagant-ideas-presents-2023"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $100","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23951136/gifts-under-100-best-cheap-tech-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $50","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23952179/tech-gifts-under-50-best-cheap-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $25","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23874403/tech-gifts-under-25-best-cheap-ideas-stocking-stuffers-2023-budget"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="1vsqCq"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12102763"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/23919557/holiday-gift-ideas-2023-pc-desktop-laptop-wfh-content-creator-tech-gadgets"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/23919557/holiday-gift-ideas-2023-pc-desktop-laptop-wfh-content-creator-tech-gadgets</id>
    <author>
      <name>Antonio G. Di Benedetto</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2023-12-18T19:22:05-05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-18T19:22:05-05:00</updated>
    <title>The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $25</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of hands holding various products on a brightly colored background of stars." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/1H0sEX0F0mODlwoLCW8drLTlf8M=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/72891806/236830_UNDER_25_Gift_Guide_Artboards_CVirginia_LEDE_2040x1360.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo Illustration by Amelia Holowaty Krales and Cath Virginia / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;Whether you need a stocking stuffer or a white elephant present, we’ve got an inexpensive gift idea for nearly every occasion.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="O7ACrQ"&gt;Even with inflation on the decline, it often feels like it’s an uphill battle to find the right gift at the right price. Dollars simply don’t stretch like they used to, at least not in a world where high-end handsets and handhelds reign supreme. Luckily, you’re in the right spot if you’ve found yourself working with a limited budget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="toF1Hx"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 Holiday Gift Guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23939057/holiday-gift-guide-2023-best-ideas-unique-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $100","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23951136/gifts-under-100-best-cheap-tech-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $50","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23952179/tech-gifts-under-50-best-cheap-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 home tech holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23933231/smart-home-tech-gift-guide-2023-video-doorbells-plugs-robot-vacuums"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 PC Gift Guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23919557/holiday-gift-ideas-2023-pc-desktop-laptop-wfh-content-creator-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 digital gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23958480/digital-gift-ideas-2023-last-minute-subscriptions-unique-memberships-boxes"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 gaming and entertainment holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23959483/gaming-entertainment-gifts-ideas-2023-playstation-nintendo-xbox-tv-accessories"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for moms","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23955826/holiday-gifts-mom-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for dads","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23947139/holiday-gifts-dad-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for kids","url":"https://www.theverge.com/e/23728469"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="quNmYl"&gt;Like in previous years, we’ve taken the accumulated knowledge of &lt;em&gt;The Verge &lt;/em&gt;staff and set out to find the best bang for your buck across several categories, resulting in a selection of gifts that are cheap only in price. Our low-cost collection includes an assortment of well-loved tech staples, from &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B072JYDQ7N/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;charging cables&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07YN82X3B/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;gaming mice&lt;/a&gt; to a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00E4LGTYC/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;wired pair of earbuds&lt;/a&gt; that — gasp! — come in more than one color. And because many of us are obsessed with more than just gadgets behind the scenes, we’ve also included a few non-tech gifts. After all, you never know who in your orbit might be a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09V84WNPK/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;wannabe dungeon master&lt;/a&gt; or an &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0000DE824/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;aspiring &lt;em&gt;Top Chef&lt;/em&gt; contestant&lt;/a&gt; with a competitive edge and one ruthless picadillo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="gRn9d0"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12052486"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/23874403/tech-gifts-under-25-best-cheap-ideas-stocking-stuffers-2023-budget"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/23874403/tech-gifts-under-25-best-cheap-ideas-stocking-stuffers-2023-budget</id>
    <author>
      <name>Verge Staff</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2023-12-18T18:14:07-05:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-18T18:14:07-05:00</updated>
    <title>The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for kids </title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of hands holding various products on a brightly colored background of stars." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/BuamjMoqrNyuzYDmwJ1sITdned8=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/72888273/236830_FOR_KIDS_Gift_Guide_Art_CVirginia_LEDE_2040x1360.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo Illustration by Amelia Holowaty Krales and Cath Virginia / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;Let us help you find all kinds of gifts for all kinds of kiddos.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="5NrY7F"&gt;Some kids may just want a boatload of Robux for the holidays, but honestly, it’s more satisfying to gift them something a tiny bit more tangible or that you can enjoy together. While not all of us here at &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; are parents, all of us are undoubtedly kids at heart — so let us help you find the right gift for your little ones, whether they’re toddlers or hard-to-impress teens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="lqhiyI"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 Holiday Gift Guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23939057/holiday-gift-guide-2023-best-ideas-unique-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $100","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23951136/gifts-under-100-best-cheap-tech-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $50","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23952179/tech-gifts-under-50-best-cheap-ideas-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s favorite holiday gifts under $25","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23874403/tech-gifts-under-25-best-cheap-ideas-stocking-stuffers-2023-budget"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 home tech holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23933231/smart-home-tech-gift-guide-2023-video-doorbells-plugs-robot-vacuums"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 PC gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23919557/holiday-gift-ideas-2023-pc-desktop-laptop-wfh-content-creator-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for dads","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23947139/holiday-gifts-dad-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 holiday gift guide for moms","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23955826/holiday-gifts-mom-unique-ideas-2023-tech-gadgets"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 gaming and entertainment holiday gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23959483/gaming-entertainment-gifts-ideas-2023-playstation-nintendo-xbox-tv-accessories"},{"title":"The Verge’s 2023 digital gift guide","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23958480/digital-gift-ideas-2023-last-minute-subscriptions-unique-memberships-boxes"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="VADPLt"&gt;Gadgets like &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2F2021-Apple-10-2-inch-iPad-Wi-Fi-64GB-Space-Gray-9th-Generation%2F483978365%2F&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Apple’s entry-level iPad&lt;/a&gt; ($249) make for popular gifts, but it’s okay to pull back a little and opt for something a little more unplugged, such as a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DGSMNTC?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;cooperative board game&lt;/a&gt; ($31.99) or a &lt;a href="https://www.electronicexpress.com/catalog/208421/hasbro-e4859-nerf-rival-perses-mxix-5000-red-motorized-blaster"&gt;motorized Nerf blaster&lt;/a&gt; ($59.99). All of them are age-appropriate, and some ideas, like a subscription-based family photo book (&lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fchatbooks.com%2Fproducts%2Fgift-a-subscription&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F23964428%2Fkids-teens-gifts-unique-ideas-2023-presents-children-tech-gadgets" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$21&lt;/a&gt;), can even bring the entire fam together (if not physically, then at least in photographic form).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="YxLnK1"&gt;So take a look at the smorgasbord of &lt;em&gt;Verge&lt;/em&gt;-sanctioned picks below, all of which should make shopping for your loved ones this holiday season that much simpler. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="Sy4eJN"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="table:12146000"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/23964428/kids-teens-gifts-unique-ideas-2023-presents-children-tech-gadgets"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/23964428/kids-teens-gifts-unique-ideas-2023-presents-children-tech-gadgets</id>
    <author>
      <name>Antonio G. Di Benedetto</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
