<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Robots</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-15T11:09:15-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/robot/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/robot" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T11:09:15-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T11:09:15-04:00</updated>
    <title>Mercedes is trialing humanoid robots for ‘low skill, repetitive’ tasks</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Apptronik’s Apollo robot carrying a blue crate in a Mercedes factory." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Hler2Mv0m6dICO6Ru6FHyUfY0kg=/503x113:5081x3165/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209516/24C0101_003.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mercedes also eventually plans to assess how Apollo handles delivering totes of kitted parts.&lt;/em&gt; | Image: Apptronik&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="JV4taN"&gt;Mercedes-Benz is the latest automotive company to trial how humanoid robots could be used to automate “low skill, physically challenging, manual labor.” On Friday, &lt;a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/apptronik-and-mercedes-benz-enter-commercial-agreement-that-will-pilot-apptroniks-apollo-humanoid-robot-in-mercedes-benz-manufacturing-facilities-302089972.html"&gt;robotics company Apptronik announced&lt;/a&gt; it had entered into a commercial agreement with Mercedes to pilot how “highly advanced robotics” like Apollo — Apptronik’s 160-pound bipedal robot — can be used in manufacturing. The news follows a similar pilot announced by &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/18/24043065/bmw-figure-robotics-humanoid-robot-workers-deployment"&gt;BMW in January&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="0neAmt"&gt;Apptronik says that Mercedes is exploring use cases like having Apollo inspect and deliver components to human production line workers. Neither company has disclosed any figures for the agreement or how many Apollo robots are being trialed. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="DyI4eX"&gt;According to Apptronik, humanoid robots would allow vehicle manufacturers to start automating manufacturing tasks without having to redesign their existing facilities. The company says its approach instead “centers on automating some physically demanding, repetitive and dull tasks for which it is increasingly hard to find reliable workers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="5g1mmz"&gt;&lt;div style="left: 0; width: 100%; height: 0; position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uJOA5IDaL5g?rel=0" style="top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute; border: 0;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="accelerometer; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share;"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="z6WJIc"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/0dd1227c-0971-4d90-960e-5aef7f18ee48"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Financial Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; reports that Mercedes has started trialing an undisclosed number of Apollo robots at a factory in Hungary. The country has experienced labor shortages for several years as workers migrate to Western Europe, with &lt;a href="https://europe.autonews.com/article/20161019/ANE/161019840/audi-mercedes-face-labor-shortage-in-hungary"&gt;Audi and Mercedes&lt;/a&gt; having both expressed concerns regarding labor supply in 2016. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GZoHKY"&gt;“This is a new frontier and we want to understand the potential both for robotics and automotive manufacturing to fill labor gaps in areas such as low skill, repetitive and physically demanding work and to free up our highly skilled team members on the line to build the world’s most desirable cars,” said Mercedes’ production chief Jörg Burzer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="abeZZu"&gt;Apollo stands at five feet, eight inches tall, with Apptronik claiming the robot can lift objects up to 55 pounds. Its “face” is delightfully goofy, but otherwise its form factor isn’t too different from other humanoid robots in development, such as &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/16/23726139/tesla-robot-update-video-shareholder-meeting"&gt;Tesla’s Optimus robot&lt;/a&gt;, or the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/18/24043065/bmw-figure-robotics-humanoid-robot-workers-deployment"&gt;Figure 01 robots&lt;/a&gt; that BMW is trialing at its South Carolina manufacturing facility. Other bipedal robots like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/20/23648343/agility-robotics-digit-next-gen-bipedal-bot"&gt;Agility Robotics’ “Digit”&lt;/a&gt; are also being piloted in &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/18/23922202/amazon-robots-sorting-machines-sequoia-warehouse"&gt;Amazon’s US warehouses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101791/mercedes-robot-humanoid-apptronik-apollo-manufacturing"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101791/mercedes-robot-humanoid-apptronik-apollo-manufacturing</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jess Weatherbed</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-22T09:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-22T09:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Nuro gets a leg up from Arm in launching its third-generation delivery robot</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Nuro R3 delivery robot" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/C84jTiPOJEtET1Gcv_1OyGaZPbQ=/0x0:3000x2000/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73156377/Hero_Image_2__Nuro_Groceries.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Nuro&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="srgWpD"&gt;Delivery robot company Nuro is reaching out to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23373371/arm-chips-chip-shortage-ceo-rene-haas-tech-intel-apple-decoder"&gt;chip designer Arm&lt;/a&gt; for help developing its &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/1/12/22878565/nuro-driverless-delivery-vehicle-third-generation-air-bag"&gt;third-generation vehicle&lt;/a&gt;, the companies announced today. The partnership is expected to enhance the capabilities and range of Nuro’s electric-powered robots as well as fast-track the production and commercialization of the company’s delivery service. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NxcBLJ"&gt;The Nuro Driver, which is the company’s branding for the hardware and software needed to power one of its autonomous delivery vehicles, will use Arm’s Automotive Enhanced technology. That’s the chip designer’s branding for the portfolio of intellectual property “dedicated to the safety and specialized computing needs of the automotive market,” Arm says. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TwBGnK"&gt;The news of the partnership comes at a perilous time for autonomous vehicle developers. Companies are facing new questions about safety following &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/7/24065063/waymo-driverless-car-strikes-bicyclist-san-francisco-injuries"&gt;several&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/24/23930629/california-dmv-suspends-cruise-robotaxi-permit-safety"&gt;incidents&lt;/a&gt; in which people were injured by driverless vehicles. Investment has also dwindled as timelines have stretched further into the future. Last spring, Nuro said it would &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/10/23718505/nuro-layoffs-pause-commercial-operations-robot-delivery"&gt;lay off 30 percent&lt;/a&gt; of its employees in order to cut costs. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="OcjwP5"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The partnership is expected to enhance the capabilities and range of Nuro’s electric-powered robots&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="Yd30JJ"&gt;Nonetheless, the company is forging ahead on its third-generation R3 vehicle, which is supposed to have twice the cargo space as the second-generation R2 robot. It will also include modular inserts and new temperature-controlled compartments to keep food warm or cold, depending on the need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="slgW4d"&gt;Nuro has been working with Arm for years but is announcing its plans today to “deepen” that relationship by relying on some of the company’s core technology to provide a foundation for its new vehicle, said Nuro chief technology officer Andrew Clare. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/QNc4G5NKdZf9GS2t_TL1icuHSy0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23161328/Nuro_Kroger_Employee.jpg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="FHSyp4"&gt;By teaming up with Arm, Nuro is also hoping to improve the efficiency and range of the R3 robot by up to 20 percent without changing the size of the vehicle’s battery, Clare said. Arm’s technology runs on very low power, freeing up more electrons for Nuro’s AI-powered “brain,” which makes real-time decisions regarding operation and safety of the vehicle while on the road. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="kWI8CX"&gt;“We create the lowest power performance technology,” said Dipti Vachani, senior VP and general manager for Arm’s automotive business, in an interview, “so that Nuro can then take advantage of all that AI software.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3O84qQ"&gt;Nuro was founded in 2016 by Dave Ferguson and Jiajun Zhu, two veterans of the Google self-driving car project that would go on to become Waymo. It is one of the few companies operating fully driverless vehicles — that is, vehicles without safety drivers behind the wheel — on public roads today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GlxxpS"&gt;Nuro’s current fleet of vehicles, which operates in California and Texas, has traveled over 1 million miles autonomously. While the software stack will run using Arm’s technology, Nuro’s powertrain — electric motors and batteries — is developed by China’s BYD. Nuro is also building a facility in Nevada, where it will manufacture its next-generation vehicles. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="U7HLvE"&gt;&lt;q&gt;“We create the lowest power performance technology.”&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="9qFxvo"&gt;But the company was also forced to put its commercial expansion on pause and delay production of its R3 vehicle last year as it dealt with cost issues. &lt;a href="https://medium.com/nuro/nuros-new-approach-a-message-from-our-founders-c8d296147e36"&gt;Nuro’s co-founders said&lt;/a&gt; they were focused on a “leaner model for AV development” that would allow the company enough money for three and a half years of operation. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uVEzSG"&gt;Since then, Nuro says it has been conducting small scale commercial pilots with some of its partners and is planning for the expansion of our delivery service in the coming years. “Deploying Nuro R3 on public roads later this year is an important step in our path to commercial scale,” Nuro spokesperson Sarah Eno Henderson. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Ca2yOX"&gt;Clare said that Nuro is already beginning to think beyond delivery to include applications like passenger vehicles. But that delivery remains its core focus at the moment — which is why the Arm deal is so important. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="vDC4HH"&gt;“We are developing in the next generation Nuro driver, which is our next generation sense and compute stack, that again provides this increase in power efficiency, this lower cost point,” Clare said. “And that’s what will enable us to scale this product to mass production.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8IqwFe"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/22/24079434/nuro-robot-delivery-arm-power-efficiency-range"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/22/24079434/nuro-robot-delivery-arm-power-efficiency-range</id>
    <author>
      <name>Andrew J. Hawkins</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-31T15:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-31T15:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Amazon left Roomba with a huge mess to clean up</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3Aa2whrs4OSl-Zp8nnpyWsko5IE=/0x0:5760x3840/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73101261/8A0A0511.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The newest Roomba vacuum — the Combo j9 Plus — faces stiff competition.&lt;/em&gt; | Photo by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;By abandoning its deal to buy iRobot, Amazon has left the robot vacuum maker stuck under the couch.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="cUqiSV"&gt;Amazon backing out of its deal to buy iRobot &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/29/24034201/amazon-irobot-acquisition-over-antitrust-regulator-scrutiny"&gt;due to regulatory issues&lt;/a&gt; may feel like a &lt;a href="https://www.techtarget.com/searchcio/news/252524792/Amazons-iRobot-acquisition-raises-concerns"&gt;win for privacy advocates&lt;/a&gt;, but it could be a death knell for the Roomba robot vacuum as we know it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Pb0y4H"&gt;On the face of it, the objection from the European Commission that &lt;a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/ip_23_5990"&gt;the deal was anti-competitive&lt;/a&gt; is cruelly ironic for iRobot, a foundering market leader struggling against a giant wave of competition. It was relying on Amazon to bring it an injection of cash along with the resources it needed to stay afloat in today’s insanely competitive robot vacuum market. But the deal is dead, and iRobot’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/1/23854843/robot-vacuum-ecovacs-dreametech-innovation-ifa-2023"&gt;competition is still very much there&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="0HpeFt"&gt;iRobot’s dominant market share has &lt;a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Technology/Chinese-robot-vacuums-sweep-global-rivals-with-high-tech-low-prices"&gt;been steadily eroding since 2014&lt;/a&gt;. According to data from &lt;a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/934089/worldwide-robotic-vacuum-cleaner-market-share/"&gt;Statista&lt;/a&gt;, it dropped from 64 percent in 2016 to 46 percent in 2020. As someone who has been &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22997597/best-robot-vacuum-cleaner"&gt;reviewing robot vacuums for over five years&lt;/a&gt;, it’s easy to see why. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="fhiPo9"&gt;In the last decade, Chinese companies like Ecovacs (Deebot / Yeedi), Anker (Eufy), Roborock (backed by Xiaomi), and Dreame Technology have burst onto the global market with cheaper, flashier options. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3Voor65eXiUjPl7VsWRXtsgPmg4=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25259031/all_the_robots.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;There are a lot of robot vacuums available today, and I’ve tested most of them.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="CNCuLE"&gt;Samsung and US-based SharkNinja are also taking bites out of the pie, and that’s not to mention the dozens of no-name brands with bots available on Amazon for under $200 — a fraction of the price of flagships from &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fus.roborock.com%2Fpages%2Froborock-s8-maxv-ultra&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F1%2F31%2F24057077%2Firobot-amazon-deal-collapse-roomba-uncertain-future" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Roborock&lt;/a&gt; ($1,600) and &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.irobot.com%2Fen_US%2Froomba-combo-j9plus-auto-fill-robot-vacuum-and-mop%2FC975020.html&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F1%2F31%2F24057077%2Firobot-amazon-deal-collapse-roomba-uncertain-future" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Roomba&lt;/a&gt; ($1,400). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="s3Kuy7"&gt;The market was tough enough to take down one US-based robovac company last year, &lt;a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/01/neato-robotics-is-being-shut-down-after-18-years/"&gt;Neato Robotics&lt;/a&gt;. Now, iRobot is the one with problems. &lt;a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/irobot-reports-fourth-quarter-and-full-year-2022-financial-results-301745392.html"&gt;Reporting a net loss for 2022&lt;/a&gt;, it potentially needed a deal like Amazon’s to survive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="2bTpdW"&gt;&lt;q&gt;If anyone was going to bring us a Rosey the Robot, it was iRobot&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="re1soA"&gt;A sale could have helped iRobot “better compete in the global marketplace, particularly against companies, and from countries, that aren’t subject to the same regulatory requirements in fast-moving technology segments like robotics,” said Amazon SVP David Zapolsky when &lt;a href="https://media.irobot.com/2024-01-29-Amazon-and-iRobot-agree-to-terminate-pending-acquisition"&gt;Amazon announced it was abandoning the deal&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="jXHvBF"&gt;Now iRobot has lost its CEO and founder Colin Angle, is laying off staff, and facing an existential crisis, which is a huge shame because it’s still our best bet for truly smart and innovative robovacs. Led by Angle, iRobot has been a major innovator in home robotics over the last three decades. The sum total of its advancements exceeds those of competitors like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22901270/roborock-s7-plus-robot-vacuum-and-mop-review"&gt;Roborock&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23037426/ecovacs-deebot-x1-omni-review-vacuum-mop-robot-voice-control"&gt;Ecovacs&lt;/a&gt;. If anyone was going to bring us a Rosey the Robot, it was iRobot. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/QJoxc5lpcxs7iTPzxsJa7DdC8KA=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23163835/vtuohy_220110_4963_0019.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Samsung Jet Bot AI and the Roomba j7 were two of the first robot vacuums to be able to (mostly) avoid smearing dog crap over your house.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="uLjcn5"&gt;iRobot invented the first successful robot vacuum over 20 years ago, but if your last experience with a Roomba was pre-2013, things have changed. Today, all these floor cleaning droids are much, much better — in large part due to iRobot’s innovations that have been adopted by the rest of the market. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gUdibV"&gt;It was the first to implement a viable &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/circuitbreaker/2018/9/6/17817220/irobot-roomba-i7-robot-vacuum-empties-itself-maps-house"&gt;auto-empty dock&lt;/a&gt; that sucks the dirt out of the robot’s bin for you. (&lt;a href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/robot-vacuums-that-empty-themselves"&gt;Others tried&lt;/a&gt;, but versions of iRobot’s method are now standard). It was one of the first to bring &lt;a href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2015/09/16/247936/the-roomba-now-sees-and-maps-a-home/"&gt;effective room mapping&lt;/a&gt; to move bots on from their bump-and-roll randomness, and it has led the way in developing &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/11/30/22809454/irobot-roomba-j7-plus-christmas-tree-clean-pine-needles-socks-shoes-transfer-mapping-data"&gt;reliable AI algorithms&lt;/a&gt; for avoiding household objects like socks, phone cables, and pet waste. And, based on my extensive experience testing these bots, it’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22997597/best-robot-vacuum-cleaner"&gt;still the best at cleaning your floors&lt;/a&gt;. Its unique dual rubber roller brush system, which &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/4/23531209/roborock-s8-pro-robot-vacuums-price-specs-release-date-ces"&gt;some have copied&lt;/a&gt; but none have surpassed, gets the job done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="BQyCBW"&gt;What also sets iRobot apart is its approach to software. On top of a robust and easy-to-use app, the company has built a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/5/31/23147761/irobot-os-intelligent-software-robot-vacuums"&gt;robot OS&lt;/a&gt; with the goal of elevating floor-cleaning robots from basic remote control vacuuming to something smarter. “The barrier to the next level of AI in robotics isn’t better AI. It’s context,” &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/5/31/23147761/irobot-os-intelligent-software-robot-vacuums"&gt;Angle told me in 2022&lt;/a&gt;, just prior to announcing the Amazon deal. iRobot was working on using its robots to better understand how we live in our homes to both improve how they clean and potentially expand further into the smart home. This, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23293687/amazon-irobot-acquisition-purchase-smarthome-intelligence-privacy-analysis"&gt;as I’ve said before&lt;/a&gt;, is a big part of why Amazon wanted the company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1AcENM"&gt;Potentially, it was these efforts at making the robot floor cleaner smarter, plowing money into R&amp;amp;D around intelligence rather than churning out more mass-market products like its competitors, that put iRobot in its current precarious position. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/DS-VxAaZWw0P47Aj3-i-aPRIyIg=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25259045/8A0A0435.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roborock offers a huge lineup of good robot vacuums at every price point.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zBfebH"&gt;Its competitors are &lt;a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Technology/Chinese-robot-vacuums-sweep-global-rivals-with-high-tech-low-prices"&gt;racing ahead&lt;/a&gt;, regularly launching &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/8/24024235/roborock-s8-maxv-ultra-robot-vacuum-arm-matter-video"&gt;new models at multiple price points&lt;/a&gt; with new, sometimes bizarre-seeming features (a vacuum &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/8/24024235/roborock-s8-maxv-ultra-robot-vacuum-arm-matter-video"&gt;with an arm&lt;/a&gt;, a robot that &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/7/24028690/this-robovac-can-cut-tangled-hair-for-you"&gt;can cut hair&lt;/a&gt;, and another with mops &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/6/24027023/dreamebot-l20-ultra-robovac-humble-tabletop-digital-game-bundle-deal-sale"&gt;that can do the splits&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NtBjtq"&gt;While iRobot has not been resting on its laurels, its decision not to pivot to lidar from &lt;a href="https://www.allaboutcircuits.com/news/what-is-visual-slam-not-just-a-tech-for-roomba-vacuums/"&gt;vSLAM&lt;/a&gt; (visual simultaneous localization and mapping) when the technology became more affordable was a questionable one. As was its slow adoption of the popular &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22901270/roborock-s7-plus-robot-vacuum-and-mop-review"&gt;combination mopping and vacuuming model&lt;/a&gt;. The company stuck for too long to its ethos that the tasks were better separate (it has a line of mopping-only robots) before only halfheartedly addressing the problem with the Combo j7 in 2022 and, more recently, launching more &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/28/23845899/irobot-roomba-combo-j5-plus-robot-vacuum-mop-price"&gt;lower-cost bots&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="aGzjsK"&gt;In the meantime, Roborock, Ecovacs, and Dreame Technology have been furiously innovating on the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22960447/roborock-s7-maxv-ultra-review-robot-vacuum-mop-hybrid"&gt;all-in-one solution&lt;/a&gt;: a robot vacuum that can mop, vacuum, empty its bin, refill its mop, drain its dirty water, clean and blow dry its mop pads, and even &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23845579/switchbot-s10-robot-vacuum-mop-launch-ifa"&gt;hook into your plumbing&lt;/a&gt; so you barely need to lift a finger. A year later, iRobot responded with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/11/23864923/irobot-roomba-combo-j9-plus-robot-vacuum-mop-price-features"&gt;the Combo j9 Plus&lt;/a&gt;, which has an auto-fill dock for the mop but lacks many of the features its competitors tout. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;aside id="pG22Jk"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The pandemic bump the company experienced when we were all frantically cleaning our homes turned into a catastrophic tumble&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="iwulFq"&gt;While these multifunction robovacs may be more of a fad than a trend (time will tell, but few do both well and those docks are more work than they appear), its tardiness here puts iRobot on the back foot. Now, hurting for cash and with its founder Angle out, the money men are coming in. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4CeF6F"&gt;The pandemic bump the company experienced when we were all frantically cleaning our homes turned into a catastrophic tumble as revenue dropped. The 2022 net loss has been compounded, and iRobot is &lt;a href="https://investor.irobot.com/news-releases/news-release-details/irobot-announces-operational-restructuring-plan-position-company"&gt;estimating an operating loss of up to $285 million in 2023&lt;/a&gt;. Last year, it had to borrow $200 million until the Amazon deal closed, and with just a $94 million apology from Amazon for walking away from the deal, it’s got to find the rest of that money elsewhere or risk being sold off for parts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/j8zqFj3KG4eR6ACi8vskMlQXM4A=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25259057/8A0A0026.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Photo by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Ecovacs Deebot X2 Omni is one of a new breed of very expensive robot vacuums that promise to do almost everything for you.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="nhoQQu"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://investor.irobot.com/news-releases/news-release-details/irobot-announces-operational-restructuring-plan-position-company"&gt;plan&lt;/a&gt; includes cutting a third of its staff, shutting down offices, and reducing research and development by $20 million year over year through offshoring non-core engineering functions. It’s also abandoning its &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.irobot.com%2Fen_US%2Fpremium-air-purifiers%2FAair-3-in-1-Pro-Air-Purifiers.html&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F1%2F31%2F24057077%2Firobot-amazon-deal-collapse-roomba-uncertain-future" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;line of air purifiers&lt;/a&gt; (it purchased &lt;a href="https://investor.irobot.com/news-releases/news-release-details/irobot-acquires-air-purification-company-aeris-cleantec-ag#:~:text=BEDFORD%2C%20Mass.%20%2C%20Nov.,%2FPRNewswire%2F%20%2D%2D%20iRobot%20Corp."&gt;Aeris&lt;/a&gt; in 2021) and its &lt;a href="https://www.irobot.com.au/Terra"&gt;Terra robot lawnmower&lt;/a&gt; (which never launched in the US), which will once again put the competition ahead of it. &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ecovacs.com%2Fglobal%2Fcampaign%2Fgoat-robotic-lawn-mower&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F1%2F31%2F24057077%2Firobot-amazon-deal-collapse-roomba-uncertain-future" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Ecovacs&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/dreame-launches-revolutionized-robotic-lawn-mower-a1-that-brings-real-hands-free-experience-at-ces-2024-302031707.html"&gt;Dreame&lt;/a&gt; are both shipping robot lawnmowers to the US for the first time this year, and &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ecovacs.com%2Fglobal%2Fairbot-air-purifier-robot%2Fairbot-z1&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F1%2F31%2F24057077%2Firobot-amazon-deal-collapse-roomba-uncertain-future" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Ecovacs has a robot air purifier&lt;/a&gt; it says is coming to the US soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NQ4YWm"&gt;Without substantive R&amp;amp;D, innovative new products, and building on its (comparatively) excellent software, Roomba could quickly become an also-ran as Chinese companies move in and hoover up more market share. These companies make good robot vacuums and are innovating rapidly, but they come with their own issues, including a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22997597/best-robot-vacuum-cleaner#:~:text=Roborock%2C%20for%20example%2C%20doesn%E2%80%99t%20sell%20spare%20parts%20beyond%20bags%2C%20bins%2C%20and%20brushes%20on%20its%20accessories%20site%3B%20you%20have%20to%20ship%20the%20robot%20to%20the%20company%20for%20any%20repairs."&gt;lack of user repairability&lt;/a&gt;  (which iRobot excels at) and some &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ifixit.com%2FNews%2F88815%2Fthe-worst-in-show-2024-losers-are-in%23%3A%7E%3Atext%3DThe%2520CES%2520Worst%2520in%2520Show%2520award%2520for%2520cyber%2520security%2520goes%2520to%2520the%2520China%252Dbased%2520smart%2520vacuum%2520maker%2520Ecovacs%252C%2520which%2520unveiled%2520its%2520X2%2520Combo%2520vacuum%25E2%2580%2594an%2520update%2520of%2520its%2520Deebot%2520X2%2520Omni%2520robot%2520vacuum%25E2%2580%2594at%2520CES.&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F1%2F31%2F24057077%2Firobot-amazon-deal-collapse-roomba-uncertain-future" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;privacy concerns&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gfAb4P"&gt;Angle &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/colinangle"&gt;said this week&lt;/a&gt; that he believes “iRobot has an exciting future ahead of it.” With basic robot vacuums fast becoming a commodity product, the next big thing in home robotics is a leap I’m genuinely excited about. While iRobot was high on my list of companies to deliver that, I wish I could be as optimistic about its future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="IWUSOd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/31/24057077/irobot-amazon-deal-collapse-roomba-uncertain-future"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/31/24057077/irobot-amazon-deal-collapse-roomba-uncertain-future</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jennifer Pattison Tuohy</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-29T08:43:28-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-29T08:43:28-05:00</updated>
    <title>Amazon abandons $1.4 billion deal to buy Roomba maker iRobot</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A robot vacuum with mopping arm deployed. The arm is a circular section of the top case of the Roomba with a mop pad on the underside. It presses against the floor when in use." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/rnaN_fS3bZTZw21krdy6_Ouxh8k=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73093589/226425_Roomba_Combo_Review_JTuohy_0014.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;One of iRobot’s Roombas in action.&lt;/em&gt; | Photo by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="p1Kbbj"&gt;Amazon’s deal to buy Roomba maker iRobot is off, the &lt;a href="https://media.irobot.com/2024-01-29-Amazon-and-iRobot-agree-to-terminate-pending-acquisition"&gt;companies announced today&lt;/a&gt;, after iRobot said the deal has “no path to regulatory approval in the European Union.” iRobot is also announcing that it’s laying off around 350 employees, or around 31 percent of its workforce as &lt;a href="https://investor.irobot.com/news-releases/news-release-details/irobot-announces-operational-restructuring-plan-position-company"&gt;part of a restructuring&lt;/a&gt;. It expects to notify the majority of affected employees by the end of March.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="M48tVd"&gt;As part of the announcement, iRobot chair and CEO Colin Angle, who co-founded the company in 1990, is stepping down from both roles. iRobot’s current executive vice president and chief legal officer, Glen Weinstein, will serve as interim CEO, and Andrew Miller, formerly lead independent director of the board, will become chair. As part of the restructuring, iRobot is pausing its work on devices outside of its core floor-cleaning product lineup like air purifiers and lawn mowers, and closing offices and facilities in “smaller, underperforming geographies.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AXAD3h"&gt;The collapse of the deal means Amazon will pay a $94 million termination fee to iRobot, which will largely be used to help pay off a $200 million loan it took out last year. As part of today’s announcement, iRobot published its preliminary fourth quarter results for 2023 and said it expects to report a GAAP operating loss of “between $265 and $285 million.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mvkljc"&gt;The announcement comes after the $1.4 billion acquisition ran into difficulties with EU regulators. Last November, the &lt;a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/ip_23_5990"&gt;European Commission said&lt;/a&gt; it believed the deal had the potential to restrict competition in the robot vacuum cleaner market. Many of iRobot’s competitors also sell their devices on Amazon’s online store, and regulators were concerned that Amazon could delist or reduce the visibility of rival robot vacuum cleaners, restricting competition and “leading to higher prices, lower quality, and less innovation for consumers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="loTD5S"&gt;Amazon had until January 10th to try to convince the European Commission to let the deal go through, but &lt;a href="https://www.politico.eu/article/amazon-dodges-concessions-to-appease-eu-on-irobot-deal/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Politico &lt;/em&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; that the deadline passed without Amazon offering any concessions. The companies &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/8/5/23293349/amazon-acquires-irobot-roomba-robot-vacuums"&gt;first announced the deal&lt;/a&gt; in August 2022 and &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/amazon-s-purchase-of-roomba-maker-cleared-by-cma"&gt;received the go-ahead from the UK’s competition regulator&lt;/a&gt; in June 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="TPlqV7"&gt;&lt;q&gt;“Undue and disproportionate regulatory hurdles discourage entrepreneurs”&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mweuUp"&gt;In a statement, Amazon SVP and general counsel David Zapolsky said he was “disappointed” that the deal couldn’t proceed. “This outcome will deny consumers faster innovation and more competitive prices, which we’re confident would have made their lives easier and more enjoyable,” Zapolsky said. “Mergers and acquisitions like this help companies like iRobot better compete in the global marketplace, particularly against companies, and from countries, that aren’t subject to the same regulatory requirements in fast-moving technology segments like robotics. Undue and disproportionate regulatory hurdles discourage entrepreneurs, who should be able to see acquisition as one path to success, and that hurts both consumers and competition.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="B6pjyt"&gt;The deal is one of several major tech acquisitions to have fallen apart in recent years as global regulators ramp up scrutiny. Adobe &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/18/24005996/adobe-figma-acquisition-abandoned-termination-fee"&gt;walked away from its $20 billion deal to buy Figma late last year&lt;/a&gt; in the face of pressure from UK and EU regulators, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/2/7/22922731/nvidia-no-longer-buying-acquiring-arm-reportedly"&gt;Nvidia formally abandoned its $40 billion Arm deal&lt;/a&gt;, citing “significant regulatory challenges” in early 2022, and even &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/18/23410487/meta-sell-off-giphy-following-uk-cma-competition-ruling"&gt;Meta was unable to buy Giphy&lt;/a&gt;. Microsoft was able to push its deal to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/13/23791235/microsoft-activision-blizzard-acquisition-complete-finalized"&gt;buy Activision Blizzard through&lt;/a&gt;, but only after first granting concessions &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/13/23796552/microsoft-activision-blizzard-cma-approval-uk"&gt;to the UK&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/15/23723703/microsoft-activision-blizzard-acquisition-approved-eu-european-commission"&gt;EU authorities&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="FXDjNr"&gt;In the past, Amazon has been able to make smart home acquisitions with less difficulty. It &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/circuitbreaker/2017/12/22/16810516/amazon-blink-acquisition-smart-camera-doorbell-company"&gt;acquired camera and doorbell company Blink in 2017&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2018/2/27/17059664/amazon-ring-acquisition-smart-home-security-cloud-cam"&gt;home security company Ring in 2018&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2019/2/11/18220960/amazon-eero-acquisition-announced"&gt;mesh router company Eero in 2019&lt;/a&gt;. Since then, Amazon has maintained the individual brand names of the companies and has continued to sell competing devices via its online store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1XRRe7"&gt;In the time since announcing its plans to buy iRobot, Amazon’s devices and services business has gained a new boss. When the deal was first announced, Dave Limp was still serving as Amazon hardware’s top executive. But as of the end of October 2023, Limp had been &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/27/23892462/amazon-hires-panos-panay-microsoft"&gt;replaced by Panos Panay&lt;/a&gt;, who moved into the role from Microsoft, while Limp has transitioned to CEO of Jeff Bezos’ aerospace company, Blue Origin.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/29/24034201/amazon-irobot-acquisition-over-antitrust-regulator-scrutiny"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/29/24034201/amazon-irobot-acquisition-over-antitrust-regulator-scrutiny</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jon Porter</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-18T14:50:41-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-18T14:50:41-05:00</updated>
    <title>BMW’s South Carolina plant is testing humanoid robot workers</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Three of Figure’s prototype humanoid robots displayed in a factory setting." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/pwdI0KmJeg38STRiVqK1oNPqdvY=/249x0:1751x1001/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73066381/Figure_robotics_prototype.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Figure unveiled its first prototype humanoid robot (pictured) in October 2023, just one year after the company was founded.&lt;/em&gt; | Image: Figure&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="CIpchN"&gt;Robotics startup &lt;a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/figure-announces-commercial-agreement-with-bmw-manufacturing-to-bring-general-purpose-robots-into-automotive-production-302036263.html"&gt;Figure has signed a “commercial agreement” with BMW to introduce&lt;/a&gt; its “general purpose” humanoid robots to BMW’s manufacturing facility in Spartanburg, South Carolina, as it tries to identify use cases in automotive production. The robots are intended to automate “difficult, unsafe, or tedious” manufacturing tasks, and if they’re found to be viable, they’ll then be deployed in the BMW facility in stages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HpiMkV"&gt;“Single-purpose robotics have saturated the commercial market for decades, but the potential of general purpose robotics is completely untapped,” said Figure CEO Brett Adcock. “Figure’s robots will enable companies to increase productivity, reduce costs, and create a safer and more consistent environment.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="qIebL1"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"&gt;
&lt;p lang="en" dir="ltr"&gt;Just last week Figure 01 learned how to make coffee using an end-to-end AI system&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are excited to be introducing industry leading AI to the automotive sector&lt;a href="https://t.co/DNAZWnaYK3"&gt;pic.twitter.com/DNAZWnaYK3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;— Figure (@Figure_robot) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Figure_robot/status/1747982255337959753?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;January 18, 2024&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="z5mgY8"&gt;Car manufacturers like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2018/6/28/17514134/honda-asimo-humanoid-robot-retire"&gt;Honda&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/12/11/22167835/hyundai-boston-dynamics-aquisition-consumer-robotics"&gt;Hyundai&lt;/a&gt; have had a visible presence in the development of walking robots over the years, but attempts at integrating them into the real world are ramping up. Tesla unveiled the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/13/23999559/teslas-new-optimus-gen-2-robot"&gt;second generation of its Optimus robot&lt;/a&gt; back in December, and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/18/23922202/amazon-robots-sorting-machines-sequoia-warehouse"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; is trialing &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/20/23648343/agility-robotics-digit-next-gen-bipedal-bot"&gt;Agility Robotics’ “Digit” robot&lt;/a&gt; in its US warehouses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="fUP3yr"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.bmwgroup-werke.com/spartanburg/en.html"&gt;BMW manufacturing facility in South Carolina&lt;/a&gt; is the company’s only US-based plant, where it assembles around 1,500 X-series and XM-series vehicles every day. It currently employs around 11,000 people and is the largest automotive exporter in the US by value, with an export value of $9.6 billion. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="nFRWhk"&gt;Neither company has disclosed how many of Figure’s humanoid robots will be deployed at the facility or what tasks they’re expected to undertake, though Adcock &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/bmw-taps-humanoid-startup-figure-take-teslas-robot-2024-01-18/"&gt;told &lt;em&gt;Reuters&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that the partnership will start with “small quantities” that will increase if performance targets are met. The &lt;em&gt;Reuters &lt;/em&gt;report also gives a fairly wide window for deployment to allow Figure to train the bots to perform specific tasks — it could take anywhere from 12–24 months for them to actually be integrated into BMW’s manufacturing processes if it does identify a viable use for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="nuqbGn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/18/24043065/bmw-figure-robotics-humanoid-robot-workers-deployment"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/18/24043065/bmw-figure-robotics-humanoid-robot-workers-deployment</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jess Weatherbed</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-08T17:50:37-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-08T17:50:37-05:00</updated>
    <title>Samsung’s Ballie robot is now a projector that follows you around</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A picture of Ballie, which is small, yellow, and round, projecting an image on the floor in front of a golden retriever." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/twtoFvvBRyFrk4vm5fwfmSGg57Y=/353x0:2510x1438/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73036470/Screenshot_2024_01_08_at_4.26.53_PM.0.png" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ballie can entertain your pets by projecting things on the floor.&lt;/em&gt; | Screenshot: Wes Davis / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="NlZgPN"&gt;Samsung’s Ballie robot is back — and now, it’s a projector, too. At CES 2024, Samsung revealed an updated version of its round Ballie robot, and its signature new feature is that it can project things onto the floor, wall, or ceiling as it follows you around the home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="sJljr7"&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YBfSX3QiqDM"&gt;a charming video&lt;/a&gt;, Ballie (which Samsung once again showed off in a playful yellow color) had a bunch of clever projection tricks, including playing a video of a bird for a dog to watch, displaying a video call on a wall, and showing a fitness video for someone working out. Samsung also says in a press email that Ballie can automatically adjust the projection depending on how far away it is from the wall and your lighting conditions and that “it’s the world’s first projector to automatically detect people’s posture and facial angle and adjust the optimal projection angle for you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="fTqNC6"&gt;But in the video, the robot also served as a smart home assistant, turning on lights and dispensing dog food and texting somebody to tell them what it was doing. (The press email says that Ballie can control “air conditioners, lights, laundry machines, and more.”) Ballie can also follow you around the house and greet you when you come in the door. At the end of the video, Ballie filled a ceiling above the actors’ bed with a cosmic scene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="yGBM6t"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12213328"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="35Lozp"&gt;It was a really entertaining video — but unfortunately, it was &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; a video. At CES 2020, where Samsung &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/1/6/21054353/samsung-ballie-robot-ai-assistant-ces-2020"&gt;first showed off Ballie&lt;/a&gt;, the robot rolled around onstage, but this year the company only showed off the robot through the video. And Samsung didn’t share any details about if or when Ballie might be released or how much it could cost. Still, it was fun to see Ballie show up at CES once again; hopefully Samsung actually launches the product this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="UcV8ts"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update January 8th, 6:01PM ET&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;: Added further details from Samsung.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/8/24030713/samsung-ballie-robot-projector-ai-ces"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/8/24030713/samsung-ballie-robot-projector-ai-ces</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jay Peters</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-04T16:21:34-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-04T16:21:34-05:00</updated>
    <title>Google wrote a ‘Robot Constitution’ to make sure its new AI droids won’t kill us</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Google’s&amp;amp;nbsp;autonomous wheeled robot identifies objects on a table." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/lyYWD3KwBJG8R7iNaD2RU57Akgo=/169x0:1942x1182/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73023782/Screen_Shot_2024_01_04_at_10.55.35_AM.0.png" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Google&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="nD0lsk"&gt;The DeepMind robotics team has revealed &lt;a href="https://deepmind.google/discover/blog/shaping-the-future-of-advanced-robotics/"&gt;three new advances&lt;/a&gt; that it says will help robots make faster, better, and safer decisions in the wild. One includes a system for gathering training data with a “Robot Constitution” to make sure your robot office assistant can fetch you more printer paper — but without mowing down a human co-worker who happens to be in the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="T9AtXG"&gt;Google’s data gathering system, AutoRT, can use a visual language model (VLM) and large language model (LLM) working hand in hand to understand its environment, adapt to unfamiliar settings, and decide on appropriate tasks. The Robot Constitution, which is inspired by &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2014/5/17/5725248/is-asimovs-first-law-enough-to-keep-a-robot-bartender-from-harming"&gt;Isaac Asimov’s “Three Laws of Robotics,”&lt;/a&gt; is described as a set of “safety-focused prompts” instructing the LLM to avoid choosing tasks that involve humans, animals, sharp objects, and even electrical appliances.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="UeZEZ3"&gt;For additional safety, DeepMind programmed the robots to stop automatically if the force on its joints goes past a certain threshold and included a physical kill switch human operators can use to deactivate them. Over a period of seven months, Google deployed a fleet of 53 AutoRT robots into four different office buildings and conducted over 77,000 trials. Some robots were controlled remotely by human operators, while others operated either based on a script or completely autonomously &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/28/23811109/google-smart-robot-generative-ai"&gt;using Google’s Robotic Transformer (RT-2) AI learning model&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="In the example given in the post, the AutoRT’s VLM sees a countertop with a sponge and cloth on it, as well as other nearby individual objects such as a bag of chips and napkin. The robot’s LLM then suggests tasks such as placing the napkin on the countertop and opening the bag of chips." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ZkLwdUtK6JQbwT0MIn-1d61WZ6s=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25203936/Screen_Shot_2024_01_04_at_11.52.15_AM.png"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;AutoRT follows these four steps for each task.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="tF0lCT"&gt;The robots used in the trial look more utilitarian than flashy — equipped with only a camera, robot arm, and mobile base. “For each robot, the system uses a VLM to understand its environment and the objects within sight. Next, an LLM suggests a list of creative tasks that the robot could carry out, such as ‘Place the snack onto the countertop’ and plays the role of decision-maker to select an appropriate task for the robot to carry out,” noted Google in its blog post. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3Fd8HQcM53nPN5aq9LJC62x8BNg=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25204049/ezgif.com_optimize.gif"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Google&lt;/cite&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="JRrLLI"&gt;DeepMind’s other new tech includes SARA-RT, a neural network architecture designed to make the existing Robotic Transformer RT-2 more accurate and faster. It also announced RT-Trajectory, which adds 2D outlines to help robots better perform specific physical tasks, such as wiping down a table. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4bWrWT"&gt;We still seem to be a very long way from robots that serve drinks and fluff pillows autonomously, but when they’re available, they may have learned from a system like AutoRT.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/4/24025535/google-ai-robot-constitution-autort-deepmind-three-laws"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/4/24025535/google-ai-robot-constitution-autort-deepmind-three-laws</id>
    <author>
      <name>Amrita Khalid</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
