<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  TV Shows</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-15T11:29:48-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/tv/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/tv" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T11:29:48-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T11:29:48-04:00</updated>
    <title>Doctor Who’s new season streams in May</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A man wearing a leather trench coat, a striped blue and white shirt with a deep neck, and baggy trousers. Next to the man is a woman wearing a leather bomber jacket, a cardigan skirt, black stockings, and leather boos. Both the man and the woman are leaning on opposite sides of a circular hallway of what seems to be a spaceship." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/zwoH4OkFRdsxxMNiwOVCsWOXn5w=/0x0:2000x1333/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209592/jpp_who_170623_0005_embargoed_15_6415cf64.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Ncuti Gatwa as The Doctor, and Millie Gibson as Ruby Sunday. | BBC / Disney Plus&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="vmHrGh"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/25/23422663/doctor-who-disney-plus-bbc-streaming-announcement"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Doctor Who&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;’s most recent Christmas Special gave us a interesting taste of what showrunner Russell T Davies has been dreaming up for &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/12/23996697/doctor-who-the-giggle-bigeneration"&gt;Ncuti Gatwa’s run as the time traveling alien&lt;/a&gt;, and it won’t be long until we get to see what’s coming next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZKCoyF"&gt;Disney Plus announced today that &lt;em&gt;Doctor Who &lt;/em&gt;season 14 starring Ncuti Gatwa as the Fifteenth Doctor and Millie Gibson as his companion Ruby Sunday will premiere with two new episodes on May 10th in the US and internationally, except for the United Kingdom. UK viewers will be able to stream the new episodes via BBC iPlayer beginning at 12AM on May 11th (GMT) before it is available on BBC One later in the day. In &lt;a href="https://thewaltdisneycompany.com/doctor-who-debut-disney-plus/"&gt;a press release&lt;/a&gt; about the new season, Davies teased that the Doctor and Ruby’s adventures will involve “a terrifying secret that’s been spanning time and space for decades.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="T0xbhF"&gt;News of the premiere date comes months after news broke that, after starring in the show for just a single season, Gibson is already set to be replaced by actress Varada Sethu as the Doctor’s companion for reasons that have not been made clear.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101820/doctor-who-season-14-ncuti-gatwa-millie-gibson-premiere-date"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101820/doctor-who-season-14-ncuti-gatwa-millie-gibson-premiere-date</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-07T10:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-07T10:30:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Pokémon Horizons: The Series is an evolutionary fresh start for the anime</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A girl in a brown Japanese school uniform looking down at a green cat that’s facing her." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/b0RDlKazDdbbxtp5EKM-Ub-W5sk=/100x0:1180x720/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73188969/20230921113922_Liko_choosing_Sprigatito.0.png" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Netflix&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;Pokémon Horizons brings a refreshing new energy to the anime franchise by amping up the action and making the larger Pokémon world feel like a more cohesive place.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="3WTiZu"&gt;We were all sad to &lt;a href="https://www.polygon.com/23542929/pokemon-anime-ash-leaving-brock-misty-reunion"&gt;see Ash Ketchum go&lt;/a&gt;, but his still being the &lt;em&gt;Pokémon &lt;/em&gt;anime’s 10-year-old &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/11/23451915/pokemon-ash-ketchum-ultimate-journeys-champion"&gt;main character after 25 years of adventures&lt;/a&gt; was a huge part of why the show seemed stuck in the past. Though Ash never really changed all that much, the larger &lt;em&gt;Pokémon &lt;/em&gt;franchise did. And while the anime always took cues from the games, it also became very comfortable sticking to its own straightforward formula. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AtXiN4"&gt;Considering how &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23462858/pokemon-violet-scarlet-review-nintendo-switch"&gt;buggy the most recent generation of &lt;em&gt;Pokémon &lt;/em&gt;games has been&lt;/a&gt;, it might be hard to imagine the anime faring all that much better with or without its old protagonist. But &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/29/23980926/pokemon-horizons-netflix-premiere-date"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pokémon Horizons: The Series&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;— the franchise’s latest core animated series — has a surprisingly refreshing energy to it that makes it feel like the beginning of an exciting new era.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WULiuf"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pokémon Horizons &lt;/em&gt;has an unusually large cast of characters, but it primarily revolves around a trainer named Liko (Alejandra Reynoso) as she embarks on her first real &lt;em&gt;Pokémon&lt;/em&gt; journey. As a native Paldean who never previously traveled outside of her home region, Liko feels a bit out of her element as a new student at the Kanto region’s Indigo Academy, where young trainers from across the world come to learn the basics of raising pokémon. But Liko knows that stepping outside of her comfort zone is good for her, and from the moment she meets her first partner pokémon Sprigatito (Kira Buckland), there’s no doubt in her mind that she’s on the right path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="DSh2BO"&gt;&lt;div style="left: 0; width: 100%; height: 0; position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Sw7MoYbJ4Lc?rel=0" style="top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute; border: 0;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="accelerometer; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share;"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="P6Whsd"&gt;The concept of children regularly attending school rather than being free to roam around at their leisure has been featured in the &lt;em&gt;Pokémon &lt;/em&gt;anime before, but the emphasis &lt;em&gt;Horizons &lt;/em&gt;puts on Liko being a student feels very much like the series expanding on the educational theme of the &lt;em&gt;Scarlet &lt;/em&gt;and &lt;em&gt;Violet&lt;/em&gt; games. At the Indigo Academy, studies come before anything else, and Liko’s keen on staying in all of her teachers’ good graces. But when Amethio (Daman Mills) — a menacing boy with a Ceruledge — shows up one day demanding that Liko hand over her grandmother’s mysterious pendant, she knows her life is in danger. And while Liko and Sprigatito put up a good fight, it’s only thanks to the arrival of pokémon professor Friede (Crispin Freeman) that she’s able to get away safely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NxV8Bx"&gt;Though &lt;em&gt;Horizons &lt;/em&gt;is set in the same world as previous seasons of &lt;em&gt;Pokémon&lt;/em&gt;, there’s a complexity to its central story and an intensity to its battles that makes it feel like a drastically different kind of show that’s aiming for a slightly older, more action-oriented audience. Whereas Ash just wanted to make friends and battle for glory, Liko’s on the run and in the thick of discovering how many secrets her family has kept hidden from her. What feels most distinct about the new show, though, is how Liko’s story quickly becomes focused on her exploring the world with Friede and his crew — the Rising Volt Tacklers — on their massive airship.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZHA78r"&gt;By introducing so many distinct supporting characters like Mollie (Erica Mendez), a pink-haired doctor too cool for the Pokémon Center, and Orla (Mara Junot), the Rising Volt Tacklers’ resident engineer, &lt;em&gt;Pokémon Horizons&lt;/em&gt; is able to shift gears between being a weekly one-off adventure series and one that’s telling a more drawn-out story. Once Liko’s with the crew, &lt;em&gt;Horizons &lt;/em&gt;shifts its focus to other members like secret streamer Dot (Faye Mata) and her gourmand uncle Murdock (Major Attaway), with episodes that take the Rising Volt Tacklers to a number of different regions in quick succession.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="pjFh7h"&gt;The almost &lt;em&gt;One Piece&lt;/em&gt;-like way the Rising Volt Tacklers race across the globe makes &lt;em&gt;Horizons&lt;/em&gt;’ take on the &lt;em&gt;Pokémon &lt;/em&gt;world feel more cohesive and connected than in previous seasons of the show or most of the games. But as different as the new show feels, you can still see &lt;em&gt;Horizons&lt;/em&gt; paying homage to the original series through its second main protagonist, a very Ash-like boy named Roy (Anjali Kunapaneni) who has a special relationship with a legendary pokémon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/DXpELtlDDcWIobefvA9lgwRzCdQ=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25317611/HZ006.png"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="cQCnbt"&gt;Because Liko’s kind of a wallflower and more of a team player compared to Ash — who was a stereotypical shonen protagonist focused on his own priorities — &lt;em&gt;Horizons &lt;/em&gt;feels like a proper ensemble series that wants you to appreciate how much more there is to the world of &lt;em&gt;Pokémon &lt;/em&gt;than battling. Of course, battles are still important here, and Liko’s character development is most clearly reflected in the way that she and Sprigatito become more powerful as they face new opponents. But the exciting thing about &lt;em&gt;Horizons &lt;/em&gt;is how open it feels in terms of being able to take off in new directions as its characters evolve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8WIyJj"&gt;While &lt;em&gt;Horizons&lt;/em&gt;’ potential to wander even further off the traditional &lt;em&gt;Pokémon &lt;/em&gt;anime beaten path is great, it’s easy to imagine it also making the series a bit harder to jump into compared to the original series. But the show’s early episodes feel perfectly calibrated for newcomers to the franchise and diehard fans alike, and with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/27/24083767/pokemon-legends-z-a-nintendo-switch-2025-launch-date"&gt;the next big &lt;em&gt;Pokémon &lt;/em&gt;game not dropping until 2025&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Horizons &lt;/em&gt;should be just the thing to tide everyone over while we wait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NLw1Sh"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pokémon Horizons: The Series &lt;/em&gt;is streaming on Netflix now.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24081618/pokemon-horizons-series-netflix-show-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24081618/pokemon-horizons-series-netflix-show-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-07T10:01:58-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-07T10:01:58-05:00</updated>
    <title>Dive into the world of Netflix’s 3 Body Problem</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/hzXF2nNFlN62QOkdVzPsrYwwVs8=/0x0:3600x2400/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73171118/3BP_102_Unit_03502RC.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;ED MILLER/NETFLIX&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Check out all of The Verge’s coverage of Netflix’s upcoming 3 Body Problem series based on Cixin Liu’s epic sci-fi novel.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="1Re15H"&gt;The idea of trying to adapt &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/7/24062452/three-body-problem-audiobook-rosalind-chao-netflix"&gt;Cixin Liu’s &lt;em&gt;The Three-Body Problem&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;for a Western audience &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/28/23375177/netflix-3-body-problem-tudum-db-weiss-david-benioff"&gt;sounds wild at first blush&lt;/a&gt; given how complex and deeply rooted in Chinese identity the book is. But every &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23955973/netflix-3-body-problem-teaser-trailer-release-date"&gt;glimpse of Netflix’s new series based on the epic novel&lt;/a&gt; has made it feel like showrunners David Benioff and D. B. Weiss and executive producer Alexander Woo might have figured out a way to pull it off. Between the show’s focus on physics-defying mysteries, metaversal gaming, and humanity making first contact with otherworldly beings, Netflix’s &lt;em&gt;3 Body Problem &lt;/em&gt;seems poised to capture viewers’ imaginations with a fascinating, larger-than-life story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="pjGcvI"&gt;&lt;em&gt;3 Body Problem &lt;/em&gt;has been on &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;’s radar from the moment Netflix first announced it, and we’ll have even more updates, reviews, and interviews to share as we get closer to the show’s March 21st release date. And given how much more there is to this tale beyond the first book, you’re probably going to want to keep an eye on this feed for even more news about potential future seasons of the show.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24083744/netflix-3-body-problem-trailers-review-interview"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24083744/netflix-3-body-problem-trailers-review-interview</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
      <name>Andrew Webster</name>
      <name>Nick Statt</name>
      <name>Andrew Liptak</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-07T09:02:08-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-07T09:02:08-05:00</updated>
    <title>Amazon’s new Fallout trailer looks just like the games: grim, goofy, and gruesome</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A still photo of actress Ella Purnell in the live-action Fallout TV show on Amazon Prime Video." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/LvF6MmiwrpRIGfhXTipKLIUboyQ=/298x0:2161x1242/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73188736/FALLOUT_S1_035_025_vR059.00086508_3000.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Amazon&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="aKPmhf"&gt;It’s still too early to say if Amazon’s live-action take on &lt;em&gt;Fallout&lt;/em&gt; will be any good. But &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23984628/fallout-trailer-amazon-prime-video"&gt;the first few trailers&lt;/a&gt; at least make one thing clear: the show seems like it’s nailing the distinct vibe of the games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xCrLSJ"&gt;The newly released second trailer follows a lot of the same beats as the first, tracking a Vault Dweller named Lucy (Ella Purnell) heading out into the Wasteland only to discover how dangerous things have become two centuries after the apocalypse. The show looks gritty and violent, as you’d expect from a post-apocalyptic series, but also balances that out with a goofy sense of humor and playfully retrofuturistic style. Case in point: a Mister Orderly bot that simply wants to harvest Lucy’s organs. No big deal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZCvjbB"&gt;Aside from that, the trailer is filled with classic &lt;em&gt;Fallout&lt;/em&gt; details that will make fans of the games feel right at home, from the copious Stimpaks to some impressive-looking power armor. When The Ink Spots start singing “I Don’t Want to Set the World on Fire,” it’s hard not to think about the end of the world. It also looks like the series will spend a bit more time exploring the before times; the trailer is bookended by a sales pitch for the vaults that wouldn’t be out of place in &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23597881/hello-tomorrow-review-apple-tv-plus"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hello Tomorrow!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="IJJEFo"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fallout&lt;/em&gt; is directed by &lt;em&gt;Westworld&lt;/em&gt; co-creator Jonathan Nolan, with Geneva Robertson-Dworet and Graham Wagner serving as showrunners. It also stars Aaron Moten, Walton Goggins, and Kyle MacLachlan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rDZYM2"&gt;The show starts streaming on April 11th — one day earlier than previously announced. And instead of a weekly schedule, all eight episodes will drop at once.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24092492/fallout-trailer-amazon-bethesda-date"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24092492/fallout-trailer-amazon-bethesda-date</id>
    <author>
      <name>Andrew Webster</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-06T10:50:49-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-06T10:50:49-05:00</updated>
    <title>Netflix’s Avatar: The Last Airbender has been renewed for two more seasons</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A tight shot of a woman with a face painted in white with red eye shadow. The woman’s wearing a golden ornamental hat, and a a green warrior’s outfit." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/4hx0KAqAunDC5kz69Z4x1hnCl4k=/575x0:3026x1634/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73186304/Avatar__The_Last_Airbender_n_S1_00_36_42_04.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Yvonne Chapman as Avatar Kyoshi. | Netflix&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="nAbbsN"&gt;The season 1 finale of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24071094/netflix-avatar-last-airbender-review"&gt;Netflix’s live-action &lt;em&gt;Avatar: The Last Airbender&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;made it fairly clear that more episodes were probably on the way, and now the streamer’s making it official.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="6F6YEK"&gt;Netflix announced today that it has greenlit Albert Kim’s take on &lt;em&gt;Avatar: The Last Airbender &lt;/em&gt;for another two seasons that will “bring The Legend of Aang to its proper conclusion.”  Netflix also shared a new teaser image suggesting that, like the animated series, the live-action show’s second and third seasons will focus on Team Avatar’s adventures in the Earth Kingdom and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24050899/netflix-avatar-the-last-airbender-dallas-liu-interview"&gt;Fire Nation&lt;/a&gt;, respectively. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/bUUW5XDFIbiqVhhK8JiK9fpwWFk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25321054/EN_US_ATLA_s2s3_Announcement_Vertical_27x40_sRGB_PRE.jpeg"&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="6YP6fE"&gt;There’s no word yet on when production on the new seasons will begin or when we might expect to see them on Netflix.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092243/netflix-avatar-the-last-airbender-season-2-renewal"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092243/netflix-avatar-the-last-airbender-season-2-renewal</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-05T13:44:46-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-05T13:44:46-05:00</updated>
    <title>Max is getting in on the big streaming password crackdown</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Warner Bros. Discovery’s CEO, David Zaslav." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/mOf7jbQrbbPivCWj5AJrvOLwoz0=/306x0:3470x2109/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73184253/Screen_Shot_2023_04_12_at_1.09.40_PM__2_.0.png" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Warner Bros. Discovery&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="dok8GJ"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/max-password-sharing-crackdown-streaming-netflix-disney-plus/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt; reports&lt;/a&gt; that Warner Bros. Discovery (WBD) is gearing up to implement a new set of restrictions designed to prevent subscribers from sharing their passwords with people who aren’t paying for the service themselves. Speaking at &lt;a href="https://seekingalpha.com/article/4675991-warner-bros-discovery-inc-wbd-morgan-stanley-2024-technology-media-and-telecom-conference"&gt;Morgan Stanley’s Technology, Media &amp;amp; Telecom conference&lt;/a&gt; on Monday, WBD head of global streaming and games JB Perrette said that the company plans to launch its crackdown some time in late 2024. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="SoVIU4"&gt;“We’re launching in a bunch of European markets as we go into the second and third quarter,” Perette said. “And password sharing crack down, which, obviously, Netflix has implemented extremely successfully. We’re going to be doing that starting later this year and into ‘25, which is another growth opportunity for us.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gjRLjd"&gt;Max’s decision comes just weeks after &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/7/24065158/disney-plus-password-account-sharing-summer-2024"&gt;Disney Plus&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/31/24057641/hulu-password-sharing-crackdown"&gt;Hulu&lt;/a&gt; both updated their terms of service to ban users from sharing login credentials with people living outside of their households. Those moves came in response to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/23/23734725/netflix-password-sharing-us-pricing-streaming"&gt;Netflix rolling out new password sharing restrictions in 2023&lt;/a&gt; in an effort to combat its stalling signup rate — an issue many platforms are now facing as the streaming wars mature. Max’s password crackdown is likely going to lead to more than a few new signups, which might please shareholders in the short term. But between WBD’s other recent &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/9/24067496/coyote-vs-acme-amazon-netflix-paramount-rejected-offers-theatrical"&gt;ham-fisted attempts at getting its finances straight&lt;/a&gt;, and the fact that the streaming space as a whole is feeling increasingly hostile toward consumers, this next crackdown could just as easily become the sort of thing that drives some customers away.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091397/max-password-sharing-crackdown-netflix"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091397/max-password-sharing-crackdown-netflix</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-05T12:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-05T12:30:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>The best entertainment of 2024</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A still photo of Rebecca Ferguson in Dune: Part Two." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ILSQrDY5-7T-1lyUYDJ3BECigGU=/720x0:3294x1716/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73183419/rev_1_DUN2_FP_0120r_High_Res_JPEG.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dune: Part Two.&lt;/em&gt; | Image: Warner Bros. Pictures&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="LBbit4"&gt;Finding something to watch or play can sometimes feel like work — there’s just so much out there vying for your free time. That’s true whether you’re heading to a theater, browsing the many streaming platforms, or looking for a new video game. It’s easy to get overwhelmed with choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NPrr4k"&gt;So, as we’ve done in &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23613289/best-games-movie-tv-entertainment-2023"&gt;years&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22949266/best-games-movies-tv-2022"&gt;past&lt;/a&gt;, we’re collecting all of our favorite releases from 2024 in one place. The goal is to make your decision-making a little easier. That could mean highlighting anything from &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24086957/dune-part-two-movie-review"&gt;an anticipated movie that actually lives up to the hype&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24082252/balatro-review-poker-roguelike-videogame"&gt;a surprise indie game that takes the world by storm&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="V6kIeN"&gt;And we’ll be updating this page all year long as we continue to check out the latest in film, television, and gaming — so stay tuned.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/24090208/best-entertainment-2024-games-film-tv-streaming"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/24090208/best-entertainment-2024-games-film-tv-streaming</id>
    <author>
      <name>The Verge Staff</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-02T09:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-02T09:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Halo’s latest episode showed us the best a Spartan could be</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Image from Halo episode 4, “Reach,” featuring Natasha Culzac as Spartan Riz-028 wielding a large minigun as sparks fly around her." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/d7Jwgfkpsu4Dz4M3XUjKdRwxyzk=/0x0:1920x1280/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73177589/Halo_204_AS_1103_1020_RT.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Adrienn Szabo / Paramount Plus&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="EHVQZh"&gt;When &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24063618/halo-season-2-premiere-review-paramount-plus"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Halo &lt;/em&gt;season 2&lt;/a&gt; finally covered the fall of the planet Reach — a foundational, emotional moment in &lt;em&gt;Halo&lt;/em&gt; lore — I figured that I’d write a few words of praise about it. But then I saw the episode after, “Aleria,” and that episode, not “Reach,” is the one that truly delivers a &lt;em&gt;Halo&lt;/em&gt; experience worthy of the games yet so wonderfully unlike them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GFZKdL"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spoilers for &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Halo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; season 2 to follow&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="S1MGBZ"&gt;One of the elements missing from &lt;em&gt;Halo&lt;/em&gt; season 1 &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23132662/halo-tv-series-season-1-review-paramount-plus"&gt;was the camaraderie between Spartans&lt;/a&gt;.  The first half of &lt;em&gt;Halo&lt;/em&gt;’s second season &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/10/24067616/pablo-schreiber-halo-season-two-paramount-plus"&gt;better developed and defined the relationships of Silver Team&lt;/a&gt; (Master Chief Petty Officer John-117, Riz-028, Kai-125, and Vannak-134); specifically, Riz-028 (Natasha Culzac) and Vannak-134 (Bentley Kalu), who were all but neglected in season 1, really got moments to shine in season 2. Riz, after suffering a debilitating injury, struggles with keeping up with the physical and emotional demands of being a Spartan. Meanwhile, Vannak, after removing his emotion regulator chip, is cultivating a peaceful life for himself beyond his Mjolnir armor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="IsCCxb"&gt;It was touching and funny to see Vannak show off as an animal facts guy who likes to feed the local pigeons while Riz suffers a bit of embarrassment realizing the guy she’s developed a crush on is in a committed relationship. But &lt;em&gt;Halo&lt;/em&gt; is also a story of war. And when it comes to the planet Reach, in the form of a devastating surprise attack, Riz, Vannak, and the rest of Team Silver are called into action — and some of them don’t make it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EIwCYY"&gt;I expected the deaths of notable characters in the “Reach” episode. It pained me a little bit to see Vannak go because viewers were given such precious little time with him. Captain Keyes’ (Danny Sapani) death also surprised me since that character dies elsewhere in the games, and I didn’t think the show would kill him off so soon. Ultimately, “Reach” was a decent episode with bits of really good action but lacked the emotional weight an episode based on one of &lt;em&gt;the &lt;/em&gt;moments in &lt;em&gt;Halo&lt;/em&gt; lore should have.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Natasha Culzac as Riz-028 in Halo episode 5, season 1, streaming on Paramount Plus." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/I0F7h2ahLK8vH8nM885ck7Vhx54=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313769/Halo_105_4289_RT_v3__1_.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Adrienn Szabo / Paramount Plus&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spartan Riz-028, you will always be famous.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="XGWfYo"&gt;The next episode, “Aleria,” picks up right where “Reach” ended, with the remaining Spartans and Dr. Halsey surrounded by Covenant soldiers with no chance of escape. But then, as so often happens in this series, &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/JMYrKTU8Hmc?si=mKq9CuaPXTDhzWnt"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Halo&lt;/em&gt; delivered hope&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rY2m9i"&gt;As everyone piled onto the ship, the Covenant kept getting closer. Riz, though injured and without her armor (nobody has any armor because plot) jumped off the ship with naught but pistols, ostensibly to keep the Covenant at bay to give the ship time to take off safely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="DRDf62"&gt;I started screaming, incensed that the show was about to kill yet another character I had come to care for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TGQZ6M"&gt;But then, she came back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="aNLgih"&gt;Riz returned carrying Vannak’s body, and my indignant screams morphed into equally loud sobs. That wasn’t her noble sacrifice suicide run. She just went back for her friend, her comrade, her brother.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gD8JgH"&gt;In that moment, Riz-028 delivered the best portrayal of a Spartan seen outside the series’ many games, while the show itself subverted my expectations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="pDVsAM"&gt;I was ready to begrudgingly accept Riz’s death as I had Vannak’s and Keyes’. After all, she’s a Black character, as were Vannak and Keyes, while a previous heroic death in the “Reach” episode featured yet another Black character. In a media climate where characters of color are often sacrificed as a way to raise stakes or heighten emotion without threatening a show’s “more valuable” white stars, Riz’s death would’ve fit right in. Furthermore, Riz is a Spartan — so long as she’s not John-117, she’s expendable.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Pablo Schreiber as Master Chief in Halo episode 4, season 2, streaming on Paramount+ 2024." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Jxjb-7HZ4rQO4LyvtUUuItjdLlk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25313775/Halo_204_AS_1103_0817_RT.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Adrienn Szabo / Paramount Plus&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Astounding that the big hero moment in “Aleria” didn’t feature Master Chief at all.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="4un0vK"&gt;Afterward, as everyone regroups and recovers on the planet Aleria, Riz decides to stay behind as John swears vengeance on the military leaders responsible for abandoning Reach to its fate. John vehemently opposes this, attempting to guilt her by asking what she intends to do about their lost planet and comrades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="J0hmQN"&gt;“I’m going to live,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Grw35i"&gt;For &lt;em&gt;Halo&lt;/em&gt;, that’s profound. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EEKT03"&gt;Spartans are always fighting. &lt;em&gt;Always.&lt;/em&gt; There’s an &lt;a href="https://www.halopedia.org/ONI_Directive_930"&gt;in-universe military directive&lt;/a&gt; that mandates Spartans never be declared “KIA” but “missing in action,” not only to reinforce their mythos as the invincible soldier but a perpetual one as well — one who’s always still out there, still fighting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7RgneV"&gt;When they can’t fight, like the Spartans who survived augmentation with permanent disabilities, they still serve in the military in some capacity. Even when there are no more battles to fight, Master Chief himself never puts down his gun, famously telling Cortana at the end of &lt;em&gt;Halo 3&lt;/em&gt; to wake him when he’s needed again. And when we see Spartans die, it is always in service of the mission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HQofhe"&gt;But TV &lt;em&gt;Halo,&lt;/em&gt; for the first time in the series, dares to imagine something different for a Spartan: &lt;em&gt;life&lt;/em&gt;, one beyond fighting, serving, or death. And it was beautiful to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="9jTxAz"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/2/24087962/halo-paramount-plus-episode-five-aleria"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/2/24087962/halo-paramount-plus-episode-five-aleria</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ash Parrish</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-29T11:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-29T11:30:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>The golden age of DVDs isn’t over yet for anime fans</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo collage featuring screenshots from two animes licensed through Discotek." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/nyGkBDGTmRrIII7IoJu7EhvaNko=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73173202/236948_PHYSICAL_MEDIA_DISCOTEK_CVIRGINIA_copy.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Collage by Cath Virginia / The Verge | Images courtesy of Discotek&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;Physical media might seem like it’s on its deathbed, but the anime DVD and Blu-ray industry couldn’t be more alive.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="GtvlCC"&gt;Production studios still regularly release their latest, greatest films and series on DVD and Blu-ray. But over the past few years, it has become increasingly clear that physical media just isn’t as much of a priority as it used to be for Hollywood’s biggest players. You could see it in the way that &lt;em&gt;Barbarian &lt;/em&gt;— one of the biggest sleeper hits of 2022 — &lt;a href="https://www.giantfreakinrobot.com/ent/physical-media-barbarian.html"&gt;came and went without a physical release&lt;/a&gt; and in the way Disney only seemed keen on putting projects like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/21/23839994/disney-plus-mandalorian-loki-wandavision-blu-ray"&gt;&lt;em&gt;WandaVision&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Loki&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;The Mandalorian&lt;/em&gt; on disc&lt;/a&gt; years after their streaming debuts. Given the way that the pivot to streaming has decimated most brick-and-mortar retail and rental entertainment businesses, it has often felt like we’re hurtling toward a future where people simply won’t be able to physically own copies of their favorite mainstream hits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="IrlUQM"&gt;But as dire as the situation seems, there are still a handful of small anime-focused outfits working to give fans the kinds of robustly featured physical home releases they crave. And at a time when it has become clear that viewers should never expect their streaming favorites to always be accessible, the work these smaller companies are doing to preserve beloved pieces of art, and literally get it into people’s hands, feels more important than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4J5ePb"&gt;Brands like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/8/24065940/funimation-shutdown-crunchyroll-digital-library"&gt;Funimation&lt;/a&gt;, Viz Media, and Discotek are typically associated with newly remastered anime classics. And it’s through partnerships with postproduction companies like &lt;a href="https://www.mediaocd.com/"&gt;MediaOCD&lt;/a&gt; that they’re able to bring those types of projects to market as physical discs. According to MediaOCD founder and CEO Justin Sevakis, many niche publishers have found success by &lt;a href="https://www.polygon.com/23681111/anime-home-video-blu-ray-dvd-thriving-dragon-ball-evangelion"&gt;playing specifically to the small, passionate communities&lt;/a&gt; of fans who want to own a piece of the media they love. Though major studios don’t usually consider physical releases for projects that aren’t expected to move at least 50,000 units, according to Sevakis, “a good hit in the niche Blu-ray space will move something like 5,000.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="FXrdLW"&gt;“We’re not talking huge numbers here,” he said. “But those are 5,000 people that really loved that anime or show or what have you. And because they get excited over the idea of physically owning media like this, I think it’s imperative on us — the people that put these products out — to make something special and definitive.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="8qHDAa"&gt;&lt;div style="left: 0; width: 100%; height: 0; position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XwGQj4V1W-w?rel=0" style="top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute; border: 0;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="accelerometer; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share;"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="xAZxA3"&gt;Before Sevakis got into remastering anime professionally, he was a high schooler obsessed with &lt;em&gt;Project A-ko &lt;/em&gt;and making VHS fan subs of series like &lt;em&gt;Kodocha&lt;/em&gt; by hooking up a LaserDisc player to his Amiga in order to twitch-time subtitles in by hand. Producing those early fan subs lit a passion in him — not just for the specific series he loved but also for keeping tabs on all the other anime that was making its way to the market. And after realizing that there weren’t really any websites making it easy for people to follow anime news, Sevakis took it upon himself to get &lt;em&gt;Anime News Network &lt;/em&gt;off the ground in 1998.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7Kjxob"&gt;Sevakis’ time at &lt;em&gt;ANN&lt;/em&gt; was brief, but his interest in anime never faded. After a chance encounter on a plane with the president of Central Park Media, Sevakis landed a gig producing subtitles for series like &lt;em&gt;Project A-ko&lt;/em&gt; as well as “some of the most flesh-crawlingly awful hentai you’ve ever seen” at one of the biggest anime distributors in America.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="Tex4f1"&gt;&lt;q&gt;“When discs became commoditized, there was a lack of care that became very evident.”&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="CdtvMz"&gt;Sevakis remembers the early days of DVD as a time of experimentation for studios that were still figuring out how to get people into the habit of buying media on the new format. “It was good because a lot of cool stuff was made, like a lot of really nifty, innovative bonus features that you just don’t see today that really took advantage of what DVD could do interactivity-wise, like little minigames,” Sevakis described. “But after DVDs became commoditized, the thinking shifted to, ‘Well, people don’t really buy a disc for the bonus features. That doesn’t move the needle sales-wise.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="LB09EI"&gt;Looking back at the menu-focused minigames that were included with the DVD releases of films like &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p5ja2h1aNv4&amp;amp;ab_channel=Boogadrew%27sDumpingGrounds"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Who Framed Roger Rabbit&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AY-PHM7nTcs&amp;amp;ab_channel=FullMotionFun"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Charlie and the Chocolate Factory&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8uP8NPjxz8Y&amp;amp;ab_channel=ABonDVD"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shrek&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, it &lt;em&gt;is &lt;/em&gt;somewhat hard to imagine people rushing to buy those movie discs just for their bonus features. But as simplistic as those features were, they gave viewers a small taste of how much more interactive DVDs could be compared to VHS tapes. But as DVDs became the new standard, those types of features were the first things to be cut for production costs, and Sevakis points to that initial period of paring back as one of the reasons that mainstream Blu-ray releases today tend to feel pretty bare-bones. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KwfZc7"&gt;“When discs became commoditized, there was a lack of care that became very evident,” Sevakis said. “There’s always been an antipathy towards the end consumer, which might be why they’re not doing super well at direct-to-consumer.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="qAa6oh"&gt;In 2023, the top-selling DVD in the US (&lt;em&gt;Black Panther: Wakanda Forever&lt;/em&gt;) moved &lt;a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/187013/dvd-sales-in-the-us-in-2010-by-units-sold/"&gt;just over 300,000 units&lt;/a&gt; — a far cry from the &lt;a href="https://www.the-numbers.com/home-market/dvd-sales/2013"&gt;millions&lt;/a&gt; that used to put films on the charts just a decade ago. Sales of physical media have &lt;a href="https://www.animenewsnetwork.com/news/2023-02-14/japanese-home-video-sales-down-by-16.1-percent-in-2022/.194888"&gt;similarly been on a downward trend in Japan&lt;/a&gt; for the better part of the past 20 years. But between &lt;em&gt;Demon Slayer – Kimetsu No Yaiba – The Movie: Mugen Train &lt;/em&gt;becoming the highest-grossing Japanese film in global box office history and moving record numbers of Blu-rays in the process, it’s obvious that audiences are still interested in the genre. And with Sony doubling down on its &lt;a href="https://variety.com/2023/film/news/sony-strategic-plans-music-games-anime-india-1235617171/"&gt;investment in becoming&lt;/a&gt; a bigger player in &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/8/24065940/funimation-shutdown-crunchyroll-digital-library"&gt;the anime streaming market&lt;/a&gt;, it’s clear that bigger studios have come to see that interest in anime as a moneymaking opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="QT59om"&gt;&lt;div style="left: 0; width: 100%; height: 0; position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/G2xtJqKNXmE?rel=0" style="top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute; border: 0;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="accelerometer; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share;"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="RRQIlh"&gt;The advent of services like Crunchyroll — which subsumed Funimation as part of Sony’s plans for anime dominance — has made legally accessing popular Japanese-produced animated series and films easier than ever before. But much in the same way that subscribers to other platforms have watched titles suddenly vanish from their libraries with little to no warning, there are no guarantees that &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/8/24065940/funimation-shutdown-crunchyroll-digital-library"&gt;digital offerings from anime streamers will always be there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="x5E6JR"&gt;Even if people like Sevakis didn’t pour time and energy into painstakingly remastering the projects coded onto the Blu-rays they’re selling, the simple fact that the discs will just play if you’ve got the right equipment on hand would keep people buying them. A deeper and more important reality, though, is that physical releases have also played a key role in the preservation of classic media. It’s only because Sevakis and the Discotek team were able to find an old Betamax tape of &lt;em&gt;Nutcracker Fantasy &lt;/em&gt;— Sanrio’s 1979 stop-motion feature based on the Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky ballet and E.T.A. Hoffmann’s 1816 story — that they were able to produce a remaster of the film’s international cut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3tcSR0"&gt;Sevakis could not tell me the number of times during the production process “where it’s like, ‘Oh, we need this English dub, but the masters are gone. Better find an old DVD,’” only to then realize that the DVD in question never came out. That’s when the hunt turns to eBay, where, luck willing, there might be a collector with an old VHS they’re willing to part ways with. That willingness, Sevakis insisted, has been crucial to the continued existence of media that would otherwise probably become lost in the streaming age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="J8x7oD"&gt;“It’s easy to blame the studios, but I’ve been in a fast-paced production environment, and I know what it’s like to not have time or bandwidth to deal with archiving stuff after you’re done,” Sevakis said. “But it’s important to make sure that films are preserved and not ephemera, and things only become ephemera when no one saves them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dxZuIq"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="poOU4Z"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24062618/anime-dvd-bluray-discotek-physical-media"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24062618/anime-dvd-bluray-discotek-physical-media</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-28T16:43:20-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-28T16:43:20-05:00</updated>
    <title>Apple is turning William Gibson’s Neuromancer into a TV series</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="U.S. Author William Gibson attends the 7th editition of the Festival of Literature at Literature House on May 26, 2007 in Rome, Italy." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/7n88TZ-N4zvEjgiH1jydKJcSRaA=/0x0:3000x2000/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73171526/81237818.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;William Gibson.&lt;/em&gt; | Photo by Elisabetta A. Villa/WireImage&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="INw8HC"&gt;Another sci-fi adaptation is making its way to Apple TV Plus. The streamer announced that it’s adapting William Gibson’s seminal cyberpunk novel &lt;em&gt;Neuromancer&lt;/em&gt; into a 10-episode series. Graham Roland (&lt;em&gt;Lost&lt;/em&gt;,&lt;em&gt; Jack Ryan&lt;/em&gt;) will serve as showrunner, while JD Dillard (&lt;em&gt;Utopia&lt;/em&gt;) will direct the first episode. (Both will also be executive producers on the series.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="6UBauc"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"William Gibson interview: time travel, virtual reality, and his new book","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2014/10/28/7083625/william-gibson-interview-time-travel-virtual-reality-and-the-peripheral"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="Cd6tmo"&gt;That’s about all we know right now. There are no details on when the series might start streaming or who will star. In &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/02/apple-tv-announces-neuromancer-new-drama-based-on-the-multi-award-winning-science-fiction-novel-by-william-gibson/"&gt;a press release&lt;/a&gt;, Apple said that the show “will follow a damaged, top-rung super-hacker named Case who is thrust into a web of digital espionage and high stakes crime with his partner Molly, a razor-girl assassin with mirrored eyes aiming to pull a heist on a corporate dynasty with untold secrets.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="9ztybU"&gt;This is also not the first adaptation of &lt;em&gt;Neuromancer&lt;/em&gt;, which originally came out 1984 as Gibson’s debut novel. Its been &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neuromancer_(video_game)"&gt;turned into a video game&lt;/a&gt;, a graphic novel, and is &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2017/8/9/16121760/neuromancer-movie-deadpool-director-tim-miller"&gt;reportedly being made into a movie&lt;/a&gt; as well. (In 2022, Amazon adapted another Gibson novel — &lt;em&gt;The Peripheral&lt;/em&gt; — into &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23412567/the-peripheral-review-amazon-prime-video-william-gibson-book"&gt;a live-action streaming series&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="YRjlBQ"&gt;Whenever it does premiere, &lt;em&gt;Neuromancer&lt;/em&gt; will join an ever-growing lineup of sci-fi on Apple TV Plus. So far that has included series like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23786940/foundation-season-2-david-goyer-interview-apple-tv-plus"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Foundation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;For All Mankind&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23711259/silo-review-season-1-apple-tv-plus"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Silo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23932047/invasion-season-2-review-apple-tv-plus"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Invasion&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23913217/monarch-legacy-of-monsters-apple-nycc-preview-godzilla"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monarch&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Constellation&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24065198/constellation-review-apple-tv-plus"&gt;which premiered earlier this month&lt;/a&gt;. An adaptation of Martha Wells’ &lt;em&gt;The Murderbot Diaries&lt;/em&gt; is &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/14/24001803/murderbot-series-apple-tv-plus-alexander-skarsgard"&gt;also in the works&lt;/a&gt;, starring Alexander Skarsgård.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24086056/apple-tv-plus-neuromancer-streaming-series-william-gibson"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24086056/apple-tv-plus-neuromancer-streaming-series-william-gibson</id>
    <author>
      <name>Andrew Webster</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
