<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Ubers</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-15T12:14:39-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/uber/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/uber" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T12:14:39-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T12:14:39-04:00</updated>
    <title>Uber and Lyft to leave Minneapolis over ‘deeply flawed’ pay rules</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Uber company name written on a multicolored background." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/O6GRXLzYMSHtZfvE982hb1v3olc=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209741/acastro_STK106__01.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration by Alex Castro / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="TqD504"&gt;Uber and Lyft are pulling their services out of Minneapolis after the city council passed an ordinance that will increase drivers’ pay. Both companies say they will no longer offer ridesharing services in the city when the ordinance goes into effect on May 1st.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="PqTda0"&gt;The ordinance, which guarantees drivers a minimum rate of $1.40 per mile and 51 cents per minute while carrying a rider, was &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/minneapolis-city-council-uber-lyft-rideshare-ordinance-vote/"&gt;first passed last week&lt;/a&gt; but &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/minneapolis-mayor-vetoes-minimum-wage-rideshare-ordinance/"&gt;later vetoed&lt;/a&gt; by Minneapolis Mayor Jacob Frey. The City Council &lt;a href="https://minnesotareformer.com/2024/03/14/minneapolis-council-overrides-mayors-veto-of-uber-and-lyft-minimum-rates/"&gt;voted 10–3 to override&lt;/a&gt; the veto on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xms1gF"&gt;Lyft spokesperson CJ Macklin calls the ordinance “deeply flawed,” as &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/minneapolis-mayor-discusses-recently-passed-rideshare-ordinance/"&gt;the rates were determined&lt;/a&gt; before the state released a study detailing how much drivers would have to be paid to earn Minneapolis’ $15.57 per hour minimum wage. &lt;a href="https://dli.mn.gov/sites/default/files/pdf/TNC_driver_earnings_analysis_pay_standard_options_report_030824.pdf"&gt;The study&lt;/a&gt; analyzed over 18 million trips taken in 2022. &lt;a href="https://www.startribune.com/minnesota-uber-and-lyft-drivers-often-earn-less-than-minimum-wage-state-study-says/600349568/"&gt;It found&lt;/a&gt; that drivers could earn the city’s minimum wage — while also accounting for health insurance, paid leave, and retirement savings — with rates of $1.21 per mile and 49 cents per minute, lower than what the city council approved. &lt;em&gt;“&lt;/em&gt;We support a minimum earning standard for drivers,” Macklin says, “but it should be done in an honest way that keeps the service affordable for riders.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="o7pPAD"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"How Uber learned to stop fighting and play nice with taxis ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/26/23888950/uber-taxi-driver-referral-third-party-los-angeles"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zaxeQX"&gt;Uber spokesperson Josh Gold similarly tells &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; that it’s “disappointed the Council chose to ignore the data and kick Uber out of the Twin Cities.” The company says the move will leave 10,000 drivers without work. “We know that by working together with all stakeholders — drivers, riders and state leaders — we can achieve comprehensive statewide legislation that guarantees drivers a fair minimum wage, protects their independence and keeps rideshare affordable,” Gold says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ulGO1V"&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/minneapolis-uber-lyft-ridehailing-minimum-wage-d60db6a2e2580dc1d93c438a8cffa5ee"&gt;statement provided to &lt;em&gt;The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Associated Press&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Minneapolis council member Jamal Osman said that affordable rides shouldn’t come at the expense of the drivers’ welfare. “Drivers are human beings with families,” he said, “and they deserve dignified minimum wages like all other workers.” He added that the “vote showed Uber, Lyft, and the Mayor that the Minneapolis City Council will not allow the East African community, or any community, to be exploited for cheap labor.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Q3IWSX"&gt;Last year, Minnesota Governor Tim Walz &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/minnesota-veto-lyft-uber-pay-6407e997298464c931d8c0c1e6e371a0"&gt;vetoed a bill that would’ve&lt;/a&gt; increased wages for Uber and Lyft drivers across the state, saying at the time it could “make Minnesota one of the most expensive states in the country for rideshare.” With both Lyft and Uber saying they’ll leave Minneapolis, concerns remain about how people will get around the city and the &lt;a href="https://www.startribune.com/article/600350241/?refresh=true"&gt;effect it will have on those&lt;/a&gt; with disabilities. A report from &lt;em&gt;Axios&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.axios.com/local/twin-cities/2024/03/14/uber-lyft-alternatives-minneapolis-legislation"&gt;revealed that Minneapolis&lt;/a&gt; only has 39 licensed cab drivers, far less than the 2,000 cab drivers in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="za90J7"&gt;Some areas already set a minimum wage for ridesharing and food delivery drivers. Last year, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/29/23895637/uber-doordash-grubhub-nyc-delivery-worker-minimum-wage-ruling"&gt;New York City enacted a new rule&lt;/a&gt; that will increase drivers’ minimum wage to around $18 an hour to start, while &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/29/23661878/seattle-gig-workers-paid-sick-time-uber-eats-doordash"&gt;Seattle has a rule&lt;/a&gt; that requires companies like DoorDash, Uber, and Instacart to give delivery drivers paid sick time off. Uber &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/3/16/22334771/uber-uk-drivers-workers-benefits-employees-decision"&gt;also started paying&lt;/a&gt; drivers a minimum wage in the United Kingdom in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101774/uber-lyft-leave-minneapolis-minimum-pay"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101774/uber-lyft-leave-minneapolis-minimum-pay</id>
    <author>
      <name>Emma Roth</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-11T10:01:47-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-11T10:01:47-04:00</updated>
    <title>Uber’s posh electric rideshare service is coming to NYC</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Uber company name written on a multicolored background." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Fr7M-tO4F9z98ex1SM4adhpWu7Q=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73197795/acastro_STK106__01.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration by Alex Castro / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="VcIijZ"&gt;Uber is bringing its &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/15/23354587/uber-comfort-electric-ev-cities-list-north-america"&gt;all-electric luxury rideshare service&lt;/a&gt; to its biggest market yet: New York City. The launch will coincide with the rollout of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/6/8/23752721/uber-ev-uber-eats-takeout-containers-car-sharing"&gt;new product features&lt;/a&gt; aimed at steering its customers toward greener choices when using Uber. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KbzTvT"&gt;Uber first launched its Comfort Electric service, in which customers can hail trips in premium priced EVs like Tesla, Polestar, and Ford Mustang Mach-E, in May 2022. And since then, the service has rolled out in 41 cities, the latest now being New York. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="B33tO9"&gt;The reason Uber hadn’t launched its upscale EV service in the Big Apple before today was that the city imposed a cap on the number of EV ridehail licenses handed out by the Taxi and Limousine Commission. But that cap has now been lifted, essentially opening the floodgates to more electric Uber vehicles. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="YRS22g"&gt;&lt;q&gt;steering its customers toward greener choices&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ZSkU5z"&gt;Uber Comfort Electric is an extension of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2019/7/9/20686640/uber-comfort-extra-legroom-quiet-mode-temperature-air-conditioning-ac"&gt;Uber Comfort&lt;/a&gt;, in which riders can request extra legroom, quiet cars, and other amenities that are typically associated with its higher-priced Uber Black service. And it sits alongside the company’s other EV product, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/1/12/22226094/uber-electric-vehicles-cities-public-transportation"&gt;Uber Green&lt;/a&gt;, which gives drivers an extra fee (usually $1) to use electric vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="SPLG57"&gt;One of the major obstacles to more rideshare drivers using EVs is charging availability. To that end, Uber recently announced that it was teaming up with rival rideshare service Revel (the company that used to operate a fleet of electric mopeds but has since pivoted to Tesla Model Ys). Uber drivers that collect rewards through the company’s Uber Pro program will get up to 25 percent off charging fees when using Revel’s massive charging hub in Brooklyn. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="UWYbWu"&gt;The company is also rolling out a number of the new features that it first announced during its annual product event last summer. The first is Emissions Savings, which is like Uber’s longstanding rider and driver five-star rating system but for carbon emissions. When opening the app, customers will see how much emissions they avoided expelling into the atmosphere by using Uber’s EV ridehail services. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="A5nOKD"&gt;Also, Uber Green and Comfort Electric are being made available to teenagers with authorized Uber accounts. Last year, Uber announced the launch of a new account process for teenagers riding without their parent or guardian present. Now, those teens can hail an electric car instead of a polluting one in select cities. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="M3LG5s"&gt;Uber has set the goal of becoming a “zero-emissions platform” in the US, Europe, and Canada by 2030 — a difficult ambition given that the company classifies its drivers as independent contractors and theoretically can’t force them all to adopt EVs. The company has said it will spend $800 million of its own money to help “hundreds of thousands of drivers in the US, Canada, and Europe transition to battery EVs by 2025.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Kr38fg"&gt;The recent slowdown in EV sales growth, as well as the pullback in investments by several major automakers, has been another wrench in Uber’s plans to go emissions-free. Recently, Uber CEO Dara Khosrowshahi penned an op-ed in &lt;em&gt;Fast Company&lt;/em&gt; imploring regulators and automakers to speed up the transition to electric vehicles. Otherwise, Uber may not hit its 2030 goal. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="6jfbtY"&gt;“The stark reality is that Uber will not reach our zero-emission goals without stronger action from policymakers and businesses,” Khosrowshahi wrote. “Unfortunately, right at the moment we need to accelerate through the turn, many governments and automakers are slowing down.”&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24094429/uber-electric-ev-nyc-emissions-teen-sustainability"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24094429/uber-electric-ev-nyc-emissions-teen-sustainability</id>
    <author>
      <name>Andrew J. Hawkins</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-08T10:50:16-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-08T10:50:16-05:00</updated>
    <title>Uber ends the year in the black for the first time ever</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/pYRi3u5Ebiy65PJWU0TUdOziorU=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73122234/acastro_180927_1777_uber_0002.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration by Alex Castro / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="FILETq"&gt;Well, it only took 15 years, but better late than never. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KjlLCR"&gt;For the first time in its history, Uber ended the year having made more money than it spent on its ridehailing and delivery operations. &lt;a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/uber-ceo-dara-khosrowshahi-helped-turn-billion-dollar-profit-2024-2"&gt;As noted by &lt;em&gt;Business Insider&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the company &lt;a href="https://investor.uber.com/news-events/news/press-release-details/2024/Uber-Announces-Results-for-Fourth-Quarter-and-Full-Year-2023/default.aspx"&gt;reported an operating profit&lt;/a&gt; of $1.1 billion in 2023, compared to a $1.8 billion &lt;em&gt;loss &lt;/em&gt;in 2022. Moreover, Uber said it made a net income of $1.9 billion after losing a whopping $9.1 billion in 2022. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="J34wxH"&gt;“Looking back, 2023 was an inflection point for Uber,” CEO Dara Khosrowshahi said in an earnings call this week, “proving that we can continue to generate strong profitable growth at scale.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="LuA6M2"&gt;&lt;q&gt;“Looking back, 2023 was an inflection point for Uber”&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="4lTFxL"&gt;Under Khosrowshahi, Uber has made steady progress in the years following the pandemic. Even as far back as February 2020, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/2/6/21126965/uber-q4-earnings-report-net-loss-revenue-profit-2019"&gt;Uber was sounding like profitability was well within reach&lt;/a&gt;. But covid led to a major crash, as the company’s rides business collapsed. Demand for delivery spiked, but it was barely enough to keep the company afloat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KMHr3K"&gt;As the pandemic subsided, driver supply became a major issue, so Uber started spending huge piles of cash luring them back to the platform. That led to more big quarterly losses, spurring Khosrowshahi to order a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/5/9/23063499/uber-ceo-slash-costs-hiring-slowdown-ride-hailing-profit"&gt;“hardcore” cost-cutting effort&lt;/a&gt;. In August 2022, Uber reported its &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/8/2/23287945/uber-positive-cash-flow-q2-2022-earnings"&gt;first positive cash flow&lt;/a&gt;, which indicated that the company was generating more money from its business operations than it was losing. Still, profitability remained elusive. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="FSC19P"&gt;Less than two years later, Khosrowshahi finally found the right balance and will have a lot to brag about heading into the company’s investor day event next week. Analysts are predicting some sort of share repurchase program and updated financial targets. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ot93xa"&gt;But all that belies the importance of getting Uber onto stronger financial ground. For years, the company was derided for using its bundles of venture capital cash to subsidize the price of a car trip in a city, artificially lowering the cost of a ride to lure in millennial customers who were turned off by clunky, digitally hostile taxis. And &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2019/5/10/18564197/uber-ipo-stock-valuation-pricing-fares-drivers-public-market"&gt;critics predicted&lt;/a&gt; that Uber would never be profitable because its business model was fundamentally flawed. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Wng7Ex"&gt;Now, Uber trips are more expensive, and taxi fleets are slowly rebuilding their operations. In fact, Uber is adding taxis to its app in a bid to offer a helping hand to its former rival. And instead of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2017/12/14/16778064/uber-criminal-investigation-confirm-doj-waymo"&gt;subverting the law and thumbing its nose at regulators&lt;/a&gt;, the company is attempting to play nice — or at least that’s what it says. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZVnP1C"&gt;Still, it faces legal challenges around the world. It recently announced it’s spending $30 million in California’s upcoming races to elect friendly lawmakers. What better use for all those new profits?&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/8/24065999/uber-earnings-profitable-year-net-income"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/8/24065999/uber-earnings-profitable-year-net-income</id>
    <author>
      <name>Andrew J. Hawkins</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-01-10T17:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-01-10T17:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>Kia gets its first customer for the PV5 modular electric vehicle: Uber</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Kia PV5 electric vehicle" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/sWGvTsIEK-8hlOoKBbBhmL60g2k=/0x0:1350x900/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73043125/21654_PV5_Concept.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Kia&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="bAjcHW"&gt;Kia and Uber &lt;a href="https://www.kianewscenter.com/news/all/kia-signs-mou-to-offer-ride-hailing-pbvs-to-drivers-on-the-uber-platform/s/714dabf1-7e77-468f-b969-07600c84065f"&gt;have signed a memorandum of understanding&lt;/a&gt; to use the automaker’s newly announced PBV modular electric vehicles for ridehailing. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ek26mP"&gt;PBV, which stands for Platform Beyond Vehicle, was &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/8/24028828/kia-platform-beyond-vehicle-pbv-modular-ev-ces"&gt;introduced during CES in Las Vegas&lt;/a&gt; as a family of EVs built on a flexible vehicle architecture, with different swappable body types. The vehicle can be transformed from a minivan to a full-size van to a small truck, depending on the specific need. The driver cab remains fixed while the rest of the vehicle is interchangeable, like a real-life Duplo set. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RIJ2VH"&gt;One of the possible variations is the PV5, a midsized electric van that Kia says is designed for ridehailing, delivery, and utilities. Uber wants to add the PV5 as an option for its drivers, in the hopes of fulfilling its pledge to go &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/9/8/21427196/uber-promise-100-percent-electric-vehicle-ev-2030"&gt;all-electric in all markets by 2040&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="WWnZQT"&gt;&lt;q&gt;Uber wants to add the PV5 as an option for its drivers&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="Dk9icg"&gt;Uber says the purpose of the deal with Kia is “to identify optimal specifications for PBV models, with the possible further integration of technology and services to benefit drivers and ride hailing users alike.” The two companies will work together on the creation of “proofs of concept, prototypes, and the production of PBVs tailored to the needs of drivers that use the Uber platform.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="62Z7sN"&gt;Uber is &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/26/23573100/nyc-uber-lyft-electric-mayor-adams-2030"&gt;under pressure from governments&lt;/a&gt; around the world to get more of its drivers into EVs to reduce tailpipe pollution and fight climate change. Of course, getting the hundreds of thousands of people who drive for Uber to switch to EVs will be no easy task. Ridehail drivers are classified as independent contractors, and many use their personal cars to drive for not just one but several gig economy companies. Uber can’t just force all its drivers to make the switch without jeopardizing their status as freelancers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Da0Ai9"&gt;Conor Ferguson, a spokesperson for Uber, said the company would have more to say about financing the purchase of Kia’s PBV vehicles closer to when they are available. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="FlFPMF"&gt;Currently, Uber works with automakers to offer drivers &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/6/1/23744827/ford-uber-ev-flexible-lease-driver-mustang-mach-e"&gt;flexible leases on EVs&lt;/a&gt; and incentives &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/9/15/23354587/uber-comfort-electric-ev-cities-list-north-america"&gt;like added bonuses&lt;/a&gt; on each trip they do in an electric vehicle. Uber says it has over 74,000 drivers using electric vehicles in North America and Europe. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2kmD7f"&gt;Uber previously made a deal with UK-based startup Arrival to acquire its EVs, but that company is barely staying afloat these days.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/10/24033010/kia-uber-mou-pv5-modular-ev-ridehail-deal"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/10/24033010/kia-uber-mou-pv5-modular-ev-ridehail-deal</id>
    <author>
      <name>Andrew J. Hawkins</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
