<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Policies</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-15T15:00:42-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/policy/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/policy" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T15:00:42-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T15:00:42-04:00</updated>
    <title>Supreme Court defines when it’s illegal for public officials to block social media critics</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of the Supreme Court building with gavels behind." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/qDcyAhagcgN_zrbQ8UmbSkIMLZQ=/20x0:2021x1334/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73210251/STK463_SCOTUS_A.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Cath Virginia / The Verge | Photos via Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="rHfe8R"&gt;In an &lt;a href="https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/23pdf/22-611_ap6c.pdf"&gt;opinion signed by Justice Amy Coney Barrett&lt;/a&gt;, the Supreme Court established a test to determine when a public official can be considered to be engaging in state action in blocking someone from their social media account. The official must have both “(1) possessed actual authority to speak on the State’s behalf on a particular matter, and (2) purported to exercise that authority when speaking in the relevant social-media posts.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="fNZNNX"&gt;The court issued a unanimous decision in &lt;a href="https://www.scotusblog.com/case-files/cases/lindke-v-freed/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lindke v. Freed&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a case about whether Port Huron, Michigan city manager James Freed violated the First Amendment by &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/4/24/23695910/supreme-court-first-amendment-government-officials-block-social-media-users"&gt;blocking and deleting comments&lt;/a&gt; on his Facebook page from resident Kevin Lindke, who critiqued Freed’s pandemic policies. The test creates a new way to determine if an official can be held liable for violating a citizen’s First Amendment rights through actions on their social media pages. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="w9BQ95"&gt;But it’s not enough for a social media page to simply belong to a public official. Barrett wrote, “The distinction between private conduct and state action turns on substance, not labels: Private parties can act with the authority of the State, and state officials have private lives and their own constitutional rights—including the First Amendment right to speak about their jobs and exercise editorial control over speech and speakers on their personal platforms.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="CBnZir"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The distinction between private conduct and state action turns on substance, not labels&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ZQuj2w"&gt;Barrett suggested that simple disclaimers could make a difference in the determination. “Here, if Freed’s account had carried a label—e.g., ‘this is the personal page of James R. Freed’—he would be entitled to a heavy presumption that all of his posts were personal,” the ruling says, “but Freed’s page was not designated either ‘personal’ or ‘official.’” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1vBbNo"&gt;Katie Fallow, senior counsel of the Knight First Amendment Institute at Columbia University said in a statement the court was “right to hold that public officials can’t immunize themselves from First Amendment liability merely by using their personal accounts to conduct official business.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RRaqoj"&gt;But, Fallow added, “We are disappointed, though, that the Court did not adopt the more practical test used by the majority of the courts of appeals, which appropriately balanced the free speech interests of public officials with those of the people who want to speak to them on their social media accounts. We hope that in implementing the new test crafted by the Supreme Court today, the courts will be mindful of the importance of protecting speech and dissent in these digital public forums.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="yrVTPy"&gt;&lt;a href="https://knightcolumbia.org/cases/knight-institute-v-trump"&gt;The Knight Institute challenged former President Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt; in 2017 over blocking users from his @realDonaldTrump Twitter account. They argued his account was a “public forum” where people could not be excluded for their views, and the lower courts agreed. In 2021, when Trump was no longer in office, the Supreme Court ordered the lower court to vacate a ruling against Trump and &lt;a href="https://knightcolumbia.org/cases/knight-institute-v-trump"&gt;dismiss it as moot&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="qSw3Hb"&gt;Dhillon Law Group partner Gary Lawkowski said in an emailed statement about the new ruling that “the biggest impact of this opinion may not be the formal test set forth in its holding—rather, its language buried in the opinion that effectively creates a safe harbor for public officials who place disclaimers on their social media accounts, providing an easy way for public officials to stay on the ‘personal’ side of the law going forward.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="kjTGmq"&gt;The justices vacated and remanded the case back to the lower court.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="KBHOjw"&gt;
&lt;iframe src="https://embed.documentcloud.org/documents/24483483-scotus-lindke-v-freed/?embed=1&amp;amp;responsive=1&amp;amp;title=1" title="SCOTUS - LINDKE v. FREED (Hosted by DocumentCloud)" width="700" height="450" style="border: 1px solid #aaa; width: 100%; height: 800px; height: calc(100vh - 100px);" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-forms allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101983/supreme-court-public-officials-block-critics-social-media-lindke-v-freed"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101983/supreme-court-public-officials-block-critics-social-media-lindke-v-freed</id>
    <author>
      <name>Lauren Feiner</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T13:39:32-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T13:39:32-04:00</updated>
    <title>Zoomers are turning on the TikTok famous congressman who voted to ban the app</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Debt Ceiling Vote" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/4LyNetd4kOn0mEi7Y8IURzyI5cQ=/0x0:8640x5760/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73210023/1258639155.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Tom Williams/CQ-Roll Call, Inc via Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="UgxORa"&gt;Until relatively recently, Rep. Jeff Jackson, a freshman Democratic congressman from North Carolina, had more than 2.5 million followers on TikTok. Jackson’s follower count dropped by over 100,000 virtually overnight — as did his esteem among some of TikTok’s young users — after he &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24097125/house-bill-vote-tiktok-ban-china-bytedance-divestment"&gt;voted to ban the app&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gt7WOk"&gt;The bill passed with 352 votes, but to the legions of TikTokers who &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093308/tiktok-congress-ban-push-notification"&gt;called their representatives&lt;/a&gt; to urge them not to ban the app, Jackson’s vote feels like a unique betrayal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="tlQCAN"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="tiktok-embed" cite="https://www.tiktok.com/@noahglenncarter/video/7346291613947186475" data-video-id="7346291613947186475" data-embed-from="oembed" style="max-width:605px; min-width:325px;"&gt; &lt;section&gt; &lt;a target="_blank" title="@noahglenncarter" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@noahglenncarter?refer=embed"&gt;@noahglenncarter&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt;An update on Jeff Jackson. Hes losing everything right now because he boted yes &lt;a title="keeptiktok" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/keeptiktok?refer=embed"&gt;#keeptiktok&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="jeffjackson" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/jeffjackson?refer=embed"&gt;#jeffjackson&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="tiktokban" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/tiktokban?refer=embed"&gt;#tiktokban&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="foryou" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/foryou?refer=embed"&gt;#foryou&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;a target="_blank" title="♬ Stargazing (Slowed + Reverb) - Marcelo De Carvalho" href="https://www.tiktok.com/music/Stargazing-Slowed-Reverb-7221312697249531906?refer=embed"&gt;♬ Stargazing (Slowed + Reverb) - Marcelo De Carvalho&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/section&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;script async="" src="https://www.tiktok.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="2x31GH"&gt;On Wednesday, Jackson posted a video on X laying out the rationale for his vote. “I don’t think TikTok is going to be banned,” he began. If the bill passes in the Senate, Jackson said in the video, he thinks the likeliest scenario is that “TikTok will be sold for billions of dollars and will continue to operate.” His opposition, he continued, is not with TikTok itself but with China’s national security laws and the sway the Chinese government has over TikTok’s algorithms — and, potentially, over American politics. “We got a big example of how that power could be used last week, and it wasn’t subtle,” Jackson said, referring to the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093308/tiktok-congress-ban-push-notification"&gt;pop-up notification&lt;/a&gt; TikTok served users that warned Congress is “planning a total ban of TikTok.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5tu5IT"&gt;Jackson also acknowledged TikTok users’ concern that Congress is attempting to pass legislation that could potentially ban an app they don’t even understand. “I know a lot of you have seen some members of Congress be deeply uninformed about this because they don’t use TikTok and they don’t care,” he said. “But I do use it, and I think we can solve this problem and keep marching on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="o2sxAg"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet"&gt;
&lt;p lang="en" dir="ltr"&gt;The best-case scenario for TikTok is that it continues to operate but is no longer owned - and potentially controlled - by an adversarial country. &lt;a href="https://t.co/JsXHliZACJ"&gt;pic.twitter.com/JsXHliZACJ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;— Rep. Jeff Jackson (@JeffJacksonNC) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/JeffJacksonNC/status/1767936238625984739?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;March 13, 2024&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="1dBQ6P"&gt;TikTok users, meanwhile, weren’t happy with Jackson’s explanation. The comments section of his &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@jeffjacksonnc/video/7345130701836094762?lang=en"&gt;most recent video&lt;/a&gt;, posted on Monday, is full of people calling him a hypocrite. Some of the comments suggest that Jackson originally cross-posted his post-vote explanation video on TikTok, and then deleted it after a wave of backlash. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="36hLhN"&gt;“WITHOUT TIKTOK YOUR NOTHING!!! @Jeff Jackson,” said one irate viewer. “SELLLOUUUUTTTTTTTTTTT,” said another. Jackson’s office did not immediately respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="DSYikU"&gt;Jackson grew his following on TikTok by posting explainers on everything from the Russia-Ukraine war to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23635692/silicon-valley-bank-svb-collapse-explainer-startups-venture-capital"&gt;the Silicon Valley Bank collapse&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Ybqtdk"&gt;In interviews with &lt;a href="https://rollcall.com/2023/04/05/rep-jeff-jackson-congress-biggest-tiktok-star-sees-the-app-as-a-tool-for-transparency/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roll Call&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;and &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2023/04/11/tiktok-congressman-jeff-jackson/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, he’s touted TikTok as a way of educating constituents about the ins and outs of the legislative process. The app, he’s said, is good for transparency. Since the White House has forbidden federal employees, including members of Congress, from having TikTok on their government-issued phones, Jackson has the app installed &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2023/04/11/tiktok-congressman-jeff-jackson/"&gt;on a separate personal device&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="y9ag1X"&gt;Last April, Jackson told &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2023/04/11/tiktok-congressman-jeff-jackson/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;he’d vote for legislation banning TikTok “as a last resort,” though he’d prefer that ByteDance sell the app so he — and his constituents — can keep using it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Mwj9d8"&gt;For now, Jackson can still post, although his posts are being brigaded with comments like “&lt;strong&gt;                 &lt;/strong&gt;.” And despite his recent drop in followers, he remains the most-followed member of Congress on TikTok.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101851/tiktok-ban-vote-jeff-jackson-sell-bytedance"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101851/tiktok-ban-vote-jeff-jackson-sell-bytedance</id>
    <author>
      <name>Gaby Del Valle</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T12:14:39-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T12:14:39-04:00</updated>
    <title>Uber and Lyft to leave Minneapolis over ‘deeply flawed’ pay rules</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Uber company name written on a multicolored background." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/O6GRXLzYMSHtZfvE982hb1v3olc=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209741/acastro_STK106__01.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration by Alex Castro / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="TqD504"&gt;Uber and Lyft are pulling their services out of Minneapolis after the city council passed an ordinance that will increase drivers’ pay. Both companies say they will no longer offer ridesharing services in the city when the ordinance goes into effect on May 1st.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="PqTda0"&gt;The ordinance, which guarantees drivers a minimum rate of $1.40 per mile and 51 cents per minute while carrying a rider, was &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/minneapolis-city-council-uber-lyft-rideshare-ordinance-vote/"&gt;first passed last week&lt;/a&gt; but &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/minneapolis-mayor-vetoes-minimum-wage-rideshare-ordinance/"&gt;later vetoed&lt;/a&gt; by Minneapolis Mayor Jacob Frey. The City Council &lt;a href="https://minnesotareformer.com/2024/03/14/minneapolis-council-overrides-mayors-veto-of-uber-and-lyft-minimum-rates/"&gt;voted 10–3 to override&lt;/a&gt; the veto on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xms1gF"&gt;Lyft spokesperson CJ Macklin calls the ordinance “deeply flawed,” as &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/minnesota/news/minneapolis-mayor-discusses-recently-passed-rideshare-ordinance/"&gt;the rates were determined&lt;/a&gt; before the state released a study detailing how much drivers would have to be paid to earn Minneapolis’ $15.57 per hour minimum wage. &lt;a href="https://dli.mn.gov/sites/default/files/pdf/TNC_driver_earnings_analysis_pay_standard_options_report_030824.pdf"&gt;The study&lt;/a&gt; analyzed over 18 million trips taken in 2022. &lt;a href="https://www.startribune.com/minnesota-uber-and-lyft-drivers-often-earn-less-than-minimum-wage-state-study-says/600349568/"&gt;It found&lt;/a&gt; that drivers could earn the city’s minimum wage — while also accounting for health insurance, paid leave, and retirement savings — with rates of $1.21 per mile and 49 cents per minute, lower than what the city council approved. &lt;em&gt;“&lt;/em&gt;We support a minimum earning standard for drivers,” Macklin says, “but it should be done in an honest way that keeps the service affordable for riders.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="o7pPAD"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"How Uber learned to stop fighting and play nice with taxis ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/26/23888950/uber-taxi-driver-referral-third-party-los-angeles"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zaxeQX"&gt;Uber spokesperson Josh Gold similarly tells &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; that it’s “disappointed the Council chose to ignore the data and kick Uber out of the Twin Cities.” The company says the move will leave 10,000 drivers without work. “We know that by working together with all stakeholders — drivers, riders and state leaders — we can achieve comprehensive statewide legislation that guarantees drivers a fair minimum wage, protects their independence and keeps rideshare affordable,” Gold says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ulGO1V"&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/minneapolis-uber-lyft-ridehailing-minimum-wage-d60db6a2e2580dc1d93c438a8cffa5ee"&gt;statement provided to &lt;em&gt;The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Associated Press&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Minneapolis council member Jamal Osman said that affordable rides shouldn’t come at the expense of the drivers’ welfare. “Drivers are human beings with families,” he said, “and they deserve dignified minimum wages like all other workers.” He added that the “vote showed Uber, Lyft, and the Mayor that the Minneapolis City Council will not allow the East African community, or any community, to be exploited for cheap labor.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Q3IWSX"&gt;Last year, Minnesota Governor Tim Walz &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/minnesota-veto-lyft-uber-pay-6407e997298464c931d8c0c1e6e371a0"&gt;vetoed a bill that would’ve&lt;/a&gt; increased wages for Uber and Lyft drivers across the state, saying at the time it could “make Minnesota one of the most expensive states in the country for rideshare.” With both Lyft and Uber saying they’ll leave Minneapolis, concerns remain about how people will get around the city and the &lt;a href="https://www.startribune.com/article/600350241/?refresh=true"&gt;effect it will have on those&lt;/a&gt; with disabilities. A report from &lt;em&gt;Axios&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.axios.com/local/twin-cities/2024/03/14/uber-lyft-alternatives-minneapolis-legislation"&gt;revealed that Minneapolis&lt;/a&gt; only has 39 licensed cab drivers, far less than the 2,000 cab drivers in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="za90J7"&gt;Some areas already set a minimum wage for ridesharing and food delivery drivers. Last year, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/29/23895637/uber-doordash-grubhub-nyc-delivery-worker-minimum-wage-ruling"&gt;New York City enacted a new rule&lt;/a&gt; that will increase drivers’ minimum wage to around $18 an hour to start, while &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/29/23661878/seattle-gig-workers-paid-sick-time-uber-eats-doordash"&gt;Seattle has a rule&lt;/a&gt; that requires companies like DoorDash, Uber, and Instacart to give delivery drivers paid sick time off. Uber &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/3/16/22334771/uber-uk-drivers-workers-benefits-employees-decision"&gt;also started paying&lt;/a&gt; drivers a minimum wage in the United Kingdom in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101774/uber-lyft-leave-minneapolis-minimum-pay"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101774/uber-lyft-leave-minneapolis-minimum-pay</id>
    <author>
      <name>Emma Roth</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T10:58:12-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T10:58:12-04:00</updated>
    <title>FCC clamps down on confusing ‘hidden fees’ in your cable TV bill</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Dollars float through pillars, as if to exit a bank" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/9zq22Yj8b76DwgrNB9z3hVeOpjk=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209464/STK417_H_Herrera_Money_03.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The ruling aims to make it easier to accurately compare subscription prices against other providers.&lt;/em&gt; | Illustration by Hugo Herrera / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="aT5hLP"&gt;Cable and satellite TV providers will need to ensure they show the total price of subscription plans as a “prominent single line item” — including costs described as extra fees — under a rule adopted by the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) on Thursday. The FCC says the &lt;a href="https://docs.fcc.gov/public/attachments/DOC-401215A1.pdf"&gt;new rule (pdf)&lt;/a&gt; for “all-in” pricing will make it easier for customers to compare prices against competing providers and streaming services by eliminating the “misleading practice of describing video programming costs as a tax, fee, or surcharge.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZPotRN"&gt;“No one likes surprises on their bill,” said FCC Chairwoman Jessica Rosenworcel in a &lt;a href="https://docs.fcc.gov/public/attachments/DOC-401215A2.pdf"&gt;separate statement (pdf)&lt;/a&gt;. “The advertised price for a service should be the price you pay when your bill arrives. It shouldn’t include a bunch of unexpected junk fees that are separate from the top-line price you were told when you signed up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="YWD5CF"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet"&gt;
&lt;p lang="en" dir="ltr"&gt;TV providers often use deceptive junk fees to hide real prices. We are putting an end to this form of price masking by requiring cable &amp;amp; satellite TV providers to clearly specify the “all-in” price for video programming in their promotional materials &amp;amp; on subscribers’ bills.&lt;/p&gt;— The FCC (@FCC) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/FCC/status/1768332803123352045?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;March 14, 2024&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="rfheLa"&gt;The new rules for transparent pricing on video programming will apply to both subscribers’ bills and promotional materials. The FCC says that companies often obscure certain costs and fees, which “causes significant and costly confusion for consumers.” The Commission has also proposed eliminating early termination fees issued by cable and satellite TV providers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="An example of a Comcast bill showing a breakdown of additional fees and charges." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/dkJt0t_vrgpf8nwiZgRbNl0P23Q=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25337693/HOW11878_092623_03.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Comcast Xfinity&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Bills like this &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="ql-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.xfinity.com%2Fsupport%2Farticles%2Fnew-bill-design&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F15%2F24101802%2Fcable-tv-bill-fee-satellite-tv-providers-subscription-price-fcc" target="_blank" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;example&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; from Comcast will be required to clearly display the total price, including the extra fees and charges.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="3emTKd"&gt;Forcing companies to display their subscription prices more clearly might be a relief to consumers who are sick of being surprised by unexpected additional fees, but cable providers like &lt;a href="https://www.fcc.gov/ecfs/document/10307141821162/1"&gt;Comcast, Cox, and Charter&lt;/a&gt; have argued that it’s unnecessary. The Internet &amp;amp; Television Association (NCTA) called the ruling “misguided” and claims it will only cause further confusion. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="N00PoO"&gt;“Cable providers offer clear and accurate pricing information to attract and retain subscribers, including ‘all-in’ pricing information before signing up for service,” &lt;a href="https://www.ncta.com/media/media-room/statements-of-ncta-the-internet-television-association-regarding-actions-at-todays-fcc-meeting"&gt;the NCTA said&lt;/a&gt; in response to the ruling. “The FCC’s micromanagement of advertising in today’s hyper-competitive marketplace will force operators to either clutter their ads with confusing disclosures or leave pricing information out entirely.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AlnDKE"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclosure: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Comcast is an investor in Vox Media, &lt;/em&gt;The Verge&lt;em&gt;’s parent company.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101802/cable-tv-bill-fee-satellite-tv-providers-subscription-price-fcc"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101802/cable-tv-bill-fee-satellite-tv-providers-subscription-price-fcc</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jess Weatherbed</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T10:13:33-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T10:13:33-04:00</updated>
    <title>Are we really going to ban TikTok?</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="An illustration depicting TikTok over the Vergecast team." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/EHwDyc3uJH6WLplmQFPcGzu815k=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209314/VST_0315_Site.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Alex Parkin / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="tv0Uat"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23651507/tiktok-ban-us-news"&gt;The TikTok ban&lt;/a&gt; might be for real this time. Nearly &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/9/22525953/biden-tiktok-wechat-trump-bans-revoked-alipay"&gt;four years after&lt;/a&gt; the first attempt to get the ByteDance-owned company either sold or barred from the US, a new bill is &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24097125/house-bill-vote-tiktok-ban-china-bytedance-divestment"&gt;flying through congressional votes&lt;/a&gt;, and President Joe Biden has already &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/9/24095348/president-biden-says-hell-sign-a-tiktok-ban-if-passed"&gt;said he’ll sign it&lt;/a&gt; if it comes to his desk. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="oEfzyZ"&gt;On &lt;a href="https://pod.link/vergecast"&gt;this episode of &lt;em&gt;The Vergecast&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we talk about what’s inside the Protecting Americans From Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act (everybody calls it PAFFACAA, just kidding; nobody calls it that, everybody just calls it “The TikTok Ban”) and what we know about TikTok’s connection to China. The answer: not a lot! But four years in, Congress seems more convinced than ever, and that might mean something. Or it might not. We spend a long time debating what that means.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="QkZrXb"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://player.megaphone.fm/VMP6905517148" style="border: 0; width: 100%; height: 200px;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="NC84Mv"&gt;After that, we discuss &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24097247/former-activision-ceo-bobby-kotick-is-apparently-eyeing-tiktok"&gt;who might buy TikTok&lt;/a&gt;, whether TikTok is even for sale, and what companies like Meta, Snap, and X stand to gain from a TikTok ban. And finally, we try to decide which outcome is the most likely: a TikTok ban, a TikTok sale, or nothing at all?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="bIpyw8"&gt;Once we dispense with the TikTok news, we talk about &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099533/youtube-tv-app-redesign-comments-shopping"&gt;YouTube’s new redesign for TVs&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099337/spotify-music-video-beta-11-markets-supported-artists"&gt;Spotify’s push into music videos&lt;/a&gt; — which are both, in a way, actually stories about TikTok. Neil Young &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099330/neil-youngs-music-is-back-on-low-res-spotify-two-years-after-rogan-protest"&gt;makes a surprise reappearance&lt;/a&gt; on the show, and then it’s time for a lightning round. Brought to you by your favorite new band, Algorithmic Warfare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="RNEOJ6"&gt;
&lt;div data-analytics-viewport="video" data-analytics-action="volume:view:article:middle" data-analytics-label="Are we really about to ban TikTok? | The Vergecast|115759" data-volume-uuid="5f55831ed" data-volume-id="115759" data-analytics-placement="article:middle" data-volume-placement="article" data-volume-autoplay="false" id="volume-placement-365" class="volume-video" data-volume-player-choice="youtube"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ehBTgI"&gt;If you want to read more on everything we covered in this show (there’s a lot!), here are a few links to get you started, first on TikTok:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="X9g3CD"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23651507/tiktok-ban-us-news"&gt;TikTok ban: all the news on attempts to ban the video platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="UecVfE"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091278/congress-tiktok-bytedance-ban-divest-bill"&gt;Lawmakers introduce bill that would punish app stores for hosting TikTok&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="ImCUQS"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24097125/house-bill-vote-tiktok-ban-china-bytedance-divestment"&gt;House passes bill that could ban TikTok&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="edg1nD"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/9/24095348/president-biden-says-hell-sign-a-tiktok-ban-if-passed"&gt;President Biden says he’ll sign a TikTok ban, if passed.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="r5wMDh"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099721/tiktok-ban-senate-house-vote-divest-bill"&gt;TikTok’s fate now lies with the Senate after House advances path to a ban&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="G3QQB8"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24100175/tiktok-ceo-tells-users-to-make-their-voices-heard-against-a-bill-that-could-ban-the-app-in-the-us"&gt;TikTok CEO tells users to “make their voices heard” against a bill that could ban the app in the US.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="kf72JW"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099896/nancy-pelosi-is-playing-tiktok-toe"&gt;Nancy Pelosi is playing TikTok-toe.&lt;/a&gt; (Ditto)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="wNhx2Q"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24097416/donald-trump-has-even-more-to-say-about-the-tiktok-ban"&gt;Donald Trump has even more to say about the TikTok ban.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="KwvrGU"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093308/tiktok-congress-ban-push-notification"&gt;TikTok is urging users to call Congress about a looming ban&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="dh31N5"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093490/the-tiktokers-are-revolting"&gt;The TikTokers are revolting.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="c1Y3br"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24097247/former-activision-ceo-bobby-kotick-is-apparently-eyeing-tiktok"&gt;Former Activision CEO Bobby Kotick is apparently eyeing TikTok.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="0VNlCO"&gt;And on the streaming news of the week:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="pf24W5"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099533/youtube-tv-app-redesign-comments-shopping"&gt;YouTube is revamping its TV app to make videos feel way more interactive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="KYLE54"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099337/spotify-music-video-beta-11-markets-supported-artists"&gt;Spotify now has music videos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Zt6Hg4"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099330/neil-youngs-music-is-back-on-low-res-spotify-two-years-after-rogan-protest"&gt;Neil Young’s music is back on “low res Spotify” two years after Rogan protest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="akgRDV"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099677/don-lemon-elon-musk-x-canceled"&gt;Elon Musk cancels Don Lemon’s show on X after a ‘tense’ interview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="kCPQNp"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lindayaX/status/1767675796334776506"&gt;Linda Yaccarino on X: “X is becoming a video first platform&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="ezAObe"&gt;And in the lightning round:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="QB4zvj"&gt;Alex Cranz’s pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/10/24096762/kate-middleton-edited-photo-royal-family-possible-fake"&gt;British monarchy rocked by bad Photoshop job&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="jcG1Xn"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098548/kate-middleton-royal-family-photoshop-manipulated-image"&gt;The Kate Middleton photo scandal is a rare — and consequential — flub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="DrwqJQ"&gt;Nilay Patel’s pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100501/spacex-starship-launch-third-flight-test-success"&gt;SpaceX successfully launches Starship in third flight test&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Te7A5S"&gt;David Pierce’s pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098334/apple-ios-web-distribution-eu-app-store-changes"&gt;Apple to allow iOS app downloads direct from websites in the EU&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="YNDPUb"&gt;Alex’s second pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24098771/dyson-vis-nav-robot-vacuum-hands-on"&gt;Hands-on with the Dyson 360 Vis Nav robot vacuum&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="ICMx6J"&gt;David’s second pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099723/microsoft-teams-unified-app-personal-work-accounts"&gt;Microsoft Teams is finally moving to a single app for personal and work&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Zwysf2"&gt;Nilay’s second pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093109/nikon-acquiring-red-cameras-film-motion-picture-tv"&gt;Nikon is acquiring US camera manufacturer RED&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="seBzTK"&gt;We’re really curious to hear what you think about the TikTok ban in particular. As always, you can get in touch with us by emailing vergecast@theverge.com, calling the &lt;em&gt;Vergecast&lt;/em&gt; Hotline at +1-866-VERGE11, or hitting us up on Threads. Or TikTok! For now.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24101704/tiktok-ban-kate-middleton-photoshop-vergecast-podcast"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24101704/tiktok-ban-kate-middleton-photoshop-vergecast-podcast</id>
    <author>
      <name>David Pierce</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T09:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T09:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Supreme Court to hear case on how the government talks to social media companies </title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of the Supreme Court building with pixelated red and white stripes." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ngIto8KstKG-RsoYjsfS9gfuA2I=/20x0:2021x1334/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209095/STK463_SCOTUS_D.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Cath Virginia / The Verge | Photos via Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="O8OJ52"&gt;On Monday, the Supreme Court will hear a case that could upend how social media platforms deal with posts containing anything from vaccine misinformation to election threats. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="kYEaNp"&gt;At the moment, various arms of the US government will communicate directly with platforms for all sorts of reasons. For example, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) might email directly with someone at Facebook during a global pandemic, especially if Facebook wants to set up an information hub for its users. (You can imagine similar scenarios for voter misinformation, election integrity, and all kinds of public emergencies.) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3R1yfE"&gt;The core question at issue in &lt;em&gt;Murthy v. Missouri&lt;/em&gt; is whether the government can flag potentially harmful posts to social media companies without it turning into unconstitutional coercion of speech. (Coercion in this vein is generally called “jawboning.”) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uJ9yfU"&gt;These arguments come just weeks after the court &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/23/24080521/supreme-court-netchoice-florida-texas-social-media-laws-arguments"&gt;heard another set of First Amendment challenges involving social media&lt;/a&gt;. In those cases, &lt;em&gt;Moody v. NetChoice&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;NetChoice v. Paxton&lt;/em&gt;, the court considered whether state laws legislating how social media companies could moderate posts on their sites violated the platforms’ own First Amendment rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="om5rXX"&gt;How &lt;em&gt;Murthy v. Missouri&lt;/em&gt; reached the Supreme Court&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="dYw1pA"&gt;The case at issue got started when Republican state attorneys general from Missouri and Louisiana &lt;a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/63290154/1/missouri-v-biden/"&gt;decided to sue the Biden administration in May 2022&lt;/a&gt;, arguing that various government arms — including the CDC and the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) — violated the First Amendment while communicating with social media companies. The AGs claimed that the Biden administration effectively coerced the platforms to take down posts or accounts spreading what was identified as covid or voting misinformation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rkXWaJ"&gt;If this legal argument sounds unsettlingly familiar, it may be because much of &lt;em&gt;Murthy&lt;/em&gt; is echoed in &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/12/2/23490863/elon-musk-twitter-expose-hunter-biden-flop-doxxed-multiple-people"&gt;Elon Musk’s extremely cursed crusade&lt;/a&gt; to make the “Twitter Files” a thing. The original Missouri state AG’s &lt;a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20221214070839/https://ago.mo.gov/home/news/2022/05/05/missouri-louisiana-ags-file-suit-against-president-biden-top-admin-officials-for-allegedly-colluding-with-social-media-giants-to-censor-and-suppress-free-speech"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; about the lawsuit references Hunter Biden’s laptop, the Wuhan lab leak theory, and the efficacy of masking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="G2BWLV"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The original state AG’s press release about the lawsuit references Hunter Biden’s laptop, the Wuhan lab leak theory, and the efficacy of masking&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="vc8rbP"&gt;In July 2023, a federal district court enjoined parts of the Biden administration from communicating with social media platforms, as well as groups like the Stanford Internet Observatory and Election Integrity Partnership, which track the spread of misinformation. Later that year, the Fifth Circuit Court of Appeals &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/4/23783822/free-speech-ruling-missouri-v-biden-dhs-fbi-cisa"&gt;upheld much of that broad preliminary injunction,&lt;/a&gt; though it narrowed some of its scope. Soon after, the Supreme Court &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/10/20/us/supreme-court-social-media-biden.html"&gt;lifted limits on the administration’s communications&lt;/a&gt; while considering the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xxn7gq"&gt;The decision in &lt;em&gt;Murthy v. Missouri &lt;/em&gt;will help determine the extent to which the Biden administration can notify social media platforms about potentially concerning content on their sites. That could affect the safeguards these companies have put up around misinformation, and may change the kind of flags and warnings you see on posts all over the internet. SCOTUS is likely to issue a decision around June, just months ahead of the November elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="HfTYw2"&gt;Coercion versus persuasion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="6AKLJ0"&gt;There are two Supreme Court precedents likely to come up during the arguments Monday: &lt;a href="https://supreme.justia.com/cases/federal/us/372/58/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bantam Books v. Sullivan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://supreme.justia.com/cases/federal/us/457/991/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blum v. Yaretsky&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hlCRpT"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bantam Books&lt;/em&gt; is a case from 1963 involving a Rhode Island commission created to evaluate whether books were appropriate for minors. The court ruled that the commission effectively coerced book distributors to suppress certain works through intimidation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="iS7OmX"&gt;The court “found that the intent of the commission was not to educate or inform the book distributors about how to comply with the law, but rather to intimidate them into suppressing and censoring content that the commission didn’t like,” according to Jennifer Jones, staff attorney at the Knight First Amendment Institute at Columbia University. The court recognized that while it’s constitutional for the authorities to advise or persuade intermediaries to act in a certain way, the government had gone too far in this instance. “When the acts become coercive, and when they basically apply this unrelenting pressure so that the intermediaries don’t publish speech because the government doesn’t like it, that does, in fact, violate the Constitution.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="vjAdMc"&gt;Jones added that &lt;em&gt;Murthy v. Missouri &lt;/em&gt;will be “the first time that the court is going to evaluate the application of that framework in the context of social media.” If the court agrees with the state AGs that the Biden administration inappropriately communicated with social media companies, Jones said, “that could really severely limit the ability of government officials to communicate with and work with the platforms moving forward.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="Lk4lAb"&gt;&lt;q&gt;Social media platforms could be “chilled” from reaching out to the government to verify information&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="Cpt2Q9"&gt;But it’s not just the government’s ability to reach out to platforms that’s at risk — communication is a two-way street, after all. Jones said that social media platforms themselves could be “chilled” from reaching out to the government to verify information (as they might be inclined to do during a public health emergency like the covid-19 pandemic, for example) for fear of being held liable if they’re seen as doing the government’s bidding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4zmVmd"&gt;That’s because &lt;em&gt;Blum v. Yaretsky&lt;/em&gt; created “a standard for when the conduct of a private actor can actually be transformed into state action,” Jones said. “And therefore, that private actor can be held liable because they’re essentially acting at the behest of the government.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="XEFWns"&gt;The US Chamber of Commerce, a broad business group, &lt;a href="https://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/23/23-411/294103/20231222113124560_SCT%2023-411%20-%20Murthy%20v%20Missouri%20-%20US%20Chamber.pdf"&gt;warned the court in its brief&lt;/a&gt; against allowing the theory of state action to be used to punish private entities. “[E]ven if the Court views this case through the lens of state action, it should confirm that when the government interferes with private speech choices, the remedy lies in restraining the government — not in further abridging the rights of the coerced private parties with injunctions that limit the exercise of their own First Amendment rights,” the group wrote. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WB5sHz"&gt;Gautam Hans, associate director of the First Amendment Clinic at Cornell Law School, anticipates &lt;em&gt;Murthy v. Missouri&lt;/em&gt; being a difficult case for the court to parse through, since the states identify a vast range of different actions by different parts of the government with which they take issue. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="q4SiQ0"&gt;Unlike &lt;em&gt;Bantam Books&lt;/em&gt;, Hans said, where “it’s pretty clear what happened, and it was also one specific instance of government interference, here we have a whole plethora of actions that are not necessarily created equal.” He added that the Supreme Court might not be the right place to sort out some of these tricky and fact-specific questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="AEt4VV"&gt;Wide-ranging impact&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="wlqDAW"&gt;Several interest groups wrote amicus briefs to the court warning that no matter how the justices rule, they should be careful not to craft a standard that harms these groups’ work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3oXTpv"&gt;For example, a &lt;a href="https://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/23/23-411/294238/20231226164724890_Election%20Officials%20Amicus%20Brief%20Missouri%20v.%20Murthy%20No%2023%20411.pdf"&gt;bipartisan group of current and former election officials submitted a brief&lt;/a&gt; emphasizing the importance of allowing people in their roles to “remain free to communicate with social media platforms to share accurate information about when, how, and where to vote; to correct false election information; and to address violent threats and intimidation directed at their own ranks.” They also said it’s important that election officials and government agencies are able to respond when social media companies reach out for help in promoting accurate voting information and limiting the spread of false content. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZNXcZ6"&gt;Members of the nonpartisan Election Protection coalition &lt;a href="https://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/23/23-411/294175/20231222150605479_23-411tsacTheLawyersCommitteeForCivilRightsUnderLaw.pdf"&gt;said they fear a ruling for the states&lt;/a&gt; would “endanger the right to vote as information sharing between and among civil society, government, and social media companies is essential to prevent malicious election interference and voter suppression efforts.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3c8ATv"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/23/23-411/294188/20231222155456989_12.22.23%20%20RCFP%20-%20Murthy%20v.%20Missouri%20Brief%20PDF-A.pdf"&gt;The Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press&lt;/a&gt; warned in a brief against creating a standard of coercion that is overly broad. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="tyL3kX"&gt;“A too-sensitive test for coercion could have two negative consequences,” the committee wrote. “First, it could lead to the chilling of the free flow of information from government sources to the news media. Second, it could license plaintiffs to pursue burdensome fishing expeditions for what they believe to be evidence of collusion between journalists and public officials.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="JG6rfB"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Twitter has stopped enforcing its covid misinformation policies","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/29/23483836/twitter-covid-misinformation-policy-enforcement-end"},{"title":"Surgeon general calls out platforms over COVID-19 misinformation","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2021/7/15/22578431/white-house-surgeon-general-facebook-youtube-twitter-covid-19-misinformation-vaccines"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="yZXFM2"&gt;Medical groups including the American Medical Association (AMA) &lt;a href="https://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/23/23-411/294091/20231222102540387_FINAL%20Murthy%20Amicus%20for%20filing.pdf"&gt;asserted in a brief&lt;/a&gt; that the Biden administration has a “‘compelling interest’ in combatting vaccine misinformation.” That’s because, according to the AMA, “it is an indisputable scientific fact that vaccinations save lives.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Uch4vL"&gt;But the &lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2020/02/aaps-make-health-care-great-again/607015/"&gt;smaller and conservative-oriented&lt;/a&gt; Association of American Physicians and Surgeons (AAPS) wrote in a brief that accepting the American Medical Association’s assertion would “green-light government censorship” of people like Robert F. Kennedy, Jr., a presidential candidate and leading voice in the anti-vaccine movement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="v2YGfR"&gt;“The same arguments made by the AMA Amici could be extended to other types of speech disfavored by the Biden Administration, such as criticism of transgender procedures and late-term abortion,” the AAPS wrote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GEfYbB"&gt;NetChoice and the Computer and Communications Industry Association (CCIA), the leading parties on the other social media First Amendment cases this term, joined with other industry groups to make a point about how their cases intersected with this one. While they didn’t take a position on the case itself, &lt;a href="https://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/23/23-411/293958/20231221095300230_231219a%20AC%20Brief%20for%20efiling.pdf"&gt;the groups wrote in a brief&lt;/a&gt; that there needs to be a “clear rule” to prevent governments from compelling platforms’ speech or preventing content moderation “by informal or indirect cajoling or coercion.” They also asked the court to clarify “that those digital services themselves are not state actors and may not be held liable for the government’s actions.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="4BdGbR"&gt;Hans noted that many of the amicus briefs were filed in support of neither party, even from First Amendment groups that would typically take a stand in such a case. “I take that as a sign of the sort of theoretical messiness of the issues in this case,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101298/supreme-court-murthy-missouri-speech-social-media"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101298/supreme-court-murthy-missouri-speech-social-media</id>
    <author>
      <name>Lauren Feiner</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T19:27:42-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T19:27:42-04:00</updated>
    <title>The FCC has finally decreed that 25Mbps and 3Mbps are not ‘broadband’ speed</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/9RW2HZkvg1gWK50oIr3oQjYHVN4=/0x0:3000x2000/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73208182/VRG_ILLO_4341_American_Ethernet.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration by Grayson Blackmon / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="Ekor9z"&gt;“I think our new threshold, frankly, should be 100Mbps. I think anything short of that shortchanges our children, our future, and our new digital economy.” That’s what FCC commissioner Jessica Rosenworcel &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2015/1/29/7932653/fcc-changed-definition-broadband-25mbps"&gt;argued nine years ago&lt;/a&gt; — now, it’s finally happening. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xs9o2r"&gt;Today, the FCC has &lt;a href="https://docs.fcc.gov/public/attachments/DOC-401205A1.pdf"&gt;changed its definition of “broadband”&lt;/a&gt; to mean download speeds of 100 megabits per second and upload speeds of 20 megabits per second. It had been stuck at 25Mbps/3Mbps since 2015. As recently as 2021, outgoing FCC chairman Ajit Pai claimed &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/1/21/22242635/fcc-ajit-pai-internet-speed-advanced-telecommunications-3mbps"&gt;we still didn’t need more than that&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="bDSHco"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"What’s wrong with US broadband?","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2022/11/17/23460070/internet-bill-broadband-survey-data-consumer-reports-cost"},{"title":"The government is helping Big Telecom squeeze out city-run broadband","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23763482/municipal-broadband-biden-internet-funds-telecom-lobbying"},{"title":"We need to fix America’s internet","url":"https://www.theverge.com/22177154/us-internet-speed-maps-competition-availability-fcc"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="oCcPZ7"&gt;These definitions matter, because they let the FCC report whether it’s failing or succeeding to close the broadband gap — and how much &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22177154/us-internet-speed-maps-competition-availability-fcc"&gt;to regulate&lt;/a&gt; (or &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23763482/municipal-broadband-biden-internet-funds-telecom-lobbying"&gt;throw money at&lt;/a&gt;) broadband providers to spread decent internet across the United States. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="o44Z42"&gt;In this case, the money came first: the FCC writes that it based the standard on what federal and state funding grants are already requiring, as well as “consumer usage patterns, and what is actually available from and marketed by internet service providers.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="quxUoC"&gt;Whether 100Mbps and 20Mbps meet your personal definition of “decent” likely depends on where you’ve lived: today, the FCC says almost 28 percent of Americans in rural areas don’t have even that much wired internet available to them. Megabits per second of bandwidth is just one factor in internet access, too — there’s also price &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23655762/l4s-internet-apple-comcast-latency-speed-bandwidth"&gt;and latency&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="S0rMOi"&gt;Here are a few more stats about the broadband gap from the FCC’s press release today:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p id="q5Ql9P"&gt;Fixed terrestrial broadband service (excluding satellite) has not been physically deployed to approximately 24 million Americans, including almost 28% of Americans in rural areas, and more than 23% of people living on Tribal lands&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gmgBQ9"&gt;Mobile 5G-NR coverage has not been physically deployed at minimum speeds of 35/3 Mbps to roughly 9% of all Americans, to almost 36% of Americans in rural areas, and to more than 20% of people living on Tribal lands&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Iwh3I6"&gt;45 million Americans lack access to both 100/20 Mbps fixed service and 35/3 Mbps mobile 5G-NR service&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="tiMTDZ"&gt;Based on the new 1 Gbps per 1,000 students and staff short-term benchmark for schools and classrooms, 74% of school districts meet this goal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p id="Ys8cMh"&gt;The new definition was pushed through by the FCC’s Democratic majority, something it hasn’t had for the majority of President Biden’s term in office. The FCC spent years completely deadlocked without its full five commissioners, until Anna Gomez was finally confirmed by the Senate &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/7/23863365/anna-gomez-fcc-commissioner-senate-confirmation-net-neutrality"&gt;last September&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24101313/fcc-new-broadband-definition-100mbps-20mbps"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24101313/fcc-new-broadband-definition-100mbps-20mbps</id>
    <author>
      <name>Sean Hollister</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T18:02:21-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T18:02:21-04:00</updated>
    <title>Pornhub shuts down in Texas to protest age verification law</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A photo showing Pornhub’s website open on a laptop" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/A2FzgOvc8KWqzwGele9IeoXo-8A=/0x0:3543x2362/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73207959/1246842106.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo Illustration by Adrien Fillon/NurPhoto via Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="GoUnx4"&gt;Pornhub has disabled its site in Texas in response to the state’s online age verification law. The site now displays a message to users in the state that says having to provide an ID when accessing an adult website “is not an effective solution for protecting users online.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="zHa0s0"&gt;Last year, &lt;a href="https://www.texasattorneygeneral.gov/news/releases/attorney-general-ken-paxton-wins-major-victory-protecting-children-obscene-materials"&gt;Texas enacted&lt;/a&gt; a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/31/23854369/texas-porn-age-verification-law-blocked-judge"&gt;previously blocked&lt;/a&gt; age verification law (&lt;a href="https://legiscan.com/TX/text/HB1181/id/2819916"&gt;HB 1181&lt;/a&gt;) that requires users to upload photos of their government IDs (or use another third-party verification service) before accessing a pornographic website. The law &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/12/23914832/texas-hb-1181-porn-age-verification-vixen-media-group"&gt;also requires porn sites&lt;/a&gt; to display health warnings that claim porn impairs “human brain development,” among other unproven issues. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/27/24084615/texas-ken-paxton-pornhub-aylo-lawsuit-age-verification"&gt;Texas sued Pornhub’s parent company&lt;/a&gt; Aylo in February, alleging that Pornhub failed to comply with the new law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="a7oWe1"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-dnt="true" align="center"&gt;
&lt;p lang="en" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/New?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;#New&lt;/a&gt;: Pornhub, one of the largest adult entertainment websites, has completely shut down services in Texas, after the OAG and lawmakers sought to do more to require those websites to verify user age. &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/txlege?src=hash&amp;amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;#txlege&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you pull up Pornhub (don’t ask), this letter comes up ⬇️ &lt;a href="https://t.co/RjavLjUcwU"&gt;pic.twitter.com/RjavLjUcwU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;— Michael Adkison (@madkisonews) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/madkisonews/status/1768348155723014592?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;March 14, 2024&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="m6xoYx"&gt;This isn’t the first time Pornhub has disabled its site in protest of age verification requirements. Last year, Pornhub blocked access to its site in &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/3/23782776/pornhub-blocks-mississippi-virginia-age-verification-laws"&gt;Mississippi, Virginia&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/3/23818865/pornhub-mindgeek-arkansas-age-verification-block-ban-porn"&gt;Arkansas&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/5/2/23707861/pornhub-utah-age-verification-law-protest"&gt;Utah&lt;/a&gt;. It also &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/2/24022539/pornhub-blocked-montana-north-carolina-age-verification-law-protest"&gt;went dark in North Carolina&lt;/a&gt; and Montana in January.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8jamd0"&gt;“As you may know, your elected officials in Texas are requiring us to verify your age before allowing you to access our website,” Pornhub says in a notice to users. “Not only does this impinge on the rights of adults to access protected speech, it fails strict scrutiny by employing the least effective and yet also the most restrictive means of accomplishing Texas’s stated purpose of allegedly protecting minors.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="PEcV3a"&gt;Pornhub argues that on-device age verification is “the only effective solution for protecting minors and adults alike.” This method could involve using facial recognition &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23721306/online-age-verification-privacy-laws-child-safety"&gt;or another method&lt;/a&gt; to verify a user’s age locally on their device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="jHIBFJ"&gt;“Unfortunately the Texas law for age verification is ineffective, haphazard, and dangerous,” Alex Kekesi, Aylo’s vice president of brand and community says in an emailed statement to &lt;em&gt;The Verge.&lt;/em&gt; “Not only will it not actually protect children, it will inevitably reduce content creators’ ability to post and distribute legal adult content and directly impact their ability to share the artistic messages they want to convey with it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rikenY"&gt;Pornhub may soon run into issues outside the US, too. The European Union’s Digital Services Act (DSA) &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/20/24009125/eu-dsa-pornhub-xvideos-stripchat-digital-services-act-age-verification"&gt;designates Pornhub&lt;/a&gt; and other adult sites as “Very Large Online Platforms,” which could require them to implement age verification and take down illegal content. Pornhub sued the EU over its designation last month, &lt;a href="https://www.politico.eu/article/pornhub-sues-eu-over-online-content-rules/"&gt;according to a report from &lt;em&gt;Politico&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24101116/pornhub-texas-age-verification-law-shut-down"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24101116/pornhub-texas-age-verification-law-shut-down</id>
    <author>
      <name>Emma Roth</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T16:41:30-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T16:41:30-04:00</updated>
    <title>The FTC and DOJ think McDonald’s ice cream machines should be legal to fix</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="An image showing McDonald’s ice cream machine" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/qlscuD0iKERzgvXg9dW-SeYIRDM=/232x0:2506x1516/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73207778/ifixit_mcdonalds_ice_cream_machine.0.png" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: iFixit &lt;a class="ql-link" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2uCpY3tFTIA" target="_blank"&gt;via YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="IhAPE3"&gt;The Federal Trade Commission and the Department of Justice’s antitrust division filed a comment with the US Copyright Office asking for an expanded exemption to copyright law for the right to repair certain devices. The &lt;a href="https://www.ftc.gov/system/files/ftc_gov/pdf/ATR-FTC-JointComment.pdf"&gt;comment&lt;/a&gt; was submitted on Thursday, amid the Copyright Office’s deliberations over whether to issue new exemptions to Section 1201 of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA), a law that prohibits breaking software copy protection. Under Section 1201, repairing your own devices can often become a copyright violation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="jwTTdG"&gt;Exemptions to DMCA Section 1201 are issued every three years, as per the Register of Copyrights’ recommendation. Prior &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/10/27/22747310/us-copyright-office-dmca-section-1201-exemption-rulemaking-report"&gt;exemptions&lt;/a&gt; have been issued for jailbreaking cellphones and repairing certain parts of video game consoles. The FTC and DOJ are asking the Copyright Office to go a step further, extending the right to repair to “commercial and industrial equipment.” The comment singles out four distinct categories that would benefit from DMCA exemptions: commercial soft serve machines; proprietary diagnostic kits; programmable logic controllers; and enterprise IT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="E8TNhk"&gt;“In the Agencies’ view, renewing and expanding repair-related exemptions would promote competition in markets for replacement parts, repair, and maintenance services, as well as facilitate competition in markets for repairable products,” the comment reads. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="pWxGKT"&gt;The inability to do third-party repairs on these products not only limits competition, the agencies say, but also makes repairs more costly and&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;can lead to hundreds or thousands of dollars in lost sales. Certain logic controllers have to be discarded and replaced if they break or if the passwords for them get lost. The average estimated cost of “unplanned manufacturing downtime” was $260,000 per hour, the comment notes, citing research from Public Knowledge and iFixit. As for soft serve machines, breakdowns can lead to $625 in lost sales each day. Business owners can’t legally fix them on their own or hire an independent technician to do so, meaning they have to wait around for an authorized technician — which, the comment says, usually takes around 90 days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RQ9NGe"&gt;Last August, iFixit performed a teardown on the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/29/23850595/mcdonalds-broken-ice-cream-machines-ifixit"&gt;exact ice cream machine model McDonald’s uses&lt;/a&gt;. The machine let out multiple “nonsensical, counterintuitive, and seemingly random” error codes, but there was nothing to be done — not because it was unfixable but because the law prohibits anyone but Taylor, the manufacturer, from fixing the machines. After a third-party company, Kytch, built a product that can read the error codes, McDonald’s told its franchise owners not to use it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="tmS4M8"&gt;If the Copyright Office decides to listen to the FTC and DOJ, that could all change. For now, though, the odds the ice cream machine at your local McDonald’s is broken are still pretty high.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24101023/ftc-doj-comment-dmca-ifixit-ice-cream-machines"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24101023/ftc-doj-comment-dmca-ifixit-ice-cream-machines</id>
    <author>
      <name>Gaby Del Valle</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T16:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T16:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Spotify says its iPhone app updates in the EU are getting held up by Apple</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="An illustration of Spotify’s logo." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/7kLZIck-Zl86M-MPHm-Pkhb8JxU=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73207641/STK088_VRG_Illo_N_Barclay_5_spotify.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Nick Barclay / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="an6zpV"&gt;Even after Apple was &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24005938/european-commission-antitrust-apple-investigation-anti-steering-rules-app-developers"&gt;hit with a $2 billion fine&lt;/a&gt; in the European Union over years-old complaints from Spotify about its App Store rules, Spotify says Apple is stonewalling updates issued in compliance with that very ruling. In an email to the European Commission obtained by &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;, Spotify writes that Apple has “neither acknowledged nor responded to Spotify’s submission” to bring subscription pricing information into the app, preventing it from updating the app at all for its users, even to put out fixes for bugs or add other features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="nnqpm9"&gt;On March 5th, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091430/spotify-links-pricing-information-iphone-eu-app"&gt;Spotify submitted an update&lt;/a&gt; to Apple that puts links to Spotify’s website, along with pricing information for different subscription options, directly in the EU version of its app, without using Apple’s payment system. Spotify made the change in response to a ruling issued the day before &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24005938/european-commission-antitrust-apple-investigation-anti-steering-rules-app-developers"&gt;by the European Commission&lt;/a&gt;, which said Apple’s anti-steering rules are “illegal” and ordered Apple to start allowing developers to include information about “alternative and cheaper music subscription services.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3y1hBP"&gt;Apple &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/the-app-store-spotify-and-europes-thriving-digital-music-market/"&gt;responded to the decision on March 4th&lt;/a&gt; by saying it would appeal and pointing out a list of “ways Apple creates value for Spotify, at no cost to their company,” which happened to include this bullet point:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p id="3pn1gv"&gt;Our App Review team has reviewed and approved 421 versions of the Spotify app — usually with same-day turnaround — and frequently expedites reviews at Spotify’s request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/PMaxOBwwuXdPYaT2YS_MvBleYhk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25336218/DMA_Media_Stills_2__1_.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Spotify&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spotify’s update includes pricing information and links to subscriptions.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="ueCClH"&gt;In the email, Spotify says it hasn’t heard back from Apple since submitting the update.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="MWfdMD"&gt;The company writes that this is “yet another example of how Apple if unchecked, will seek to circumvent and/or not comply with the Commission’s decision.” It also urges the European Commission to contact Apple and requires that it approve Spotify’s changes. “Given Apple’s track record, Spotify is concerned that Apple’s delay is intentional and is aimed at delaying or avoiding compliance altogether,” the email reads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dTlXmI"&gt;“It’s been nine days now and we’re still waiting to hear from Apple about our app submission to show EU consumers pricing and a link to our website, which we are now authorized to do by the European Commission’s decision on the music streaming case,” Spotify spokesperson Jeanne Moran says in an emailed statement to &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;. “Apple’s delay directly conflicts with its claim that they turn around reviews on app submissions within 24 hours, and it also flies in the face of the timeline for adoption the Commission laid out.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Q1fHHM"&gt;Apple didn’t provide a comment in response to a request from &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Yzf5jU"&gt;This ruling is separate from the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24091592/eu-dma-competition-compliance-deadline-big-tech-policy-changes"&gt;EU’s Digital Markets Act&lt;/a&gt; (DMA) regulations for big tech platforms that have only been around for about a week, but the European Commission has already intervened in response to one of Apple’s DMA-related decisions. Earlier this month, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092158/epic-apple-developer-account-terminated-digital-markets-act-alternative-ios-app-store"&gt;Apple revoked Epic Games’ developer license&lt;/a&gt; because of criticism CEO Tim Sweeney made about Apple’s DMA compliance plan. Epic Games &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/8/24094543/epic-games-ios-developer-license-apple-dma"&gt;got its developer license back days later&lt;/a&gt;, citing “a swift inquiry” from the European Commission.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100944/spotify-ios-app-update-eu-apple-dma"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100944/spotify-ios-app-update-eu-apple-dma</id>
    <author>
      <name>Emma Roth</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
