<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Apples</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-15T14:18:31-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/apple/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/apple" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T14:18:31-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T14:18:31-04:00</updated>
    <title>PC games start at just $1 in Steam’s spring sale</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/QxhWt9VzPWr3GQZCuEydQvH9L-8=/0x0:920x613/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73210131/steam_spring_sale_2024.0.png" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;From AAA blockbusters to indie cult classics, there are tons of games up to 95 percent off.&lt;/em&gt; | Valve / Steam&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="g0AV6L"&gt;You’d think most gamers would have indulged enough over the long winter season that they wouldn’t want to spend the first moments of spring doing the same, but rainy days are still a thing, yeah? And the grind never truly stops for many of us. That’s why I can appreciate the &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steam spring sale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, happening now through March 21st. It happens around this time every year and offers up to 90 percent off thousands of titles. You can find deals on game-of-the-year-worthy titles like &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1086940/Baldurs_Gate_3/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Baldur’s Gate 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; for $53.99&lt;/a&gt; ($6 off), for example, while &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2344520/Diablo_IV/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diablo IV&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is 50 percent off&lt;/a&gt; no matter which version you buy, whether it’s the base game going for $34.99 or the &lt;em&gt;Ultimate Edition&lt;/em&gt; for $49.99.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="aPUdPk"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"10 great Windows PC games from 2023 ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23979457/best-windows-pc-games-2023"},{"title":"Steam Deck OLED review: better, not faster ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23951655/steam-deck-oled-review"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="MORknD"&gt;It’s also a great chance to check out older titles you may have passed on, such as &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1091500/Cyberpunk_2077/?snr=1_4_springsale__629"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (50 percent off, down to $29.99) or &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2369390/Far_Cry_6/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Far Cry 6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for $14.99 ($45 off). There are tons of cult classics, indie hits, and other low-key titles on sale starting at just $1, too, like the undying &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/550/Left_4_Dead_2/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Left 4 Dead 2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. We’re not seeing any discounts on the &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/steamdeck/"&gt;Steam Deck&lt;/a&gt; or any of the VR headsets in &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/vrhardware/"&gt;Steam’s hardware store&lt;/a&gt;, unfortunately, but be sure to explore more games from the sale if you’re looking for something new to play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="cuowaA"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12193366"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="YOuFUD"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12193982"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="O8BIEr"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10197689"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="BoKVbF"&gt;Considering &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24089999/apple-macbook-air-m3-announced-13-15-inch"&gt;Apple has officially signaled the M1 MacBook Air’s death knell&lt;/a&gt;, Walmart’s latest sale on the outgoing model feels like a last call. The retailer is offloading the &lt;strong&gt;8GB RAM, 256GB SSD MacBook Air with M1&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FApple-MacBook-Air-13-3-inch-Laptop-Space-Gray-M1-Chip-8GB-RAM-256GB-storage%2F609040889&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$699&lt;/a&gt;, which is $300 off compared to its original price and $50 cheaper than the $749 it’s often gone for toward the end of its retail run. It’s a new all-time low price, which we predicted would happen, but perhaps not this soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="MWFMry"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Apple’s new M3 chips have big GPU upgrades focused on gaming and pro apps","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/30/23938676/apple-m3-chip-gpu-upgrade-hardware-accelerated-ray-tracing-gaming-specs-release-date"},{"title":"The MacBook Air’s wedge is truly gone — and I miss it already","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24090112/macbook-air-wedge-laptops-design"},{"title":"Look at this bonkers, beautiful Mac-iPad hybrid","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24090192/look-at-this-bonkers-beautiful-mac-ipad-hybrid"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="T3p1Cm"&gt;Although it’s discontinued, the M1 Air is still getting support and can still serve as a perfectly capable laptop for someone dipping their toes into the MacBook waters for the first time, or perhaps to replace an aging Intel-based model. It’s up to most basic school, work, and browsing tasks for those with lighter needs who would benefit from the long battery life (up to 18 hours) and power efficiency afforded by the Apple-made chipset. I’ve even found this memory-starved model capable of lightweight 4K video editing, photo editing, and other creative tasks. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="4RwrHd"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:9737407"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="gKBJ9y"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="actionbox" data-anthem-component-data='{"title":"Verge Deals on X","description":"Join more than 50,000 followers and keep up with the best daily tech deals with @vergedeals","label":"Follow us!","url":"http://bit.ly/2JzR5Ud"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;h2 id="6DvR1d"&gt;A few more ways to save&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="LzC9S2"&gt;The keyboard has become something of a fashion statement on the modern desk, and&lt;strong&gt; 8Bitdo’s wireless retro mechanical keyboard &lt;/strong&gt;— down to $84.99 ($15 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CCP8KYGG/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; — offers a distinct look resembling a Super Nintendo for those who favor a nostalgic aesthetic&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;The tenkeyless board offers both 2.4GHz and Bluetooth wireless connectivity options (in addition to wired), an integrated volume knob, and ships with two oversized buttons that you can program to execute your favorite macros and other custom functions. The hot-swappable PCB allows you to switch out the Kailh Box V2 switches with ease, too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="UsUAyM"&gt;If you own a Samsung Galaxy smartphone and you need an alternative to AirTags, it’s worth considering a&lt;strong&gt; four-pack of Galaxy SmartTag2 trackers. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://howl.me/clP25RGFVQ5"&gt;Samsung has it down to $74.99&lt;/a&gt; ($25 off). Similar to Apple’s version, SmartTag2 uses Bluetooth ultra-wideband for pinpoint compass-guided directions to your lost items. That functionality requires a&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Galaxy Note 20 Ultra, S21 Plus and Ultra or newer, or a Galaxy Z Fold 2 and newer, although you can use any Samsung phone with SmartThings Find to track down the last known location. The battery can last up to 500 days and up to 40 percent longer in a low-power state, Samsung says, and the trackers can survive a bit of rain or dust with IP67 protection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="R4Byuf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22958216/kitchen-tools-personal-gear-gadgets-favorites"&gt;favorite&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;’s Allison Johnson, the &lt;strong&gt;Breville Barista Express&lt;/strong&gt; is an attractive and versatile espresso machine that &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Breville-BES870XL-Barista-Express-Espresso/dp/B00DS4767K/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clP4iJVM1gt"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://westelm.e54b.net/c/482924/267856/4336?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.williams-sonoma.com%2Fproducts%2F2101673%2F&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Williams Sonoma&lt;/a&gt; have down to $559.99 right now ($140 off). It grinds its own beans at whichever consistency you desire and has an integrated microfoaming milk frother, both helping to make delectable cups of the good stuff with a presentation that will make you forget all about those expensive Starbies runs. It’s also easy to clean and maintain, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/10/23864688/breville-barista-express-home-espresso-maintenance"&gt;says Allison&lt;/a&gt;, whether you’re using its self-cleaning option or opening it up for a deep scrub.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="7enZCU"&gt;If you’re looking for a flagship-rivaling smartphone that simply does exactly what you need it to, we see nothing wrong with the &lt;strong&gt;OnePlus 12R.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s already a great value at $499.99 for the unlocked 128GB storage model, and both &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CW9R75NB/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clP3JT0Cvjg"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt; are throwing in a $100 gift card to sweeten the deal. We wish it had wireless charging and more substantial ingress protection compared to midrange contemporaries from Samsung and Google. Otherwise, it’s hard to find a smartphone at this price with its display quality and size (the 6.78-inch, 1080p display has a 120Hz variable refresh rate), not to mention its respectable photography potential and the strong processing power of the Snapdragon 8 Gen 2. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24072383/oneplus-12r-review-screen-camera-price"&gt;Read our review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;aside id="aSZQAL"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="newsletter" data-anthem-component-data='{"slug":"deals"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101003/steam-spring-sale-m1-macbook-air-breville-barista-express-espresso-machine-deal-sale"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101003/steam-spring-sale-m1-macbook-air-breville-barista-express-espresso-machine-deal-sale</id>
    <author>
      <name>Quentyn Kennemer</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T11:27:02-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T11:27:02-04:00</updated>
    <title>How to make an Apple Vision Pro Persona</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Vector collage showing different aspects of making a Persona on the Vision Pro." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/PuDAt2mir0wigmgijdrowZoqDXg=/0x0:3000x2000/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209576/HT047_VISION_PRO_PERSONA.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Samar Haddad for The Verge | Photo by Apple&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="fpjYR7"&gt;Now that you’ve got your &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24054862/apple-vision-pro-review-vr-ar-headset-features-price"&gt;$3,500 Apple Vision Pro&lt;/a&gt;, gone through the tutorial, and gotten the hang of things, it’s time to do the next best thing: make a Persona.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GS2EGY"&gt;Personas are Apple’s name for a digital avatar of yourself for video calls. Or, in &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/persona/#:~:text=Persona%20is%20a%20natural%20representation,upper%20body%2C%20and%20facial%20expressions."&gt;Apple’s words&lt;/a&gt;, a “natural representation of you that you can use to connect with others.” Aside from FaceTime, your Persona is also used with the &lt;a href="https://duet-cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/0x0:2700x1800/1440x960/filters:focal(1350x900:1351x901):format(webp)/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25255977/246965_vision_pro_AKrales_0002.jpg"&gt;EyeSight feature&lt;/a&gt; — you know, the ghostly eyes that appear on the Vision Pro’s front display. It’s created using image captures and 3D measurements of your head, face, upper body, and facial expressions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="q5ncJe"&gt;But before you go run off and make a Persona, there’s one thing to keep in mind. Right now, Personas are in beta which means... they look kind of cursed. I’ve heard mine described as a soft focus ‘70s-style portrait and as a memorial photo like the ones used in obituaries. Hair often looks blocky, sort of like a non-playable character in a PlayStation 3 game. You’ll recognize yourself, but it won’t quite get everything right. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="QnG8zm"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Apple Vision Pro review: magic, until it’s not ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/24054862/apple-vision-pro-review-vr-ar-headset-features-price"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="aSMc9M"&gt;Personas have gotten a bit better since launch, thanks to software updates, but mine is still not what I’d call a fully “natural representation” of me. But it’s okay — you don’t &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; to make one, especially if you’re worried about privacy, since Apple is essentially taking photos of you to generate the Persona.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;(You can read Apple’s official Persona privacy policy &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/persona/#:~:text=Persona%20is%20a%20natural%20representation,upper%20body%2C%20and%20facial%20expressions."&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="mSEHNC"&gt;How to begin&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="miVSvV"&gt;You’ll get prompted to create your Persona while you’re setting up the Vision Pro. But in the event you skipped that to explore other features, here’s how to get started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="JMNaQT"&gt;Press the digital crown, look at &lt;strong&gt;Settings&lt;/strong&gt;, and pinch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="yOWF2M"&gt;Scroll down and select &lt;strong&gt;Persona.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="PXNRq4"&gt;Select &lt;strong&gt;Get Started.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="AQQv2C"&gt;You’ll be prompted to hold out your hands. Do this, and then wait until you hear the cue to take off your headset. But don’t take it off quite yet, because... &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="DZ3TZf"&gt;...a video will pop up with some pointers. You may want to watch it, because it’s helpful for getting a sense of what you’re supposed to do — especially since you will now take off the headset to continue making your Persona. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Screenshot of the Persona Menu within the Vision Pro" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/A8Kp3N0427Dob4hcKLQAbcF7tt0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25335981/IMG_0041.PNG"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Screenshot: Victoria Song / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;After you’ve made your Persona, you can edit it or recapture. I encourage doing it a few times!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="vcVcjN"&gt;Once you take off the headset, this is a good time to fix your hair and your makeup (if you wear any). You might also want to remove dangly earrings, earbuds, glasses, and hats.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="qsSLqt"&gt;Hold the Vision Pro at eye level with the front display facing toward you. Make sure your entire face is within the circle that appears. Make sure that you’re holding the Vision Pro by its frame and not the light seal or straps. Those attach magnetically and can pop off if you’re not careful.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="h2iIBS"&gt;Follow the directions to slowly look left, right, up, and down. There are arrows and sounds that give you clear visual and audio cues as to where to look and whether you’re doing it correctly. You may hear instructions to redo portions or adjust your facial position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="oVEQZi"&gt;You’ll also be asked to smile with your mouth open and closed, raise your eyebrows, and close your eyes. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="DjycVF"&gt;When capture is done, put the headset back on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div id="gPYhQU"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12279322"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="WnKBJl"&gt;You should see a preview of your Persona. Bask in its cursed image. But there are still some things you can do to edit how it appears. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="Phk7Sa"&gt;You can select lighting styles. Natural is, well, natural, while Studio brightens everything up and Contour adds some extra shadowing. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="WgySFI"&gt;There are also sliders at the bottom that let you adjust the photo temperature and brightness. If you wear glasses, this is where you can swipe through various styles. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="2a6Bcf"&gt;When you’re done, tap &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt;. If it’s too cursed, you can hit &lt;strong&gt;Recapture&lt;/strong&gt; and go through the process again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mgRYkE"&gt;It’s okay if you need to try making your Persona a second time. I’ve made three thus far, and here are a couple of tips:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="ljF8sz"&gt;Open your eyes wide and exaggerate your facial expressions more than you normally would during capture. Inside the headset, I tend to have “resting sleepy face” and that makes my Persona look a little stoned. Starting out with wider eyes and bigger facial expressions has, according to my friends, resulted in my Persona looking more like me. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="8DTgQO"&gt;Make sure you have good, even lighting. If you have funky light or really strong backlighting, you might end up with odd shadowing. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Screenshot of two people talking on FaceTime with Personas in Vision Pro" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3smNjVij5eZKfJ8FOYU-EAS29n0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25336348/IMG_0095.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Screenshot: Wes Davis / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wes and I regularly FaceTime to make silly faces with our new Personas.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mGG18C"&gt;At this point, it’s imperative that you call your best friend or loved ones on FaceTime. This way, you can listen to them roast you. Better yet, if you know someone who has a Vision Pro, call them and the two of you can have a jolly time laughing at how your Personas turned out. I did this with our weekend news editor Wes Davis, and we had a great time guffawing over how his mustache would not move. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="33rrUZ"&gt;So long as you don’t go in with too high expectations, Persona FaceTimes can be a fun conversation starter with people you know. Have a lot of people laughed at my expense? Sure, but I’d be lying if I said I didn’t have a blast in the process. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gQhg6H"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24100674/apple-vision-pro-persona-how-to"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24100674/apple-vision-pro-persona-how-to</id>
    <author>
      <name>Victoria Song</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T09:58:02-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T09:58:02-04:00</updated>
    <title>The wedge-shaped M1 MacBook Air lives on — at Walmart, for $699</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="The new MacBook Air is fast" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3Zr5g_HbeCTGXphQ1MSMlrDANzU=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209244/vpavic_4291_20201113_0380.0.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Walmart’s selling them for $699 with 8GB of RAM and 256GB of storage.&lt;/em&gt; | Photo by Vjeran Pavic / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="vTMiJg"&gt;When Apple stopped selling the M1 MacBook Air last week to make way for &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24089999/apple-macbook-air-m3-announced-13-15-inch"&gt;the new M3 version&lt;/a&gt;, I mourned &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24090112/macbook-air-wedge-laptops-design"&gt;the loss of the M1 Air’s iconic wedge shape&lt;/a&gt;. But perhaps that was a bit premature. Walmart &lt;a href="https://corporate.walmart.com/news/2024/03/15/walmart-brings-the-popular-macbook-air-with-the-m1-chip-to-its-shelves"&gt;just announced&lt;/a&gt; that for the first time, you’ll be able to directly buy the M1 MacBook Air &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FApple-MacBook-Air-13-3-inch-Laptop-Silver-M1-Chip-8GB-RAM-256GB-storage%2F609040889&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;from its online store for a discounted $699&lt;/a&gt;. The retailer also said the M1 Air is coming to select retail stores soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rUaenN"&gt;Looking at Walmart’s site, these M1 Airs are being sold new, which makes the $699 price compelling (Best Buy will also &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clP3qrJRdXP"&gt;deliver a new one for $999&lt;/a&gt; if you prefer to pay full price). That said, you only get to choose the base model, which comes with 8GB of RAM and 256GB of storage. I’d normally bristle at 8GB of RAM in 2024 — but the drop to $699 takes some of the sting out of that, and it’s even lower than &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22399419/apple-macbook-air-pro-mac-mini-imac-deals#:~:text=with%20Parallels.-,The%20best%20MacBook%20Air%20deals,-M1%20MacBook%20Air"&gt;recent discounts&lt;/a&gt; that had taken the laptop’s price down to $749. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="MgXcH3"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The MacBook Air’s wedge is truly gone — and I miss it already ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24090112/macbook-air-wedge-laptops-design"},{"title":"The M3 MacBook Air has a familiar look ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/24092910/apple-macbook-air-m3-first-impressions"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="QtNG1A"&gt;The one thing that’s unclear is how long Apple will continue supplying Walmart with new M1 Airs or whether this is a short-term arrangement until the existing stock is cleared out. We’ve reached out to Apple for clarification but didn’t immediately receive a response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="V3pSzy"&gt;If this is an ongoing deal, that’s huge for Walmart and wedge-heads everywhere. And even if it isn’t, at least it gives folks the option of getting one before they’re truly gone. The M1 Air is a beloved laptop, and it warms the heart to see the wedge shape will be around for just a smidge longer.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101727/apple-m1-macbook-air-laptop-walmart"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101727/apple-m1-macbook-air-laptop-walmart</id>
    <author>
      <name>Victoria Song</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T16:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T16:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Spotify says its iPhone app updates in the EU are getting held up by Apple</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="An illustration of Spotify’s logo." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/7kLZIck-Zl86M-MPHm-Pkhb8JxU=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73207641/STK088_VRG_Illo_N_Barclay_5_spotify.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Nick Barclay / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="an6zpV"&gt;Even after Apple was &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24005938/european-commission-antitrust-apple-investigation-anti-steering-rules-app-developers"&gt;hit with a $2 billion fine&lt;/a&gt; in the European Union over years-old complaints from Spotify about its App Store rules, Spotify says Apple is stonewalling updates issued in compliance with that very ruling. In an email to the European Commission obtained by &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;, Spotify writes that Apple has “neither acknowledged nor responded to Spotify’s submission” to bring subscription pricing information into the app, preventing it from updating the app at all for its users, even to put out fixes for bugs or add other features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="nnqpm9"&gt;On March 5th, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091430/spotify-links-pricing-information-iphone-eu-app"&gt;Spotify submitted an update&lt;/a&gt; to Apple that puts links to Spotify’s website, along with pricing information for different subscription options, directly in the EU version of its app, without using Apple’s payment system. Spotify made the change in response to a ruling issued the day before &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24005938/european-commission-antitrust-apple-investigation-anti-steering-rules-app-developers"&gt;by the European Commission&lt;/a&gt;, which said Apple’s anti-steering rules are “illegal” and ordered Apple to start allowing developers to include information about “alternative and cheaper music subscription services.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3y1hBP"&gt;Apple &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/the-app-store-spotify-and-europes-thriving-digital-music-market/"&gt;responded to the decision on March 4th&lt;/a&gt; by saying it would appeal and pointing out a list of “ways Apple creates value for Spotify, at no cost to their company,” which happened to include this bullet point:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p id="3pn1gv"&gt;Our App Review team has reviewed and approved 421 versions of the Spotify app — usually with same-day turnaround — and frequently expedites reviews at Spotify’s request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/PMaxOBwwuXdPYaT2YS_MvBleYhk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25336218/DMA_Media_Stills_2__1_.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Spotify&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spotify’s update includes pricing information and links to subscriptions.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="ueCClH"&gt;In the email, Spotify says it hasn’t heard back from Apple since submitting the update.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="MWfdMD"&gt;The company writes that this is “yet another example of how Apple if unchecked, will seek to circumvent and/or not comply with the Commission’s decision.” It also urges the European Commission to contact Apple and requires that it approve Spotify’s changes. “Given Apple’s track record, Spotify is concerned that Apple’s delay is intentional and is aimed at delaying or avoiding compliance altogether,” the email reads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dTlXmI"&gt;“It’s been nine days now and we’re still waiting to hear from Apple about our app submission to show EU consumers pricing and a link to our website, which we are now authorized to do by the European Commission’s decision on the music streaming case,” Spotify spokesperson Jeanne Moran says in an emailed statement to &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;. “Apple’s delay directly conflicts with its claim that they turn around reviews on app submissions within 24 hours, and it also flies in the face of the timeline for adoption the Commission laid out.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Q1fHHM"&gt;Apple didn’t provide a comment in response to a request from &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Yzf5jU"&gt;This ruling is separate from the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24091592/eu-dma-competition-compliance-deadline-big-tech-policy-changes"&gt;EU’s Digital Markets Act&lt;/a&gt; (DMA) regulations for big tech platforms that have only been around for about a week, but the European Commission has already intervened in response to one of Apple’s DMA-related decisions. Earlier this month, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092158/epic-apple-developer-account-terminated-digital-markets-act-alternative-ios-app-store"&gt;Apple revoked Epic Games’ developer license&lt;/a&gt; because of criticism CEO Tim Sweeney made about Apple’s DMA compliance plan. Epic Games &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/8/24094543/epic-games-ios-developer-license-apple-dma"&gt;got its developer license back days later&lt;/a&gt;, citing “a swift inquiry” from the European Commission.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100944/spotify-ios-app-update-eu-apple-dma"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100944/spotify-ios-app-update-eu-apple-dma</id>
    <author>
      <name>Emma Roth</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T12:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>The latest Prince of Persia, Returnal, and other PS hits are up to 50 percent off </title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Two Persian statues facing each other outside against the sky." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/b7f7ntk09B7z5hopXVYqMweCJX4=/75x0:885x540/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73206890/princeofpersia.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can buy &lt;/em&gt;Prince of Persia: The Lost Crown&lt;em&gt; for just $30.&lt;/em&gt; | Image: Ubisoft&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="vGckeD"&gt;What’s with all the good PlayStation deals lately? First, the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/PlayStation-Console-Marvels-Spider-Man-Bundle-5/dp/B0CKZGY5B6/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;disc-based&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/PlayStation-Digital-Marvels-Spider-Man-Bundle-5/dp/B0CV4J3TS7/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;discless&lt;/a&gt; versions of the PS5 “slim” dropped to an all-time low (with a digital copy of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23915605/spider-man-2-review-ps5"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marvel’s Spider-Man 2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, no less). Now, Sony is taking up to 80 percent off a ton of PlayStation games through March 27th as part of its &lt;a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-us/category/9d01f039-7058-43e2-93c2-e462d977dc63/2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Picks sale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which drops digital copies of newer hits like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24035933/prince-of-persia-the-lost-crown-review-ubisoft"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prince of Persia: The Lost Crown&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/UP0001-PPSA10067_00-MEMSTDED00000000"&gt;$29.99 ($20 off)&lt;/a&gt; and both &lt;a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/UP0082-PPSA10664_00-FF16SIEA00000002"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Final Fantasy XVI&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/UP0001-PPSA01576_00-AVATAR2GAME00001"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Avatar: Frontiers of Pandora&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to $41.99 ($28 off).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="VKcnP7"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Final Fantasy XVI adds blood and grit but doesn’t change the series’ soul","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23767669/final-fantasy-xvi-review-ps5"},{"title":"Final Fantasy VII Rebirth is a modern open-world RPG with the soul of 1997 ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/24079544/final-fantasy-7-rebirth-review-ps5"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ih9yCf"&gt;Hundreds of other older games are on sale, too, so you’ll likely find something that’ll strike your fancy if none of the newer games do. Right now, for example, you can challenge yourself for hours on end with either &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/29/22408468/returnal-ps5-dualsense-3d-audio"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Returnal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22150718/demons-souls-remake-ps5-playstation-5-sony-game-of-the-year-2020"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Demon’s Souls&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which are on sale with their DLC for &lt;a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/UP9000-PPSA01284_00-RETURNALDDE00001"&gt;$39.99 ($40 off)&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/UP9000-PPSA01342_00-DEMONSSOULSDX000"&gt;$49.49 ($40 off)&lt;/a&gt;, respectively. You can also snag &lt;em&gt;Spider-Man: Game of the Year Edition&lt;/em&gt; for &lt;a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/UP9000-CUSA02299_00-MARVELSSMGOTY000"&gt;$19.99 ($20 off)&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;em&gt;The Last of Us Part I&lt;/em&gt; for&lt;a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/UP9000-PPSA03396_00-THELASTOFUSPART1"&gt; $39.89 ($30 off)&lt;/a&gt; if you want to get ahead before diving into their respective sequels. And if you’re after something more relaxing, there’s always &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/7/18/23220428/stray-video-game-review-ps4-ps5-steam"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Stray&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;(now &lt;a href="https://store.playstation.com/en-us/product/UP2470-PPSA02100_00-STRAYSIEA0000000"&gt;$19.79&lt;/a&gt;), which has become a hit &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23271212/stray-game-cats-watching-twitter-annapurna-interactive"&gt;with humans and cats alike&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="wKCkW4"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12278443"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="gLobW4"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12036865"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="NQ55nS"&gt;If you’ve been thinking about picking up a pair of fitness-focused earbuds, &lt;strong&gt;Jabra’s Elite 8 Active &lt;/strong&gt;are available through March 24th from &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Jabra-Elite-Active-Wireless-Earbuds/dp/B0CB9563MB?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clPbsE1vVvE"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.jabra.com/bluetooth-headsets/jabra-elite-8-active/buy/##100-99160701-98"&gt;direct from Jabra&lt;/a&gt; for $159.99 ($40 off). That’s just $10 shy of their all-time low, which we last saw during the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="tfr6bZ"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Sonos soundbars and speakers are on sale just in time for March Madness","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100247/sonos-ray-beam-sub-mini-move-2-march-madness-deal-sale"},{"title":"The best wireless earbuds to buy right now","url":"https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="cz9rMk"&gt;Like their predecessors, the Elite 8 Active feature effective noise cancellation and a design that should allow them to stay firmly in place even during vigorous workouts. The new model boasts an improved IP68 rating for dust and water resistance and meets the military standard for ruggedized electronics, making them even more durable than before. At the same time, they deliver good sound with support for multipoint connectivity and wireless charging. Plus, thanks to &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.jabra.com%2Fsupport%2Frelease-notes%2Frelease-note-jabra-elite-8-active&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F14%2F24099507%2Fprince-of-persia-ps5-games-jabra-earbuds-anker-511-charger-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;a recent OTA software update&lt;/a&gt;, they support better wind detection, which should allow you to cut back on unwanted noise when running outside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="7hgrQf"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12070746" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="74Hhnv"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="actionbox" data-anthem-component-data='{"title":"Verge Deals on X","description":"Join more than 50,000 followers and keep up with the best daily tech deals with @vergedeals","label":"Follow us!","url":"http://bit.ly/2JzR5Ud"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;h2 id="N6xriK"&gt;Five more ways to save&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="YEgc9m"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23835595/samsung-galaxy-tab-s9-plus-ultra-tablet-review"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Samsung’s base Galaxy Tab S9&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;is on sale at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/SAMSUNG-Snapdragon-Processor-Included-Graphite/dp/B0C4BC6R95?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; with 128GB of storage for $679.99 ($120 off), one of its better prices to date. If you’re looking for a speedy Android tablet for entertainment and light productivity, the standard S9 is a terrific option. It’s great for watching movies thanks to its lovely 120Hz OLED display and Dolby Atmos-compatible speakers, the latter of which sound just as good while listening to music. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23835595/samsung-galaxy-tab-s9-plus-ultra-tablet-review"&gt;Read our review.&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="syq58E"&gt;Now through March 20th, you can pick up a PC copy of &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave the Diver&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; for $14.99 ($5 off) via &lt;a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/8532386/type/dlg/sid/verge/https://www.humblebundle.com/store/dave-the-diver-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;H&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-8836598-14555742?sid=vergedeals031424&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.humblebundle.com%2Fstore%2Fdave-the-diver-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;umble&lt;/a&gt;. My colleague Jay Peters said the Nintendo Switch version of the deep diving adventure game &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/25/23930889/dave-the-diver-nintendo-switch"&gt;was one of his favorite titles from last year&lt;/a&gt;, with charming characters, stunning pixel art, and a great soundtrack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="yzGYZ0"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2F1-or-2-pack-apple-airtag-leather-key-ring-7&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F14%2F24099507%2Fprince-of-persia-ps5-games-jabra-earbuds-anker-511-charger-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Woot is on&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-8836598-13142092?sid=vergedeals031424&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2F1-or-2-pack-apple-airtag-leather-key-ring-7" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;ce again selling a single&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;leather&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;AirTag Key Ring&lt;/strong&gt; for $14.99 ($20 off), or a pair for $19.99 ($50 off). This time, though, you can also get an extra $3 off an individual Key Ring or a two-pack when you apply code &lt;strong&gt;TECHDEAL&lt;/strong&gt;, which drops them to $11.99 and $16.99, respectively. Although discontinued, Apple’s leather accessories remain &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/20/23882255/apple-iphone-15-finewoven-case-wallet-bad"&gt;far more durable than its new FineWoven options&lt;/a&gt;, allowing you to attach them to your belongings longer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="lVkhUt"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Ember’s Travel Mug 2 Plus&lt;/strong&gt; is on sale for around $159.99 ($40 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Ember-Travel-Temperature-Control-Smart/dp/B0CK639YVV/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clPjk5xGP0t"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-8836598-13720150?sid=vergedeals031424&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wayfair.com%2Fkitchen-tabletop%2Fpdp%2Fember-travel-mug-2-12-oz-temperature-control-smart-travel-mug-black-ebdr1009.html" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Wayfair&lt;/a&gt;. Like the standard model, Ember’s newer smart mug can keep your coffee hot all day using the included charging coaster (or for up to three hours using the built-in battery). The Plus model can also tap into Apple’s extensive Find My network, so you can easily locate the 12-ounce vessel using your iPhone, Mac, and other Apple devices should you ever lose it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="id__2ktudjy35sr"&gt;You can buy &lt;strong&gt;Anker’s versatile 511 Charger &lt;/strong&gt;at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Charger-Anker-Foldable-iPhone-Included/dp/B0CQ551F44?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; starting at $15.99 ($7 off), which matches its all-time low. The USB-C GaN charger can supply phones, tablets, laptops, and other electronics with up to 30W of power, yet it’s also small enough to easily toss in your bag before heading out the door.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;aside id="8zzy7J"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="newsletter" data-anthem-component-data='{"slug":"deals"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24099507/prince-of-persia-ps5-games-jabra-earbuds-anker-511-charger-deal-sale"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24099507/prince-of-persia-ps5-games-jabra-earbuds-anker-511-charger-deal-sale</id>
    <author>
      <name>Sheena Vasani</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-13T16:40:01-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-13T16:40:01-04:00</updated>
    <title>Epic asks judge to enforce the Apple App Store injunction</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="An illustration of the Epic Games logo." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/RF_HKCXgUghjo5vveaCM9lb874o=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73205146/acastro_STK108__03.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration: Alex Castro / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="wSKElB"&gt;Epic Games &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24049014/apple-epic-court-ruling-developer-tax"&gt;isn’t done with Apple&lt;/a&gt;. A &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/9/10/22662320/epic-apple-ruling-injunction-judge-court-app-store"&gt;2021 ruling&lt;/a&gt; forced Apple to allow developers of App Store apps to link to outside payments, and Epic has now filed a motion asking Judge Yvonne Gonzalez Rogers to enforce her original order. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="cEoVOZ"&gt;Epic says &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/16/24040881/apple-outside-payments-app-store-policies-iphone-ipad"&gt;Apple’s updated developer policy&lt;/a&gt; that still reserves 27 percent of outside payments (or 12 percent for small developers) for Apple itself is still unjustified. Epic argues these fees are “essentially the same” as those the company charges for using its payments system. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="WEG2s7"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Epic preps its challenge to Apple’s ‘bad-faith’ outside payments changes","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/31/24056751/epic-notice-apple-app-store-outside-payments-link-27-percent"},{"title":"Epic Games v. Apple: the fight for the future of the App Store","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/29/22410877/epic-games-apple-app-store-antitrust-trial-lawsuit-news"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="VTKEqY"&gt;Christian Owens, who founded payments processor Paddle, and Benjamin Simon, the founder behind the Down Dog fitness apps for iOS, agreed in declarations also filed by Epic. Owens called the choice offered by Apple “illusory,” while Simon said his company, Yoga Buddhi Co., would still have to charge more for the iOS version than the web version of its subscriptions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="tcEA0s"&gt;Epic also says that Apple requires developers to use a specific “Plain Button Style,” which Epic says “is not a button at all” and violates the injunction on Apple forbidding developers from steering — that is, pointing customers to alternative payment “buttons, external links, or other calls to action.” It says that Apple disallowing multi-platform apps like &lt;em&gt;Minecraft &lt;/em&gt;from pointing to outside payments violates the judge’s order as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="bQXEDH"&gt;Epic spokesperson Natalie Muñoz told &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; in an email that Apple’s new policies prohibit “the kind of steering Down Dog used in its Android apps” — on Android, Down Dog is able to point its users to its website for cheaper subscriptions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="j1z9mt"&gt;The judge’s original injunction didn’t specifically mention steering, so&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Epic’s request seems to hinge on how she interprets her own order and whether steering is implicitly included.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Some close observers, at least, think Epic has a good legal argument. Daniel McCuaig, an attorney who used to be part of the Department of Justice’s antitrust division, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24049014/apple-epic-court-ruling-developer-tax"&gt;told &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; in January&lt;/a&gt; that Apple’s outside payment terms were untenable and that it was “unlikely” that the court “ultimately blesses” the 27 percent fee. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="dpH3mE"&gt;&lt;div style="left: 0; width: 100%; height: 0; position: relative; padding-bottom: 129.2857%; padding-top: 80px;"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://embed.documentcloud.org/documents/24480087-897/?embed=1" style="top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute; border: 0;" allowfullscreen=""&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099734/epic-v-apple-app-store-outside-payments-motion-enforce-injunction"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099734/epic-v-apple-app-store-outside-payments-motion-enforce-injunction</id>
    <author>
      <name>Wes Davis</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-13T12:44:44-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-13T12:44:44-04:00</updated>
    <title>Speck’s sitewide sale takes 20 percent off cases and accessories</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/NbtlqMZbhyh4kMkgET62gG1mrdU=/0x26:841x587/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73204245/speck_iphone_case.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can use our exclusive discount code on anything at Speck’s site.&lt;/em&gt; | Speck / Amazon&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="6KjVUC"&gt;Whether you’re looking to protect a new phone or freshen up the look of an older one, &lt;strong&gt;Speck’s sitewide sale&lt;/strong&gt; is a great place to start. Exclusively for readers of &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; until March 18th, you can save 20 percent on anything you purchase from &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F13%2F24099409%2Fspeck-cases-fitbit-ace-3-sling-tv-orange-amazon-fire-tv-omni-sale-deal" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;the case maker’s site&lt;/a&gt;. Just use code &lt;strong&gt;20VERGE&lt;/strong&gt; at checkout to receive the discount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="zOA443"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Verge’s favorite mobile phone gadgets ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/24048027/phone-accessories-case-iphone-pixel-samsung-favorite"},{"title":"Clicks hands-on: this BlackBerry-like iPhone case could be a winner ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/11/24034555/clicks-keyboard-case-iphone-hands-on"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="G9USEE"&gt;Speck makes &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fapple&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;cases for both Apple&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fsamsung&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;Samsung devices&lt;/a&gt;, from iPhones and flagship Galaxy Android phones to &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fall-ipad&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;tablets&lt;/a&gt; and even &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fall-airpods&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;AirPods&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fmacbook-pro&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;MacBooks&lt;/a&gt;. You can choose from several fun colors with one of the opaque &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fiphone-15-cases-for-2023%2Fproducts%2Fpresidio2-grip-magsafe-with-clicklock-iphone-15-cases&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;Presidio2 Grip iPhone 15 cases&lt;/a&gt; or show off your phone’s natural beauty with a &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fiphone-15-cases-for-2023%2Fproducts%2Fpresidio-perfect-clear-magsafe-with-clicklock-iphone-15-cases&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;Presidio Perfect-Clear&lt;/a&gt; case, for example. They have MagSafe magnets and antimicrobial protection and are down to $39.99 each ($10 off) after the discount. Speck also sells &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fbags&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;bags&lt;/a&gt; like the &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fbags%2Fproducts%2Ftp30l-bpk&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;Transfer Pro 30L Backpack&lt;/a&gt;, which is down to $79.99 ($20 off) when using the promo code. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="thbNBv"&gt;You’ll also find &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fscreen-protectors&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;screen protectors&lt;/a&gt; and a variety of &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fmagsafe-accessories&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;MagSafe accessories&lt;/a&gt;, like a &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fmagsafe-accessories%2Fproducts%2Fcar-vent-mount-for-magsafe-with-clicklock&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;car vent mount&lt;/a&gt; ($31.99, or $8 off) and attachments like &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fmagsafe-accessories%2Fproducts%2Fwallet-for-magsafe-with-clicklock&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;wallets&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fmagsafe-accessories%2Fproducts%2Fstandygrip-for-magsafe-stand-and-grip-combo-with-clicklock&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;kickstands&lt;/a&gt; for $23.99 each ($6 off), some of which work with its ClickLock design that’s said to offer a more secure magnetic attachment. If you don’t need MagSafe, you can find &lt;a href="https://imp.i308314.net/c/482924/827945/11638?u=https%3A%2F%2Fspeckproducts.com%2Fcollections%2Fiphone-15-cases-for-2023%2Fproducts%2Fgemshell-glitter-iphone-15-cases&amp;amp;subid1=vergeroundupdeals031324"&gt;case options starting as low as $19.99&lt;/a&gt; ($5 off).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="2AVg62"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12277932"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="hyO3Me"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12277945"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="4hUHQz"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12277956"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="dhpZjn"&gt;It’s never a bad idea to get your children used to developing healthy habits early in life. That’s where the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/3/9/22315951/fitbit-ace-3-fitness-tracker-kids"&gt;Fitbit Ace 3&lt;/a&gt; can help. It’s a basic activity band designed for children ages six and older, and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08VKWCL22?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clPaOZBlA8m"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt; have it down to the lowest price we’ve seen at $39.95 right now (about $40 off).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="2VaPPh"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The best Fitbits for your fitness and health ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/22982833/best-fitbit-watch-fitness-tracker"},{"title":"The best fitness trackers to buy right now ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/22985108/best-fitness-tracker"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="9qhgre"&gt;The Ace 3 is a rugged and simple activity tracking band that works with iPhones and Android smartphones. It’s water resistant and lasts up to eight days. Your child can refer to the basic display to track their steps and clock how long they’re engaged in activity on any given day, earning them virtual badges to help gamify their fitness. It also tracks sleep and reminds them when it’s time to go to bed, because they surely won’t keep an eye on the clock themselves. It doesn’t have GPS location tracking or any communication features, however, so you’ll want to consider another option if you need extra utility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="VDRXQt"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11100204"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="8N9GkA"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="actionbox" data-anthem-component-data='{"title":"Verge Deals on X","description":"Join more than 50,000 followers and keep up with the best daily tech deals with @vergedeals","label":"Follow us!","url":"http://bit.ly/2JzR5Ud"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;h2 id="l2ow8g"&gt;More midweek deals to shop&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="yYjSHp"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Four months of Sling TV’s Orange package&lt;/strong&gt; would normally cost at least $160, but &lt;a href="https://sling-tv.pxf.io/c/482924/1132376/14334?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.sling.com%2F&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;new customers can save $40&lt;/a&gt; when prepaying for a four-month subscription, bringing your total down to $120. (You’ll need to scroll down the page a bit to find the deal, then click the orange button that says “Get This Deal.”) Just in time for March Madness, Sling Orange offers access to ESPN, ESPN 2, and ESPN 3 (which will simulcast any games from the NCAA basketball tournament that air on ABC) in addition to 28 other popular channels, including Disney, TBS, TNT, AMC, Comedy Central, Food Network, and more. Your subscription includes 50 hours of DVR storage, but you can only watch on one device at a time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="ybmujB"&gt;You can buy a &lt;strong&gt;Baseus portable MagSafe charger&lt;/strong&gt; for $22.79 (about $23 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0CFF3FWW7?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; when clipping the coupon and using promo code &lt;strong&gt;HJCO3JIO.&lt;/strong&gt; The power bank has a 10,000mAh capacity and features 20W USB-C Power Delivery charging in addition to magnetic 7.5W Qi charging. You can recharge it in less than two hours thanks to 18W passthrough charging. You can also charge, say, a pair of AirPods on the Qi pad and your iPhone over USB-C simultaneously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="PEucfl"&gt;Now until March 31st, &lt;a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-8836598-13142092?sid=vergeroundupdeals031324&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-accessory-bundle-2" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Woot has a bundle&lt;/a&gt; that packs an &lt;strong&gt;Apple Watch charger and two 45mm sport bands&lt;/strong&gt; for $29.99, which is $48 off compared to buying them separately. The sport bands come in the same midnight black color but in differing sizes (S / M and M / L) to help you find the best fit. They’ll ship in generic packaging, but Woot insists the items are new and come with the original one-year Apple warranty.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="gMox1b"&gt;Exclusively for Prime members, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08T6F8YBH?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; has the &lt;strong&gt;50-inch Fire TV Omni&lt;/strong&gt; down to $299.99 ($180 off), which is only $20 more than the all-time low. Your purchase also comes with a free six-month subscription to MGM Plus. If you don’t have a Prime membership, you can still buy it for $329.99, which is a pretty good deal for a 4K TV that makes it easy to access Amazon’s deep content library comprising movies, shows, and games. It has three HDMI inputs, including HDMI eArc, and there’s a built-in microphone to help you call on Alexa without lifting a finger. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22785648/amazon-fire-tv-omni-review-alexa"&gt;Read our review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;aside id="ffngOG"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="newsletter" data-anthem-component-data='{"slug":"deals"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099409/speck-cases-fitbit-ace-3-sling-tv-orange-amazon-fire-tv-omni-sale-deal"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099409/speck-cases-fitbit-ace-3-sling-tv-orange-amazon-fire-tv-omni-sale-deal</id>
    <author>
      <name>Quentyn Kennemer</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-12T14:34:26-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-12T14:34:26-04:00</updated>
    <title>Grid’s framed, nostalgia-inducing gadgets are up to 40 percent off</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/megjC0_X00lY_3IC9cfGXrB4AHw=/0x0:1080x720/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73201775/Grid_Game_Boy_Color_Press_Image.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The framed edition of the atomic purple Game Boy Color is nearly $30 off for a limited time.&lt;/em&gt; | Image: Grid&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="slYX1w"&gt;Of all the tech-centric artwork I’ve seen over the years, few pieces have grabbed me as much as Grid Studio’s framed gadgets and gizmos. The company has been slinging the collage-like pieces for several years now, taking oft-forgotten devices once destined for the landfill and putting them on full display in classy shadowbox-style frames with exploded views. And now, thanks to its &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fgridstudio.cc%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F12%2F24097671%2Fgrid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;annual spring sales event&lt;/a&gt;, Grid is offering up to 40 percent off select items through the end of March.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="2hkTTU"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Frame has become such a hit that Samsung is making a speaker version","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/7/24029243/samsung-music-frame-speaker-announced-specs-features"},{"title":"How to modernize your retro game collection in a few convoluted steps","url":"https://www.theverge.com/24072166/retro-classic-game-roms-nfc-mister-how-to-modern"},{"title":"It’s clearly time: all the news about the transparent tech renaissance","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23774468/clear-transparent-tech-gadgets-news-announcements-products"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="pwo4hK"&gt;There are plenty of retro and contemporary items to choose from, from controllers to smartphones to gaming consoles that once dominated the handheld market in the US. The &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fgridstudio.cc%2Fproducts%2Fgrid%25C2%25AE4s&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F12%2F24097671%2Fgrid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;iPhone 4S&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fgridstudio.cc%2Fproducts%2Fgrid%25C2%25AE-nes-controller&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F12%2F24097671%2Fgrid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;original NES controller&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;— both of which are on sale for $99 ($70 off), matching their all-time low — are the most notable at 40 percent off, though you can also save 15 percent on an assortment of other pieces when you clip the on-page coupon or use promo code &lt;strong&gt;SP15 &lt;/strong&gt;at checkout. Personally, I’m partial to the see-through &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fgridstudio.cc%2Fproducts%2Fgame-boy-color&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F12%2F24097671%2Fgrid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Boy Color&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (now $161.15) as well as &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fgridstudio.cc%2Fproducts%2Fgrid%25C2%25AE-motorola-razr-v3&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F12%2F24097671%2Fgrid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Motorola’s iconic Razr V3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (now $126.65) and the &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fgridstudio.cc%2Fproducts%2Fgrid%25C2%25AE-ipod-photo&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F12%2F24097671%2Fgrid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;iPod Photo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (now $169.15) from ’04. After all, I’m an absolute sucker &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/circuitbreaker/2018/11/21/18105423/ipod-click-wheel-button-music-control-hardware-design"&gt;for a good click wheel&lt;/a&gt; and a headphone jack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="ni3Y4J"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12043362"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="9kUJK0"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12276901"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="L28R31"&gt;Sony has long been a player in the personal audio space, but in the last decade or so, it’s really become known for premium noise-canceling headphones like the &lt;strong&gt;WH-1000XM5&lt;/strong&gt;. Thankfully, if you want to see what all the fuss is about, Amazon is currently &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/deal/0bc5d519/"&gt;hosting an expansive sale&lt;/a&gt; on all things Sony, dropping discounts on headphones, gaming headsets, earbuds, and various pieces of home theater equipment. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="UX0UyG"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The best noise-canceling headphones to buy right now","url":"https://www.theverge.com/21345733/best-noise-canceling-headphones"},{"title":"Sony’s InZone gaming monitors and headsets are for more than just PS5 gamers","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2022/6/28/23180410/sony-inzone-gaming-monitors-hands-on-specs-price-ps5-pc"},{"title":"You can grab a PS5 with Marvel’s Spider-Man 2 for $399.99 right now","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/9/24094340/sony-playstation-5-ps5-slim-bundle-spider-man-2-ipad-pro-m1-m2-deal-sale"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="k1i8Nx"&gt;On the headphone front, the XM5 are &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Sony-WH-1000XM5-Headphones-Hands-Free-WH1000XM5/dp/B0BXYCS74H?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;down to $328 ($72 off)&lt;/a&gt;, which matches one of the lowest prices we’ve seen on the over-ears to date. You can also pick up the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/21356313/sony-1000xm4-noise-canceling-headphones-review-price-specs-features"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;last-gen WH-1000XM4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; — which offer an identical set of features, great sound, and a foldable design — &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Sony-WH-1000XM4-Canceling-Headphones-phone-call/dp/B0863TXGM3/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;for $248 ($100 off)&lt;/a&gt;, along with the step-down &lt;strong&gt;WH-CH720N&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Sony-WH-CH720N-Canceling-Headphones-Microphone/dp/B0BS74M665?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$128 ($22 off)&lt;/a&gt;. Last but not least are the &lt;strong&gt;LinkBuds S&lt;/strong&gt;, a pair of wireless earbuds that offer supreme comfort, strong voice call performance, and effective ANC &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Sony-LinkBuds-Wireless-Canceling-Headphones/dp/B09YL76VSR/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;for $148 ($52 off)&lt;/a&gt;. You can even snag the purple &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/26/23889814/sony-olivia-rodrigo-linkbuds-s-announced-guts-sour"&gt;Olivia Rodrigo edition&lt;/a&gt; of the latter &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Sony-LinkBuds-Wireless-Canceling-Headphones/dp/B0CHZ8J9LC/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;for an all-time low of $168&lt;/a&gt; ($32 off), which nets you two custom EQ modes that are optimized for each of Rodrigo’s albums: &lt;em&gt;Sour&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Guts&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="wF9eCe"&gt;Read our reviews of the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23067645/sony-wh-1000xm5-noise-canceling-headphones-review"&gt;Sony XM5&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23123317/sony-linkbuds-s-earbuds-headphones-review"&gt;original LinkBuds S&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div id="rdVDvs"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12170020"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="qjOtsH"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12277062"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="FCmJSK"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="actionbox" data-anthem-component-data='{"title":"Verge Deals on X","description":"Join more than 50,000 followers and keep up with the best daily tech deals with @vergedeals","label":"Follow us!","url":"http://bit.ly/2JzR5Ud"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;h2 id="3ySi37"&gt;Other deals and discounts of note&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="96hJhc"&gt;One of the coolest things about &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23765921/google-pixel-tablet-review"&gt;Google’s Pixel Tablet&lt;/a&gt; is its color-matched speaker dock, which attaches via magnets and allows you to use your slate as an ad hoc smart display. The tablet comes with one by default; however, if you’d like a second &lt;strong&gt;Charging Speaker Dock&lt;/strong&gt; to place somewhere else in your home, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0C289CD17/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clOqAIewHjA"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt; are selling the standalone device starting at $77.99 ($51 off).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="lpabrg"&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Apple’s latest AirPods Pro &lt;/strong&gt;— aka the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/21309820/best-wireless-earbuds"&gt;best pair of earbuds for iPhone owners&lt;/a&gt; or anyone locked into the Apple ecosystem — have returned to their all-time low of around $189 ($60 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Apple-Generation-Cancelling-Transparency-Personalized/dp/B0CHWRXH8B/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FAirPods-Pro-2nd-generation-with-MagSafe-Case-USB-C%2F5020133971%2F&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clOqFPs8sJz"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;. The newest model touts the same great sound quality and ANC as the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23365910/apple-airpods-pro-second-generation-review"&gt;second-gen model&lt;/a&gt; from 2022, except the latest iteration also features dust resistance and ships with a USB-C charging case instead of the Lightning-only model that came with Apple’s previous earbuds. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23878402/apple-airpods-pro-usb-c-adaptive-audio-conversation-awareness-test-review"&gt;Read our hands-on impressions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="78y805"&gt;2023 was a colossal year for gaming, with blockbuster titles such as &lt;em&gt;Baldur’s Gate 3, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23852390/starfield-review-xbox-pc"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Starfield&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23718926/zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-review-nintendo-switch"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tears of the Kingdom&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; leading the public discourse. If you didn’t have a chance to tackle the excellent &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lies of P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, however, the PC version is on sale via &lt;a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/links/8532386/type/dlg/sid/verge/https://www.humblebundle.com/store/lies-of-p" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Humble&lt;/a&gt; for $44.99 ($15 off). The action RPG is essentially a bloody gothic reimagining of &lt;em&gt;Pinocchio &lt;/em&gt;with a punishing learning curve, the kind best suited for fans of &lt;em&gt;Dark Souls&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Elden Ring&lt;/em&gt;, and other difficult games that leave you more and more deflated with every session (sigh).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="AA8Jci"&gt;Just in time for spring, Rad Power Bikes has &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.radpowerbikes.com%2Fcollections%2Fclassic-bikes&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F12%2F24097671%2Fgrid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;launched a new sales event&lt;/a&gt;, which takes $200 off select e-bikes through March 13th. It’s primarily focused on the company’s more classic models, including the &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.radpowerbikes.com%2Fcollections%2Fclassic-bikes%2Fproducts%2Fradrunner-electric-utility-bike%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F12%2F24097671%2Fgrid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RadRunner 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ($1,199) and &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.radpowerbikes.com%2Fcollections%2Fclassic-bikes%2Fproducts%2Fradrunner-3-plus-electric-utility-bike%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F12%2F24097671%2Fgrid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RadRunner 3 Plus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ($1,899), the latter of which is a short-tail cargo bike with an ergonomic design &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/1/23620081/radrunner-3-plus-rad-power-bikes-ebike-pet-trailer-specs-price"&gt;you can easily kit out&lt;/a&gt; with a rear passenger seat, a hard-shell center console, lockable panniers, and — of course — a &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.radpowerbikes.com%2Fcollections%2Fstorage-transport%2Fproducts%2Frad-trailer%3F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F12%2F24097671%2Fgrid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;trailer for your dog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="RzCKyR"&gt;We don’t often go out of our way to point out deals on 4K Blu-ray discs, but seeing how we just wrapped a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/entertainment/24054458/physical-media-preservation-discs-cartridges-digital"&gt;special package on physical media&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oppenheimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/10/24094772/oscars-2024-winners-list-oppenheimer-poor-things"&gt;dominated this year’s Academy Awards&lt;/a&gt;, we figured it’s worth pointing out that &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23800129/oppenheimer-movie-review-christopher-nolan"&gt;Christopher Nolan’s award-winning biopic&lt;/a&gt; on the father of the atomic bomb has dropped to an all-time low of $19.99 ($8 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Oppenheimer-Ultra-Blu-ray-Digital-UHD/dp/B0CL7JD41F?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FOppenheimer-4K-Ultra-HD-Blu-ray-Bonus-Blu-ray-Digital-Copy%2F5020183552%2F&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Walmart&lt;/a&gt;. (Shout out to our friends over at &lt;em&gt;Polygon&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.polygon.com/deals/2024/3/11/24097143/oppenheimer-4k-bluray-best-picture-oscars-deal-discount"&gt;for the flag&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;aside id="HhCtLh"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="newsletter" data-anthem-component-data='{"slug":"deals"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24097671/grid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24097671/grid-studio-framed-tech-sony-wh-1000xm5-headphones-oppenheimer-blu-ray-deal-sale</id>
    <author>
      <name>Brandon Widder</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-12T12:03:41-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-12T12:03:41-04:00</updated>
    <title>How to use Low Power Mode on the Apple Watch</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Apple Watch Ultra on top of a colorful illustration of different fitness trackers" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ZYBAaV2ZTB1YvEqYVN5f0kO9YxA=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/71494044/Smart_watch_master.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Low Power Mode was introduced in watchOS 9 with the Apple Watch Ultra in mind.&lt;/em&gt; | Illustration by Samar Haddad / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="eB7olN"&gt;The Apple Watch has never been known for having long battery life. Case in point: Apple never budged from the 18-hour battery life estimate until it launched the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23363948/apple-watch-ultra-review-rugged-smartwatch-gps"&gt;Apple Watch Ultra&lt;/a&gt;. In 2022, the company introduced a new Low Power Mode when it launched the Ultra, and now, it has extended the time between charges for Apple Watches using watchOS 9 and later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="B6HMZL"&gt;Previously, the Apple Watch had a Power Reserve mode, which shut off any functions aside from your ability to tell time and turned your smartwatch into a normal watch until you could get it to a charger. This mode is different — it’s more like the iPhone’s Low Power Mode. When enabled, you’ll still be able to use your Apple Watch, but certain power-hungry features will be turned off or limited to conserve the battery. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="60o9rK"&gt;What Low Power Mode does&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="iyip3N"&gt;On the Apple Watch, Low Power Mode disables the always-on display and limits sensor readings like background heart rate and blood oxygen monitoring. (You should be aware that it also disables irregular heart rhythm notifications as well as high and low heart rate notifications.) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Uj0Mtt"&gt;Low Power Mode also curtails LTE and Wi-Fi connectivity. While you’ll still be able to send messages or make calls from your watch, it’ll only fetch notifications about once an hour. As a result, you might miss timely texts and emergency alerts. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="a0xTr1"&gt;However, if you’re in the middle of a workout, don’t worry — heart rate and GPS will be unaffected. Another option that reduces heart rate and GPS sampling is also in the works but is currently unavailable.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Low Power Mode screen on the Apple Watch Ultra" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/U5cXZb6UU7reaayAdTuYcAfss-o=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24037425/226274_APPLE_WATCH_ULTRA_PHO_akrales_0595.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Low Power Mode allows you to still use the Apple Watch while disabling power-hungry features.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="ZEhUmp"&gt;This mode is a great option if you’ve got an aging Apple Watch but aren’t looking to upgrade (since battery life is often why people buy new watches). Your mileage may vary, however. Battery life depends heavily on individual usage, and your watch’s battery health is also a factor. You can only squeeze so much out of Low Power Mode if your battery has significantly degraded over the years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="w0HBQl"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"watchOS 10 preview: widgets all the way down ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23786155/watchos-10-preview-apple-watch"},{"title":"How to use the Apple Watch Ultra’s Action button","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23365635/apple-watch-ultra-action-button-how-to"},{"title":"How to use the Apple Watch Ultra’s siren","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23387063/apple-watch-ultra-siren-how-to"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="O8DVT7"&gt;As with the iPhone version, you’ll be automatically prompted to turn on Low Power Mode once your battery power hits 10 percent. But some people, especially those with Ultras, might want to be more intentional about how they use the feature — for example, if they’re participating in an Ironman and need at least 12 hours or so of GPS and activity tracking. On the Ultra and Ultra 2, Apple says Low Power Mode can stretch battery life up to 60 hours. (Though, based on our testing, you may get well beyond that.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="zoFKGU"&gt;Enabling Low Power Mode&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="q1hBHU"&gt;First things first — again, to use Low Power Mode, you’ll need to have watchOS 9 or later. (Currently, we’re on watchOS 10, but it’ll still work on watchOS 9 if you don’t like how the latest version &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23786155/watchos-10-preview-apple-watch"&gt;updated the Apple Watch interface&lt;/a&gt;.) That also means you’ll need at least a Series 4. If you have an older watch and you think this feature is worthwhile, you may want &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23037217/apple-watch-series-8-ultra-second-gen-se-best-smartwatch-how-to"&gt;to consider upgrading&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Jkms5J"&gt;In any case, assuming your Apple Watch is equipped with compatible software, you can enable the feature in two ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="XsTqcx"&gt;Using Control Center&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="dFkYdD"&gt;The quickest way is through your watch’s &lt;strong&gt;Control Center&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="iYcDh2"&gt;If you’re still using watchOS 9, swipe up to access it. In watchOS 10, you’ll need to press the side button. Then, find the battery percentage tile and tap it. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="211Ubl"&gt;You should see a readout of how much battery you have left. Tap the &lt;strong&gt;Low Power Mode toggle&lt;/strong&gt; to turn it on. You’ll then see an explainer about which features are turned off in this mode, which will pop up each time you toggle it on.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="XCjoev"&gt;From there, you can tap &lt;strong&gt;Turn On&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;Turn On For...&lt;/strong&gt; The former enables the mode for an indefinite period. The latter will give you the option to temporarily turn it on for one, two, or three days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Battery history screen on the Series 8." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/n8EA0PvcgjXgmWiAbFPG-nYrL-M=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24023348/226266_APPLE_WATCH_8_SE_PHO_akrales_0162.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Enabling the mode via the Battery menu gives you extra context about your charging history.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="Low power mode screen on the Apple Watch Series 8" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/090_MKZ1e7m2CHlhP0FxrYhWvs0=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24023347/226266_APPLE_WATCH_8_SE_PHO_akrales_0153.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can also view battery health.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h3 id="hFfAgt"&gt;Using Settings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="5rmenM"&gt;You can also turn on Low Power Mode by going to &lt;strong&gt;Settings &amp;gt; Battery &amp;gt; Low Power Mode&lt;/strong&gt;. The benefit of doing it this way is that you get extra context about your battery life. Not only can you see how your battery’s been draining since your last charge but you can also see what times you may have previously enabled Low Power Mode. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2cQYMp"&gt;And you can tap &lt;strong&gt;Battery Health&lt;/strong&gt; from this menu to check how much the battery has degraded and enable optimized battery charging settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="VilTSG"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update, March 12th, 2024, 12:03PM ET: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article was originally published on October 14th, 2022, and has been updated to include information about watchOS 10 and how to access the control panel.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/23403065/apple-watch-low-power-battery-how-to"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/23403065/apple-watch-low-power-battery-how-to</id>
    <author>
      <name>Victoria Song</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-12T08:44:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-12T08:44:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Apple to allow iOS app downloads direct from websites in the EU</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Illustration of the App Store logo on a dark black and blue background." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/zqfluYVLgOw3NRrcPM9axGc0ThE=/0x0:3000x2000/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73200567/acastro_STK045_02.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration by Alex Castro / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="uiYpye"&gt;Apple is planning to make further changes in EU countries to allow some developers to distribute their iOS apps directly from a website. The new web distribution feature will be available with a software update “later this spring,” &lt;a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/"&gt;according to Apple&lt;/a&gt;, providing developers with a key new way to distribute iOS apps in EU markets without the need for a separate app store — as long as they’re willing to adhere to Apple’s strict rules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TWlGmN"&gt;While Apple is opening up iOS to more third-party apps here, these are still some key security protections around how apps are distributed via websites — namely, you’ll still have to work within the strict Apple app development ecosystem. “Apps offered through Web Distribution must meet Notarization requirements to protect platform integrity, like all iOS apps, and can only be installed from a website domain that the developer has registered in App Store Connect,” &lt;a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/web-distribution-eu/"&gt;explains Apple&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="nKGktf"&gt;It’s also not going to be a simple process to install these apps on an iPhone in the EU. “To install apps from a developer’s website, users will first need to approve the developer to install apps in Settings on their iPhone,” says Apple. “When installing an app, a system sheet will display information that developers have submitted to Apple for review, like the app name, developer name, app description, screenshots, and system age rating.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="di9LXI"&gt;So this isn’t going to be an open and free way for developers to distribute apps over the web to iOS devices in EU markets. “Apple will authorize developers after meeting specific criteria and committing to ongoing requirements that help protect users,” says Apple. Developers will need to be part of Apple’s Developer Program and be registered in the EU. They’ll also need to agree to a number of key undertakings, as outlined by Apple:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="jMXWtI"&gt;Be enrolled in the Apple Developer Program as an organization incorporated, domiciled, and or registered in the EU (or have a subsidiary legal entity incorporated, domiciled, and or registered in the EU that’s listed in App Store Connect). The location associated with your legal entity is listed in your Apple Developer account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="7BFnkj"&gt;Be a member of good standing in the Apple Developer Program for two continuous years or more, and have an app that had more than one million first annual installs on iOS in the EU in the prior calendar year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="xUE18O"&gt;Only offer apps from your developer account.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Av4sja"&gt;Be responsive to communications from Apple regarding your apps distributed through Web Distribution, particularly regarding any fraudulent, malicious, or illegal behavior, or anything else that Apple believes impacts the safety, security, or privacy of users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="nzlLBe"&gt;Publish transparent data collection policies and offer users control over how their data is collected and used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="mongkK"&gt;Follow applicable laws of the jurisdictions where you operate (for example, the Digital Services Act, the General Data Protection Regulation, and consumer protection laws).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="aiL2kL"&gt;Be responsible for handling governmental and other requests to take down listings of apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="jCYxV4"&gt;That’s a lot of hoops for developers to jump through, and it appears that Apple is limiting this to big developers only thanks to the 1 million installs requirement. Having a good standing developer account for two years may also rule Epic Games out of this particular distribution method. Epic Games is still hoping to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/16/24074873/epic-apple-ios-developer-account-eu-games-store-fortnite"&gt;launch its iOS game store&lt;/a&gt; in the European Union soon, though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1dl3mH"&gt;Apple currently allows developers to distribute their apps on third-party marketplaces in EU countries, but if those apps reach more than 1 million annual installs per year, they’ll need to pay that 50 euro cent fee for every additional installation and update. That same &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/25/24050200/apple-third-party-app-stores-allowed-iphone-ios-europe-digital-markets-act"&gt;Core Technology Fee&lt;/a&gt; process is part of web distribution of iOS apps, too. Only nonprofit organizations, select educational institutions, and government entities in the EU are exempt from this Core Technology Fee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Rpo4sp"&gt;Still, the ability for developers to bring their apps directly to iPhone users in the EU without having to go through the App Store or another third-party store will be useful for some willing to put up with the tight restrictions. There’s some obvious friction for end users, but with some third-party stores requiring fees, this allows iOS developers to avoid stores altogether if they’re willing to host their apps directly and abide by Apple’s rules and policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="MhEqAu"&gt;Apple is also changing its strict rules around how developers link to an external webpage to complete purchases for digital goods. Developers can now “choose how to design promotions, discounts, and other deals,” according to Apple. That means Apple’s own design templates are optional, instead of being forced on developers.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098334/apple-ios-web-distribution-eu-app-store-changes"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098334/apple-ios-web-distribution-eu-app-store-changes</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
