<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Smart Home Reviews</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-14T09:00:00-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/smart-home-review/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/smart-home-review" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T09:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T09:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Mini but mighty: Blink’s tiny, inexpensive camera can now go outdoors</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;The new Blink Mini 2 wired security camera is a worthwhile upgrade to the Blink Mini, adding weather resistance, a wider field of view, and person detection for around $40.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="YcKzhV"&gt;Security cameras are a personal preference; understandably, many people don’t like the idea of potentially being watched in their homes. But these gadgets do offer useful features such as checking in on pets, monitoring your house when you’re away, or catching someone prowling in your backyard after dark. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wx22U0"&gt;The new &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0BWWZXWPL?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Blink Mini 2 ($39.99)&lt;/a&gt; is a solid inexpensive wired security camera that can be used indoors or outdoors to handle all of these scenarios. While there are a couple of wired cameras at this price point with more features, Blink’s latest offering, which just launched this week, ticks a lot of boxes. It’s especially good if you have an &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23751608/amazon-alexa-smart-home-controller-how-to"&gt;Amazon Alexa smart home&lt;/a&gt; or are already invested in Blink’s affordable battery-powered camera lineup. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="JXv2H4"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12278537"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="o5kAOC"&gt;Blink made its name with its inexpensive battery-powered cameras, which can last up to two years on two AAs. The company now offers three mains-powered models: the Blink Mini (1 and 2); the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22811985/best-smart-floodlight-security-camera#:~:text=With%201080p%20video,horizontally%20or%20vertically."&gt;Blink Wired Floodlight Camera&lt;/a&gt;; and the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/9/28/22698612/amazon-blink-video-doorbell-outdoor-camera-floodlight-solar-panel"&gt;Blink Video Doorbell&lt;/a&gt; (which can be wired or battery-powered). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uW4ov0"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/idUSKBN1FW0BJ/"&gt;Blink’s custom-built chip&lt;/a&gt; sets it apart from many other manufacturers. The company has developed super energy-efficient silicon, and a recent upgrade added on-device computer vision (CV). This enables person detection, which is found on the company’s newer cameras: the Floodlight; the Mini 2; and the new &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/24/23843590/blink-outdoor-4-security-camera-wireless-person-detection"&gt;Blink Outdoor 4&lt;/a&gt; ($120) battery-powered camera. (Person detection requires a Blink subscription.) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/k2h7hfvs414NlmjWfPlnPTMLcIY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25335553/8A0A1040.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;em&gt;The Blink Mini 2 can sit on a flat surface with or without its stand, which can be mounted to a wall or ceiling. However, the Mini 2 doesn’t work with the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="ql-link" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09N6YCT3Y?tag=theverge02-20" target="_blank" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blink Mini Pan Tilt mount&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="VHlqgo"&gt;The Mini 2 is a follow-up to the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/4/28/21231112/blink-mini-smart-home-camera-security-cam-review"&gt;Blink Mini&lt;/a&gt;, which took over from &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/5/30/23147362/amazon-cloud-cam-shutting-down-free-blink-mini-echo-replacement"&gt;Amazon’s indoor Cloud Cam in 2022&lt;/a&gt; after the retail giant &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/circuitbreaker/2017/12/22/16810516/amazon-blink-acquisition-smart-camera-doorbell-company"&gt;bought Blink in 2017&lt;/a&gt;, and it brings more to the table. Upgrades include indoor / outdoor compatibility, a new spotlight, on-device person detection, and USB-C power. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4TjbuK"&gt;There’s a wider field of view over the original Mini (143 degrees versus 110), enhanced image quality, better low-light performance, and a sleeker design. Plus, there’s still the option of local storage by adding a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B084RQ6MHJ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$50 Blink Sync Module 2&lt;/a&gt; and a USB stick (the module is not required to use the camera, only if you want local storage).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="BfU9Vr"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="imageslider:12278830"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="83hNzr"&gt;A teeny, tiny camera, the Mini 2 can fit pretty much anywhere. I tested it out in my chicken coop at the end of my garden, on my back patio, and in my office and kitchen, and it delivered clear, crisp video in all locations during the day. Infrared night vision was fair, but the spotlight-enabled color night vision was very grainy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="LGtAft"&gt;The Mini’s motion and people notifications are super speedy, but there are no rich notifications, which is a shame. Blink says this is due to its &lt;a href="https://support.blinkforhome.com/en_US/motion-detection/early-notification"&gt;Early Notification feature&lt;/a&gt;, designed to alert you as quickly as possible so you can drop in on a live view while the action is still happening. Personally, I prefer rich notifications with a snapshot of the action. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dxLStK"&gt;Two-way audio is still slightly staticky, an issue with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/9/28/22698612/amazon-blink-video-doorbell-outdoor-camera-floodlight-solar-panel"&gt;all Blink cameras I’ve tested&lt;/a&gt;. But it’s much improved over the original Mini. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="AAs79F"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12278543"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="kpWUt5"&gt;Blink has a great mounting system, and the ball and socket base on the Mini 2 makes it simple to adjust the camera’s angle and position even after you’ve screwed its base to a wall or ceiling. I could also just pop it on a flat surface without the base, which meant I could fit it everywhere I wanted to. It’s the smallest camera I’ve tested by far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="LjNU1L"&gt;The Mini 2 is also one of the least expensive security cameras you can buy, both out of the box and for cloud storage (just $3 a month — &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/8/24066592/ring-video-doorbell-security-camera-subscription-price-increase"&gt;Ring is now $5 a month&lt;/a&gt;, and Arlo and Google Nest start at $8). The addition of weather resistance (IP65 rated) makes it infinitely more useful, but you will need to pay extra for the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CBL57VRT?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Blink Weather Resistant Power Adapter&lt;/a&gt;, which is a sizable 13 feet long. It’s sold separately or in a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CRZC2R94?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;bundle with the camera for $49.98&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/T8r0OS3jDm8T_HXvYbbxUE__itY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25335559/8A0A1022.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Blink Mini 2 mounted using its side mounting option and outdoor cable in the chicken coop.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="YG8UHx"&gt;The Blink Mini 2 works with the Blink app with features such as customizable privacy and activity zones and two-way talk. The app is fairly basic but has plenty of customization options and schedules that let you arm and disarm your cameras (something you have to pay for with Ring). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WxzMZE"&gt;The camera’s motion sensitivity is good — almost too good. Without enabling person detection, I got alerts when the lights on one of my smart light strips changed color in my office. Adjusting the sensitivity helped a bit, but you need person detection if you don’t want to be inundated with notifications. Helpfully, you can snooze motion alerts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="BKOGk3"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12278545"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="PlQWlZ"&gt;If, like a lot of people, you don’t want to cough up $3 a month, you can still get motion alerts to let you know if something’s going on at home. But there’s no person detection without paying. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="E3hn85"&gt;You can also record video locally with a Sync Module 2 to avoid those cloud storage fees, but that’s an extra $50, and you won’t get person detection without a subscription and are limited to how long you can watch a live view; with a subscription, it’s up to 90 minutes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NJVlYj"&gt;The camera works with Amazon’s Echo smart displays to view livestreams, and I can pull up a view on my Echo Hub in a few seconds. It can also be set to announce motion or person detection on Echo speakers, but there’s no support for other smart home platforms. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="QK4n7P"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="imageslider:12278845"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="8Exnlx"&gt;The Mini’s closest competitors are models from Wyze and TP-Link, which both have indoor / outdoor cameras with smart alerts and local storage with an onboard microSD card for under $40: &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wyze.com%2Fproducts%2Fwyze-cam&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F24100149%2Fblink-mini-2-review" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Wyze with its $36 Wyze Cam v3&lt;/a&gt; and TP-Link with the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/1/23941020/tp-link-tapo-c120-indoor-outdoor-security-camera-price-release-date"&gt;Tapo’s $40 C120 indoor / outdoor wired camera&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wGYq3A"&gt;Considering &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/16/24075369/wyze-security-camera-stranger-feeds-glitch"&gt;Wyze’s recent security issues&lt;/a&gt;, the Tapo is the better option of the two. It also has better features than the Mini 2 — 2K video, dual spotlights, and free smart alerts for people, pets, and vehicles. Plus, there’s sound detection for dogs barking, babies crying, and cats meowing, making it potentially more useful than the Blink, especially as an indoor camera. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="361UmY"&gt;Personally, I’m not a big fan of indoor cameras, and as an outdoor wired option, the Blink worked better for me than the Tapo, streaming video from my chicken coop at the bottom of the garden more reliably. The Mini is also the smaller of the two cameras, comes in black or white, and has a longer outdoor power cable with a weatherproof plug (although it costs extra). But the Tapo does work with Google Home and Samsung SmartThings, which makes it a better choice if you use those platforms. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/vgTWf6HZ0YM6uUdWyykq8rSfUVo=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25335580/8A0A0904.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The sizable outdoor power cable for the Blink Mini 2 is very sturdy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mPMLXE"&gt;Overall, the Blink Mini 2 is an excellent upgrade to a popular inexpensive security camera. It’s very easy to set up and use — and its mounting system is one of the simplest and most flexible I’ve used. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="CPqIc0"&gt;Using this outdoors and cutting down on notification noise with person detection, all while staying under $50, are great improvements over the Mini 1. The video (both daytime and nighttime) and audio quality are noticeably better than the Mini 1. But the zoom is still limited, and I’d like to see more smart alerts for things like animals and vehicles; sound detection would be excellent, too. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5IabEz"&gt;My two biggest issues are that Blink’s app is not intuitive and it has limited smart home integrations. While the app has plenty of customization options, it feels clunky and outdated, especially compared to the excellent app of its sister company, Ring. I would love to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22704290/amazon-blink-ring-camera-doorbell-brands-smart-home-why"&gt;be able to use Blink cameras in the Ring app&lt;/a&gt;. The Blink Mini 2 is also locked in Amazon’s ecosystem, with no support for Google Home or Samsung SmartThings (although Blink &lt;a href="https://support.blinkforhome.com/en_US/ifttt/how-to-integrate-blink-with-ifttt-services"&gt;does support IFTTT&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="Vk08is"&gt;But if you use Alexa and / or other Blink cameras or are just looking for a simple security camera for a specific purpose and don’t need super high resolution, it’s a good, versatile, and affordable option.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="cZGHhE"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12278867"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="miLE4j"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photos and screenshots by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24100149/blink-mini-2-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24100149/blink-mini-2-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jennifer Pattison Tuohy</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-21T09:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-21T09:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>The Echo Hub is Alexa’s missing piece</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;Amazon’s new control panel makes using an Alexa-powered smart home as easy as flipping a light switch (only better, trust me).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="Kt21Du"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0BCR7M9KX?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon’s Echo Hub ($179.99)&lt;/a&gt; is the best solution yet for an affordable, intuitive way to control your smart home. I’ve lived with home automation for over a decade and one of my biggest challenges has been finding a simple method for managing connected devices in my home that anyone can use. Phone and voice control have their place, but with a tech-averse spouse, younger kids, and elderly grandparents who are often confounded by my living room lights, I’ve longed for an &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24043060/smart-home-interface-map-view-samsung-lg-amazon-ces-2024"&gt;easy-to-use, all-in-one control panel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="MklyWf"&gt;&lt;q&gt;With the Echo Hub, the smart home is no longer locked inside one person’s phone&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="0Bcybg"&gt;Enter the Echo Hub. It might look like an &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23945192/amazon-echo-show-8-alexa-smart-display-review"&gt;Echo Show 8’s&lt;/a&gt; skinny sibling, but the Hub is something the Show is not: a dedicated smart home controller. A smart home hub and touchscreen control panel in one, this is the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/20/23880766/amazon-alexa-echo-hub-smart-displays-price-matter"&gt;first device in a new category from Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, one that until now was only found in professionally installed smart home systems from the likes of Crestron, Savant, and Control4.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hE9IUp"&gt;The Echo Hub can play music, stream videos, and answer Alexa queries just like a Show, but its primary purpose is its smart home dashboard. This provides an easy way to dim all the lights in my living room with a swipe, view the video doorbell with the press of a button, or adjust the thermostat with a couple of taps. With the Echo Hub, the smart home is no longer locked inside one person’s phone. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="voIDJA"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12257922"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="QjQpIR"&gt;The Echo Hub is an eight-inch Alexa-powered touchscreen display that can be mounted on a wall or popped on a counter for easy, communal access to connected devices. Like the similarly designed &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22839220/amazon-echo-show-15-review-wall-mounted-alexa-tablet-kitchen-tv"&gt;Echo Show 15&lt;/a&gt;, the Echo Hub needs to be plugged in when wall-mounted. Unlike the Show 15, it uses a USB-C power adaptor and can be powered over Ethernet. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="JqomqR"&gt;With Zigbee, Thread, Bluetooth LE, and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/28/23659191/amazon-sidewalk-network-coverage"&gt;Amazon Sidewalk radios&lt;/a&gt; on board, the Hub is also a smart home hub, capable of being a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/7/19/23269460/thread-1-3-0-matter-border-routers-homepod-mini-echo-nest"&gt;Thread border router&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23568091/matter-compatible-devices-accessories-apple-amazon-google-samsung"&gt;Matter Controller&lt;/a&gt;. (You’ll still need a separate &lt;a href="https://www.z-wave.com/shop-z-wave-smart-home-products/category/smart-hubs"&gt;Z-Wave hub compatible with Alexa&lt;/a&gt; to use Z-Wave devices).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZFeRiO"&gt;While the newest &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23945192/amazon-echo-show-8-alexa-smart-display-review"&gt;Echo Show 8&lt;/a&gt; has these radios, too, it doesn’t have the Hub’s UI — instead, control for smart home devices is limited to a favorites button or several swipes and taps. The Hub also doesn’t have a camera or any of the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23944889/set-up-echo-show-without-amazon-ads-how-to"&gt;bloatware found on all Echo Show devices&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="1ufcIl"&gt;&lt;q&gt;If you don’t use Alexa to manage your smart home, you won’t want this device&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ZM2x9e"&gt;Yes, you read that right. So far, Amazon isn’t using the Hub as a tiny billboard in your home. There’s no rotating homescreen with ads for Amazon services and prompts for things you “might like to try.” Instead, there’s just a simple clock face with a customizable photo background. Hallelujah.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="w6toPY"&gt;Before we get too excited, let me be clear. This isn’t the same as having an iPad on your wall (if an iPad had a great, intuitive smart home UI). Unlike an iPad or those Crestron and Control4 &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/3/23385183/smart-home-controller-ava-remote-cedia-2022"&gt;smart home controllers&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/1/4/22865808/samsung-smartthings-smart-home-hub-dashboard-ces2022"&gt;this Home Hub&lt;/a&gt; Samsung showed off a couple years ago, the Hub is not a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23720333/google-pixel-tablet-smart-home-display-io"&gt;tablet&lt;/a&gt;. It doesn’t have the compute power or capabilities of a tablet, and at times, it suffers because of that. But it also only costs $180, not somewhere between $400 and $2,000, which is around what you’d pay for those other devices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rI3rux"&gt;The Hub is a well thought out, intuitive smart home control panel that, thanks to local radios, makes controlling devices in your home as fast as flipping a light switch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/2k7KJtbOfUO-bZzW3v9brmTKCo8=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25289931/247023_Echo_Hub_JTuohy_0016.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Echo Hub next to the Echo Show 8.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/27A7gbManyospqln69i2rb0RQh8=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25289932/247023_Echo_Hub_JTuohy_0017.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Echo Hub needs a separate stand to sit on a table whereas the Show is self propping.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="HZ2gLi"&gt;I’ve been testing the Hub for about a week and set it up in two locations in my home. The first was wall-mounted in a main entryway, and the second was on my desk in my home office, using &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0BCR7M9KX?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;a tabletop stand ($30)&lt;/a&gt;. In both locations, it proved useful and meant I didn’t need to rely on app or voice control nearly as often. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uGC4tD"&gt;In the hallway, it was helpful for arming the Ring security system (and meant I could retire the ugly keypad), turning lights on in the house, locking the door on the way to bed at night, and adjusting the thermostat. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="9wvYzN"&gt;&lt;q&gt;Compared to using my phone or Echo Show, the Echo Hub’s dashboard is frictionless&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="TSq4du"&gt;In my office, it replaced an Echo Show as a clock / photo frame and music player (it has basic speakers on board, but pairing it with an Echo 4th-gen speaker provided more room-filling sound). An Active Media shortcut makes it simple to pause music, and I could turn off the lights or the ceiling fan with one tap. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="oUEdnE"&gt;Compared to using my phone or Echo Show, the Echo Hub’s dashboard is frictionless — no waiting 10 seconds for a voice assistant to complete a command or fiddling with unlocking routines and multiple taps and swipes to get to the controls. With some creativity using &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23312859/amazon-alexa-echo-routine-smart-speaker-how-to'"&gt;Alexa Routines&lt;/a&gt;, the Hub could rival the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23700541/stream-deck-hacks-uses"&gt;Stream Deck&lt;/a&gt; many of my colleagues use to control the gadgets in their office.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WtjMZY"&gt;Getting the Hub set up was super simple. It’s the same process as with an Echo Show smart display, minus the Visual ID set-up (there’s no camera on the Hub). Once connected to my Alexa account, the Hub auto-populated the smart home dashboard with my devices organized as in the Alexa app: favorites, groups (rooms), and device types.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="9NA9bV"&gt;The dashboard is well laid out, with all my lights, fans, shades, locks, and cameras presented in customizable panels, widgets, and shortcuts. There wasn’t much of a learning curve, and my husband could navigate everything easily, too. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="cWmp9a"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12257947"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="6IorIx"&gt;The main panel shows large, interactive widgets for groups (rooms), cameras, and favorite devices (selected in the Alexa app). On startup, it automatically included a widget for my Living Room group (where the Hub was located) with all controllable devices in that room, along with weather, calendar, shopping, and to-do list widgets. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GHgXGa"&gt;The left sidebar panel contains shortcuts to routines for one press activation and all my other groups for quick navigation. For example, tapping the Dining Room group changes the widget on the main panel to the devices in that group, along with big all-on and all-off buttons and a toggle to dim and brighten all the lights or turn them all off or all on. This feature takes the dashboard from a screen of icons to a useful interface. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="MgL64I"&gt;At first, I tried to add more widgets to the home panel, but I realized it was easier to tap the shortcuts to groups than swipe the screen to see more widgets. I could also navigate to these by voice as I approached. “Alexa, switch to Kitchen panel,” saves an extra tap. (Although, as with all voice control, this takes a beat longer than tapping).  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="aZKJRM"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12257928"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="bHqVdC"&gt;Tapping widgets and buttons activated most devices nearly instantly, but I did find other touchscreen integrations laggy and a bit frustrating. In particular, swiping was slow, and customizing widgets or navigating between screens requires patience. As mentioned, this is not a tablet, and the onboard MediaTek MT 8169 A processor struggled to keep up with tablet-style taps and swipes. Also, while the widgets, shortcuts, and side panels are customizable, the devices are locked in alphabetical order inside the widgets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Oq3Y2h"&gt;Besides the widgets, there’s a bottom row of shortcuts for quick access to all devices in a particular category — lights, locks, climate (for thermostats), cameras, switches, as well as controls for any active media playing and the Ring Alarm security system. Like the widgets, the shortcuts have an all-on or all-off toggle, but there was no option to lock all doors, and that was a shame. Unlocking doors also requires a PIN code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TXrQPy"&gt;Still, the Echo Hub’s smart home dashboard is just so much better than any other touchscreen interface I’ve used for controlling my smart home. And it’s not just the UI, the proximity sensor really makes the Hub shine. This quickly switches the UI from the default clock / photo display to the smart home dashboard as I approach, allowing instant control of devices with one or two taps. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="OryzZk"&gt;The Hub is a great camera-viewing device. It showed a live view from a Ring doorbell within a few seconds of the doorbell being pressed, and I could see and talk to the visitor. The camera widget shows recent snapshots from connected Ring cameras, and multiview can show four live feeds simultaneously from any camera, handy for keeping an eye on my critters in the backyard. But this isn’t customizable and only shows the most recently active feeds. Also, while you can view live camera feeds from Show devices, you can’t drop in on a show with video, only audio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/I_E28jCjctscq0ZSaydMuoLpbCI=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25289930/247023_Echo_Hub_JTuohy_0015.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The cable down the wall look is not a good one — but the Hub has the option of power over ethernet to help with this.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="CMejP4"&gt;Yet despite the terrific UI and lack of bloatware, the Echo Hub is still an Alexa gadget. If you don’t like Amazon or use Amazon’s assistant and its app to manage your smart home, you won’t want this device. While Amazon Alexa is one of the more open smart platforms (the company claims the Hub is compatible with thousands of devices) and it supports Matter, the Hub still works best with Amazon products. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AZZO9b"&gt;The camera widget shows live snapshots from Ring cameras (if you pay for a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/8/24066592/ring-video-doorbell-security-camera-subscription-price-increase"&gt;Ring subscription&lt;/a&gt;), but any other camera brand just shows an icon. The Security shortcut only works to arm and disarm the system if you have a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22798830/ring-alarm-pro-review-smart-home-security-alexa"&gt;Ring Alarm&lt;/a&gt;, and the Hub can listen for smoke or CO alarms and send you an alert, but only if you pay for &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/20/23882337/amazon-alexa-emergency-assist-echo"&gt;Alexa Emergency Assist &lt;/a&gt;(a feature that used to be free on all Echo speakers.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2uR8MI"&gt;I was stymied by a few of the Hub’s limitations. While it replaces some of what you have to go to the Alexa app for, it’s sadly not a replacement for the app itself. It’s an extension of the app, not a self-contained smart home controller. You still need the app to set up and manage devices, groups, and routines. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="sooIoF"&gt;&lt;q&gt;Some touchscreen integrations were laggy and frustrating&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="6xnJJ2"&gt;I frequently wanted to use the Hub to move a device to a different room, tap into Settings to delete a device, or set a PIN code for a lock, but for all this, I had to go back to the app. While, in general, using an app isn't bad, using the Alexa app, which is slow, buggy, and needlessly fiddly, is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AiWktl"&gt;It’s also a shame the built-in PIR and ambient light sensor (that switches to the smart home dashboard as you approach and enables the screen’s adaptive brightness) can’t be used as a motion or light sensor to trigger a routine. I installed the Hub where I’d had a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23841213/brilliant-plug-in-smart-home-control-panel-price-review"&gt;Brilliant Smart Home Control Panel&lt;/a&gt;. That has a built-in motion sensor I used to turn on the hallway lights — I couldn’t replicate that function with the Hub. Amazon says this could be a feature in a future update. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hQ4Z1j"&gt;I have a few other quibbles. The favorites widget is small; I’d like to see more than four devices there. Amazon says it can show up to eight, but a bug in the Alexa app meant I couldn’t test this. The bezel is too big and thick, and I’d like to be able to customize the order in which devices are shown in the widgets. Navigating back to the Home screen was tricky at times, and there was a bug in the lighting shortcut that meant the all-on / all-off toggle was gone for me. But these are minor issues found in an otherwise outstanding device.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="cHHhat"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12257936"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="8rPrJ6"&gt;The Echo Hub has been an indispensable addition to my smart home. A simple, relatively affordable, easy-to-set-up solution to a need I’ve had for over a decade of living in a smart home. While $180 isn’t a small amount, it’s competitive compared to other DIY options. I recently reviewed the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24064662/linxura-smart-controller-review"&gt;Linxura Smart Controller&lt;/a&gt;, which costs $100 and does about a quarter of what the Hub can. The $400 &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23841213/brilliant-plug-in-smart-home-control-panel-price-review"&gt;Brilliant Smart Home Control Panel&lt;/a&gt; I’ve tested has capabilities similar to the Echo Hub but can’t act as a smart home hub for connecting Zigbee, Thread, or Matter devices. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="97E8qf"&gt;Not everyone needs an Echo Hub; arguably, this is a niche device for Alexa super-users. For anyone who uses Alexa but doesn’t have a smart home, an &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23945192/amazon-echo-show-8-alexa-smart-display-review"&gt;Echo Show 8&lt;/a&gt;, with its superior speakers, camera for video calling, and lower price, will be the better choice. The Hub is also overkill if you have a smart home lite — say, three Hue bulbs and a smart lock. If you have a lot of Ring products, including a Ring Alarm and a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22954554/best-video-doorbell-camera#:~:text=and%20speedy%20response-,times,-for%20a%20battery"&gt;Ring video doorbell&lt;/a&gt;, it becomes more compelling. The Hub can replace a Ring Alarm keypad and act as a video intercom for the doorbell. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="kwtcBE"&gt;However, if you’re fully invested in an Alexa smart home with dozens of devices and routines, you will want an Echo Hub — and you’ll love it. Even if you use another smart home platform, this may find a spot in your setup as a control panel thanks to its interoperability with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/matter"&gt;Matter&lt;/a&gt;. With the Echo Hub, Amazon has found the missing piece to a big part of the smart home’s struggles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="R3xyF6"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12258384"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mzUrU3"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photos by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24078558/echo-hub-review-alexa-amazon-smart-control-panel"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24078558/echo-hub-review-alexa-amazon-smart-control-panel</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jennifer Pattison Tuohy</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-12T13:00:03-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-12T13:00:03-05:00</updated>
    <title>The best floodlight camera to buy right now</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of a variety of brands of security camera floodlights." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/RB2THX038S226wvWYSQpsoM7nP8=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/70239338/246989_Buying_Guide_Security_Floodlights_CVirginia_copy.13.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;An all-in-one security camera with motion-activated light and continuous power, an outdoor floodlight camera is a simple way to add safety and security to your home’s perimeter.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="xE3GTF"&gt;When something goes bump in the night in your backyard, you probably want to know about it. While regular security cameras with night vision can show you what’s out there, a floodlight camera can show you &lt;em&gt;and &lt;/em&gt;tell that rascal or raccoon to get off your lawn, scaring them away with some powerful lumens and possibly a blaring siren. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="WiHVPz"&gt;While there’s &lt;a href="https://www.darksky.org/light-pollution/lighting-crime-and-safety/"&gt;mixed research on whether outdoor lighting is a significant crime deterrent&lt;/a&gt; or just potentially annoying for your neighbors, there are plenty of benefits to lighting up your property from a safety and security perspective. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="T4WJyU"&gt;With smart floodlight cameras, you get the added value of better lighting plus a way to keep an eye on your home. Thanks to sensors, artificial intelligence, and machine learning, smart floodlight cameras can be set only to light up when there’s someone there instead of just when a gust of wind sends a plastic bag through your yard. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="A76GBl"&gt;A floodlight camera has a few benefits over a standard smart security camera. If you have existing hardwired lighting around your home, it’s an easy swap to add a camera &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; lighting in place of outdoor lights. This removes worries about recharging batteries, installing solar panels, or taking up an outdoor outlet. If you’re looking for advice on why you might want a floodlight camera or how to install it, I’ve got more details for you below, as well as tips on how to install a floodlight camera. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ow7uDR"&gt;Here, I’ve rounded up the best outdoor floodlight security cameras based on extensive testing over two years at a single-family home in South Carolina. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="9tpp0x"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:11953775"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="YmaxgJ"&gt;
&lt;script src="https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.sbnation.com/csk/uploads/verge-toc.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;script&gt;


//this line summons a table of contents. use as follows!


//initiateTOC takes the arguments "header", "subheader", "collapsible"


//for whatever header type ("h2", "h3" etc) you want to be the main header, type it in quotes in the function call. 


//if you don't want subheads, set to false in the function call (no quotes)


//collapsible is a true/false toggle


//see graham if you have any questions/issues


// note that all the header types are off by one: an h1 in the CMS is an h2 in the actual code. If you just want h2 and h3 to show up in the TOC you need to call them h3 and h4. 


window.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', (event) =&gt; {
	initiateTOC("h2", "h3", false, "The best floodlight cameras")
});


&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="https://s3.amazonaws.com/assets.sbnation.com/csk/uploads/verge-toc.css"&gt;


&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component verge-table-of-contents border-franklin border" id="toc-main"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr class="p-entry-hr" id="tVrS9H"&gt;
&lt;h2 id="nwyAvH"&gt;The best outdoor floodlight camera overall &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="c6kk3E"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10901138" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="eGspnu"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video quality:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 1080p HD, 8x digital zoom / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lumens: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;2,000 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart alerts: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;Person ($) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Field of view:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 140 degrees (270 motion) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Siren:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes (110 decibels) &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power options:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Hardwired or plug in / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wi-Fi:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 2.4GHz and 5GHz / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Cloud, local / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscription fee:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; $4.99 a month / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Alexa, SmartThings, Ring&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="AeWZm3"&gt;Ring’s top-of-the-line wired floodlight camera has superb video quality, excellent motion detection, and an impressive 2,000 lumens of adjustable light. Its wide horizontal and deep vertical field of view gave a better vantage over my backyard than most of the competition. It’s my favorite of all the cameras I tested, and it’s also the best floodlight camera that works with Amazon Alexa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mEd8Wk"&gt;While I didn’t find the &lt;a href="https://support.ring.com/hc/en-us/articles/360056772832-Bird-s-Eye-View-information"&gt;Bird’s Eye View&lt;/a&gt; feature that useful, the &lt;a href="https://support.ring.com/hc/en-us/articles/360057232771-Setting-up-and-Using-3D-Motion-Detection"&gt;radar-powered 3D motion detection&lt;/a&gt; was very good. Of all the cameras I tested, this was the most reliable at picking up motion anywhere in its range, even mounted on the eave of my second floor. A nice feature that no other camera I tested offers is offline alerts. It can tap into &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/28/23659191/amazon-sidewalk-network-coverage"&gt;Amazon’s Sidewalk network&lt;/a&gt; to send notifications even when your Wi-Fi is out. I couldn’t view a video feed from the notification when my internet was down, but I did know something had happened and could go back to view the event once connectivity was restored. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Slf2TM"&gt;The enhanced motion detection is the main reason to buy the Pro model over the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Ring-Floodlight-Cam-Wired-Plus/dp/B08F6DWKQP?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Floodlight Cam Wired Plus&lt;/a&gt;, which is $50 cheaper. The other key differences are no HDR imaging on the Plus or the option of 5GHz Wi-Fi. Neither of these makes much difference on a floodlight camera — due to its likely location being up high and far away from your Wi-Fi router — but better motion detection is worth a lot on a security camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="PTWVzb"&gt;Ring’s digital zoom is also excellent, and the bumped-up siren is the loudest I tested (at 110dB, 105 on the Plus). You can’t trigger the siren on motion, but there is the option to add a verbal warning telling prowlers they’re on camera — less offensive to the neighbors than a motion-triggered siren. I also like the option of a version that &lt;a href="https://ring.com/products/floodlight-cam-pro-plug-in"&gt;runs off a standard wall outlet&lt;/a&gt; if you don’t have a junction box available, but I recommend hardwiring if you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/twLaoGvquMRm97-vqRyWIl9pAC4=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24507225/IMG_6A2160B376D5_1.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Ring Floodlight Cam has an excellent field of view.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="MqpaPH"&gt;You’ll need to pay for a Ring Protect Plus plan for recorded video, starting at $4 a month, and increasingly a bargain as every other smart home company raises its subscription prices (I’m looking at you, Arlo and Nest). This also adds person detection (no other smart alerts) — without it, it’s live stream only. However, the Pro does work with local storage using a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22798830/ring-alarm-pro-review-smart-home-security-alexa"&gt;Ring Alarm Pro&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="j2qPdG"&gt;The camera works with Ring’s app and its extensive security system, but the only other smart home platform it’s compatible with is Amazon Alexa and Samsung SmartThings (which lets you view a live stream on your Samsung TV). Alexa integration is useful; you can view a live feed in the Alexa app and on Alexa-enabled smart displays and have Echo smart speakers announce when people and / or motion is detected. But you can’t control the Ring’s floodlights through Alexa, either with voice or in routines; you have to use the Ring app for all light controls. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="7wIYru"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The Ring Floodlight Cam works best with Amazon’s Alexa ecosystem&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="c7ew9A"&gt;In the Ring app, you can adjust the three motion zones for the lights — which is handy for preventing them from turning on when my neighbor walks in his yard. The lights can also be set on a schedule, adjusted in brightness, and linked with Ring devices so that if a Ring camera on one side of the house detects motion, it can turn on the floodlights on the other. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="lt01vh"&gt;If you add a Ring Alarm or Ring Alarm Pro to your setup and pay for the $20 monthly Ring Protect Pro plan, you also add the option of local storage, internet backup, and professional monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="JF0u1Z"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The best budget floodlight camera&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="ApKxvr"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12246221" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="OcjyQI"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video quality: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;1080p HD / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Lumens: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;2,600 /&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Smart alerts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Person, package, vehicle, animal ($) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Field of view:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 143 degrees / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Siren:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 105 decibels  / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power options:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Hardwired / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wi-Fi:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 2.4GHz / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cloud and local (with $35 Sync Module) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscription fee:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; $3 monthly or $30 a year / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Alexa&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="O2KiZL"&gt;The Blink Wired Floodlight Camera ($99.99) is a good budget option with on-device processing of people alerts, so nothing has to go to the cloud (although you have to subscribe for this feature). It offers local storage and 1080p video and works with Amazon Alexa for smart home control. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HBzoAC"&gt;It’s available in white or black and can fit under the eaves or be mounted on the side of a wall. The floodlight lights are easy to manually adjust and very bright (2,600 lumens). While you can adjust the brightness, the white isn’t tunable. You can set them to turn on automatically at dusk and off at dawn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EbUkgE"&gt;The video quality, day and night, is good for this price, but the motion detection is limited to about 20 feet. Also, if you don’t pay Blink’s monthly subscription ($3), you can only view a live stream for five minutes in the Blink app. Person detection is also locked behind the paywall even though it’s processed on the device. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/wWOg1GbMqw54OYCG0TU7_wCq5dM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25274323/IMG_0869.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Blink loses quality in the distance and has a short range of motion detection, but it’s clear close up and shows faces well during the day and at night.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="WihvHH"&gt;You can store recorded video locally, but you need a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Blink-Sync-Module-2/dp/B084RQ6MHJ?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$35 Sync Module&lt;/a&gt; and a USB stick. If you pay for cloud storage, you’re allowed up to 90 minutes of continuous livestreaming, with the option to record a live view. Person detection was largely accurate, although it often mistook my 80lb dog for a person (fair enough?). I like that you can set the camera to only record when it sees a person, which helps cut down on clip clutter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7GUsNM"&gt;Another issue is that the audio quality is very staticky (a problem with all Blink cameras I’ve tested), but the siren is clear and loud. Motion alerts came in instantly, but pulling up the live view could take a while. I liked that I could set an Echo speaker to announce when motion was detected and see a live view on an Echo Show smart display.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="yXknwT"&gt;Compared to my previous budget pick, the &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wyze.com%2Fproducts%2Fwyze-cam-floodlight-v1&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F22811985%2Fbest-smart-floodlight-security-camera" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Wyze Cam Floodlight V1&lt;/a&gt;, the Blink has a cleaner design and doesn’t force a five-minute cool-down period between recordings, which the Wyze does if you don’t pay for a subscription. The V1 has been replaced by the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/23/24047950/wyze-cam-floodlight-v2-price-features-release-date"&gt;Wyze Cam Floodlight V2&lt;/a&gt;, which I have yet to test. This adds 2K HD video, a wider field of view, and 2,800 lumens of light for around $10 less than the Blink. The original V1 is currently on sale for $54, a real bargain. But overall, I prefer the Blink. See &lt;em&gt;Other outdoor floodlight cameras I tested&lt;/em&gt; for more on Wyze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="TwlQdt"&gt;The best floodlight camera without subscription fees&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="ZXNlmX"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12153537" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="b0ZGhD"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video quality:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 4K (2K each camera), 10x digital zoom /  &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lumens: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;2,400 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart alerts: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;People, vehicles, animals / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Field of view:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 180 degrees / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Siren:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Yes / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power options:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; POE or plug-in / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wi-Fi:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 2.4GHz and 5GHz / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Local only / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscription fee:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; none / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Google Home, Home Assistant&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="DHhWWC"&gt;The Reolink Duo Floodlight camera lacks a few bells and whistles — there are no rich notifications, HDR imaging, tunable white light, or fancy features like zoom and track. That said, it records all video locally, and there’s no cloud connection at all. This means no subscription fees. It has on-device processing for alerts for people, vehicles, and animals, and its huge 180-degree field of view easily covered my entire half-acre backyard. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HFVWxw"&gt;This is thanks to its two lenses (hence “&lt;em&gt;duo&lt;/em&gt;”), each with 2K video quality (4608 x 1728 p). While there’s a weird wobbly effect to the image, possibly due to how it stitches together the two images, the overall quality is excellent, and the lights are bright and responsive to motion. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RtK38J"&gt;I tested the Wi-Fi version, but if you’re set up for it there is the option of power over ethernet.  The Wi-Fi version comes with a standard power brick and the option to connect it via ethernet for a more stable connection. This does means it can’t easily be wired in place of existing lighting, though, and you need an outlet nearby. It also only mounts horizontally to the side of a house, not vertically under the eaves. &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/A6j2I3EK44w8tfWPRUrrqBeG8jM=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25273036/IMG_0691.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Reolink has the widest field of view of a non-pan and tilt camera that I tested.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="ftO7sj"&gt;With a microSD card installed or a connection to a &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Freolink.com%2Fus%2Fproduct%2Frln8-410%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F22811985%2Fbest-smart-floodlight-security-camera" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Reolink NVR&lt;/a&gt;, the camera can &lt;a href="https://support.reolink.com/hc/en-us/articles/900000420623-How-to-Save-Continuous-Recordings-to-SD-Card-via-Reolink-Softwares/"&gt;record continuously&lt;/a&gt; and be set to do so on a schedule. Using the app, you can schedule times for specific motion detection, such as “only alert me to people at night.” It’s the only camera I tested with a timelapse feature that you can also schedule, and this was fun for capturing a sunset or catching my dog dashing around my yard. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="pmElTS"&gt;However, the app is complicated and fiddly to set up, the siren is very quiet, and there are limited smart home integrations, but it can connect to Google Home and Home Assistant and has a desktop app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="mQxJXY"&gt;The best wireless outdoor floodlight camera&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="dDBXLM"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10901099" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="SuKSW1"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video quality:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 2K, 12x zoom / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lumens: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;2,000 (3,000 when plugged in) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart alerts: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;Person, package, vehicle, pet ($) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Field of view:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 160 degrees (130 motion) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Siren: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yes (105 decibels) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power options:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Battery, solar panel, plug in / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wi-Fi:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 2.4GHz / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Cloud / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscription fee:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; $7.99 monthly / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Alexa, Google Home, Apple Home, Samsung SmartThings&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="zjER4Y"&gt;If you don’t have access to hardwiring or a nearby power outlet, or you want a floodlight camera that works with all the major smart home platforms, the Arlo Pro 3 Floodlight Cam is the best option. This camera works with Google Home, Samsung SmartThings, Apple Home, and Alexa. It has better video quality than the Ring, a 12x digital zoom, an option to auto-track and zoom, a motion-activated siren, and more smart alerts. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GcgpLA"&gt;But the Arlo is a battery-powered camera, and while this means you can mount it anywhere you need to, it lacks the best feature of hardwired floodlight cams: reliable, continuous power. Arlo has the option of continuous power, but you need a nearby outlet and an additional $50 power cord. It does not mount to a standard outdoor junction box and isn’t a great drop-in upgrade for an existing non-camera floodlight. I tested the Arlo for six months on battery power in a very busy location and had to charge it every two months. A $60 solar panel add-on would help, but then you’re paying over $300.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="kIXXGz"&gt;The camera’s software features are also expensive. You must subscribe to its Arlo Secure service ($7.99 monthly for a single camera or $13.99 for multiple) for zoom and track, rich notifications, and smart alerts for animals, vehicles, and packages. I couldn’t even snooze motion alerts without a subscription plan. There is the option of continuous 24/7 recording for an additional fee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/QImLLN3zc6Mib4JSDCzQiY6Q14c=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23055522/jtuohy_211129_4898_0017.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Arlo Pro 3 floodlight camera gives off a lot of light, despite its small size.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="AypfvS"&gt;The Arlo is the least obtrusive-looking floodlight camera I tested. I won’t go so far as to say it looks nice — but it’s not as large or as prominent-looking as the rest (with the exception of the Eve Outdoor Cam). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="fdY43I"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The Arlo can run on battery or off a nearby outlet but can’t be wired to a standard outdoor junction box&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="A5e6jW"&gt;Despite the camera’s smaller size, the light is very bright and more than enough to illuminate my entire back patio. It’s one of only two cameras I tested that has the option to pulse its light to scare off intruders, and you can set its 80dB siren to go off on motion. (Be careful with this feature if you don’t want your neighbors to come knocking.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="MM5pBn"&gt;One issue I ran into was water getting into the floodlight after a heavy rainstorm. I was able to dry it out, and it’s been working fine since then, but I would recommend installing this — and any floodlight camera — under an eave or some covering where possible to extend its life. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gbY6GZ"&gt;I also find the Arlo app to be finicky. It logs me out frequently and takes ages to pull up a live view. In comparison, I didn’t have the same issues with the Ring app — despite the camera being installed further from my router than the Arlo (Amazon’s Sidewalk network is lending a helping hand here).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="L05PkB"&gt;The Pro 3 Floodlight Cam doesn’t require an Arlo hub, but it can be used with one to help with range and extend battery life. If you want Apple Home compatibility, you need that hub, which costs $100. Unfortunately, it doesn’t have HomeKit Secure Video or local storage. There is no way around that Arlo subscription, which keeps &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/30/24055880/arlo-secure-security-camera-price-increase"&gt;getting more expensive&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5gpytg"&gt;A more budget-friendly option for a wireless outdoor floodlight camera is the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0BBX45V5B?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$130 Blink Outdoor 4 Floodlight Camera&lt;/a&gt;. I’ve not tested it yet, but it has the same software features as the Blink Wired Floodlight Camera (including local storage and person detection) and the same 143-degree field of view. It promises up to two years of battery life on two AAs (the floodlights run on four D-cell batteries) but only delivers 700 lumens of light. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="USAM6U"&gt;The best pan and tilt floodlight camera &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="8CWGsd"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:11560554" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="G6qmEI"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video quality:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 2K /  &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lumens: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;3,000 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart alerts: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;Person, can add animal, vehicles, packages and facial recognition with a hub / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Field of view:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 360 degrees (270 motion) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Siren&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;: 100 decibels / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power options:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Hardwired / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wi-Fi:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 2.4GHz / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Local (on-device or hub), cloud / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscription fee:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; $3 monthly — not required / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Amazon Alexa, Google Home&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="i0ZtV6"&gt;Eufy has gone for function over form with its beast of a floodlight camera that boasts a 360-degree field of view that pans and tilts to cover a vast area. This feature — plus its three adjustable, tunable lighting panels, individually addressable PIR motion sensors, and free local storage — makes the Eufy Floodlight Cam 2 Pro a great option if you have a large area to cover. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p id="E50t4C"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;In 2022 Eufy suffered some security vulnerabilities, which the company was not transparent about. We temporarily removed our recommendations while the company worked on a fix. While the security flaws appear to have been resolved, the company’s lack of transparency is something to consider before purchasing a Eufy camera. You can read more &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23573362/anker-eufy-security-camera-answers-encryption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;about the issues and Eufy’s solutions here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p id="ij8jCh"&gt;The camera comes with smart alerts for people out of the box, but you can connect it to a Eufy HomeBase 3 ($150) for animals, vehicle, and package alerts, and facial recognition, all processed locally on the hub; this also adds more storage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="f0xmeA"&gt;The 360-degree pan and tilt feature is well thought out, with subject lock and tracking that follows a person as they walk through your property. While you set the camera to a fixed point, it can detect motion outside its view (thanks to PIR motion sensors in each floodlight panel) and swivel the camera to catch it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KI8fx7"&gt;I like that I could adjust the sensitivity of each motion sensor and set up activity zones to limit false alerts. Opt-in rich notifications preview the captured clip right in your phone’s notification tray, reducing how often I had to open the app to check in. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="q7rKyH"&gt;A helpful auto-cruise feature let me set four preset positions and have the camera auto-rotate through them on a set schedule or on demand. A Look Around button on the main page of the Eufy app sends the camera into a surveillance spin for a quick check over my property.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/40F2rb0_MLDAf2pYuvPWGV2Up-E=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/23055514/jtuohy_211011_4898_0009.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Eufy Floodlight Cam 2 Pro looks like a mall security camera hanging off your house. It only works under eaves (as pictured), not mounted on a wall.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="Gz1OKQ"&gt;But it is ugly. And the outdated push-to-talk two-way audio (we’d love some full-duplex here), limited zoom, and no option for continuous video recording are all letdowns. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="oyp7vD"&gt;A neat feature is three lighting panels that deliver a blinding 3,000 lumens of light at up to 5,700 Kelvins, much higher than any competitor. At full brightness, it resembles the lighting of a prison yard, which is not great for most people. Thankfully, you can change the brightness and the color temperature from cool to warm. I set it to warm, and 20 percent brightness and it was more than bright enough without being harsh. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7Et7CQ"&gt;The 2K video quality is good, although the digital zoom is lacking. The camera works over 2.4GHz Wi-Fi, has a weather rating of IP65, and includes standard and color night vision. It doesn’t require a Eufy hub but can work with &lt;a href="https://support.eufy.com/s/article/Centralize-Your-Security-Ecosystem-with-HomeBase-3"&gt;the Eufy HomeBase 3&lt;/a&gt; for added features and storage, which adds &lt;a href="https://support.eufy.com/s/article/Introducing-eufy-S380-HomeBase-HomeBase-3"&gt;AI-powered smart alerts&lt;/a&gt; — including animals and vehicles, plus facial recognition. I’ve not tested this feature yet, and the HomeBase &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fus.eufy.com%2Fproducts%2Ft80301d1&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F22811985%2Fbest-smart-floodlight-security-camera" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;costs $150&lt;/a&gt; but will work with multiple Eufy cameras.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="V5S1a7"&gt;Without a HomeBase, there is 4GB of nonremovable onboard storage for around 14 days’ worth of recordings. You can also use a &lt;a href="https://support.eufy.com/s/article/Using-NAS-Storage-Step-by-Step"&gt;network-attached storage&lt;/a&gt; setup or Eufy’s cloud service for $3 a month per camera. There is no 24/7 continuous video recording, and it works with Google Home and Alexa to stream footage on smart displays and control the camera’s lights in the app. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="63pYSr"&gt;Eufy has a newer pan and tilt floodlight camera — &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fus.eufy.com%2Fproducts%2Ft8425121&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F22811985%2Fbest-smart-floodlight-security-camera" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;the E340&lt;/a&gt; — that you can buy with a HomeBase for $370 ($220 without). This one mounts to a wall, not under an eave, and has one less light panel for a maximum of 2,000 lumens. It offers 5GHz Wi-Fi and works with a microSD card (the Pro 2 has fixed onboard storage) and the HomeBase, giving you a bit more flexibility. It also offers 24/7 recording, which the Pro 2 doesn’t. I’ve not tested this yet, but if those features are important to you, it could be a better option. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="9ApBdT"&gt;The best floodlight camera for Google Home&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="w6ZXwg"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10901148" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="RX5nWW"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video quality:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 1080p HD, 6x digital zoom /  &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lumens: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;2,400 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart alerts: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;People, vehicles, animals, familiar faces ($), sound ($) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Field of view:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 130 degrees (180 motion) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Siren:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power options:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Hardwired, plug-in ($) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wi-Fi:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 2.4GHz and 5GHz / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Cloud and local / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscription fee:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; $8 a month / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Alexa, Google, Samsung SmartThings&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="gvYXJK"&gt;There is a lot to like about the Google Nest Cam with floodlight. It has built-in battery backup for when the power goes out, free on-device recording (up to three hours), free smart alerts for people, animals, and vehicles, and the option of 24/7 recording (for a fee). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ku0Qrh"&gt;It’s also got facial recognition if you take the time to add known faces. It’s a lot nicer to get an alert that says, “Sarah the Gardener is in the backyard,” rather than the scarier “There’s a person in the backyard.” You need to pay for a Nest Secure subscription service for this, which starts at $8 a month. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2hejhL"&gt;All of these features are part of the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22710545/nest-doorbell-battery-cam-battery-test-review-price-specs-features"&gt;Google Nest Cam&lt;/a&gt; that magnetically attaches to the two floodlights. The lights have good control options, including adjustable arms to angle your lighting, app, and voice control in the Google Home app, ambient light activation, and the option to dim the beams. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="COWdp3"&gt;&lt;q&gt;Google’s camera strangely lacks a built-in siren&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="9FvjUJ"&gt;But there is no built-in siren, making it a poor choice for a dedicated security device. It offers 5GHz Wi-Fi, and the on-device machine learning makes for speedier notifications than most cameras I tested. Motion sensors in the floodlights provide a wide 180-degree sensing range, ensuring the lights turn on when anything gets nearby. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="70kWEE"&gt;The camera works with the Google Home app (not the old Nest app) and can stream to both Google Nest and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/5/5/23058471/google-nest-camera-work-with-amazon-alexa-echo-speakers"&gt;Amazon Echo&lt;/a&gt; smart displays. It doesn’t fit well for an under-the-eave installation (as you can see in my pictures), so only consider it if you can install it on the side of your house and up high. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="fkiNs7"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22776184/google-nest-cam-floodlight-review-smart-security-camera"&gt;Read my full Google Nest Cam with floodlight review here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id="sn2JaZ"&gt;The best floodlight camera for Apple Home&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id="ZLt2HN"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10901161" data-anthem-component-data='{"layout":"full_layout"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="RTMytE"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video quality:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 1080p HD, 6x digital zoom / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lumens: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;2,400 / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart alerts: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;People, vehicles, animals, familiar faces  / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Field of view:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 157 degrees / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Siren:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; No / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Power options:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Hardwired / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wi-Fi:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; 2.4GHz / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Cloud / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscription fee:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; $1 a month (for iCloud+) / &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Works with:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;em&gt; Apple Home&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Cl2zap"&gt;The Eve Outdoor Cam is the best Apple Home-compatible outdoor floodlight camera. It works with &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2019/6/3/18646453/apple-homekit-support-smart-home-security-routers-wwdc-2019"&gt;HomeKit Secure Video&lt;/a&gt;, which processes all video locally on an Apple TV or HomePod. But it’s only compatible with the Apple Home and Eve app, which doesn’t have an Android version yet, so only get this if you use an iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5UrJ8k"&gt;The Eve camera is compact, svelte, and the smallest camera I tested. It was so small it didn’t completely cover the electrical box for the light it was replacing. (It only mounts on a vertical wall, so you can’t put it under an eave or overhang.) It has a good solid feel and the housing is aluminum (all the other models in this guide are plastic), and it comes in white or black. The Eve Outdoor Cam also looks much less like a mall surveillance camera than many of its competitors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="GhdUUH"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The Eve Outdoor Cam looks much less like a mall surveillance camera&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="OjLqlG"&gt;Its video quality is very good, especially during the day. Images were bright, clear, and only a little pixelated when I zoomed in. With the light on, the image was a little muddy at night, but I could make out faces clearly. The regular night vision was slightly better. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="l3Rrbx"&gt;Apple’s HomeKit video integration adds a slew of smart alerts, including people, packages, animals, and vehicles. You can also grant access to your Apple Photos library and get alerts when it recognizes people. Facial recognition and package alerts make this a good camera to set up by your front door. It’s also not super bright, as in it won’t blind visitors. But it will light up the scene well enough to see what’s happening. A brightness boost mode adds an extra bump for 30 seconds if you want a stronger floodlight. It’s nothing compared to the Eufy though, which is like walking down an airport runway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8f0yjf"&gt;There is no built-in siren or 24/7 recording, and you have to pay for an iCloud Plus plan (starting at 99 cents per month) to view any recorded video. But there is two-way audio, which is very good, and you can use the light and motion sensors separately to trigger automations in the Apple Home app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr class="p-entry-hr" id="tfTniA"&gt;
&lt;h2 id="hB2d7Z"&gt;Other outdoor floodlight cameras I tested&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/6jZpJgtlShMrfIOJbyHxplxJk2I=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24763704/8A0A9305.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wyze’s new floodlight camera packs a lot of features in for a very low price. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="TKXeKi"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wyze.com%2Fproducts%2Fwyze-cam-floodlight-pro&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F22811985%2Fbest-smart-floodlight-security-camera" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Wyze Cam Floodlight Pro&lt;/a&gt; ($150) is an upgrade to my previous budget pick, the Wyze Cam Floodlight V1, and it’s better all around, with higher lumens, tunable light, higher resolution (2.5K), and a wider field of view (180 degrees). It’s also more expensive but uses AI-powered light control that can be set only to turn the lights on when a person or vehicle is detected. The video quality is impressive at this price, and its AI-detection accuracy has improved since I started testing it. But the Reolink camera offers the same field of view and higher video resolution and keeps all of its recordings completely local. Considering Wyze has had some &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/8/23865255/wyze-security-camera-feeds-web-view-issue"&gt;security issues&lt;/a&gt; that might &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/23/24047950/wyze-cam-floodlight-v2-price-features-release-date"&gt;give you pause before purchasing one of its cameras&lt;/a&gt;, there are better options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1707752032.948979"&gt;I was impressed with the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Lorex-Wired-Floodlight-Camera-White/dp/B09VTL4FBH?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Lorex 2K Wi-Fi Floodlight Security Camera&lt;/a&gt; ($249) with its clear 2K video, loud siren, and free smart alerts for animals, vehicles, and people. There’s no cloud component (it records locally to an included microSD card) and no monthly fees. It also has a handy track and zoom feature, adjustable light temperature, rich notifications, and a more user-friendly app than the Reolink (my pick for the Best floodlight camera without subscription fees). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="1707754032.005589"&gt;However, until early 2023, Lorex was owned by Dahua, a company on the &lt;a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/11/01/lawmakers-costco-lorex-dahua-entity-list/"&gt;US government’s economic sanctions list&lt;/a&gt; (meaning the US government won’t allow these to be used in government projects or facilities). Lorex was recently sold to a Taiwanese company, but &lt;a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/11/01/lawmakers-costco-lorex-dahua-entity-list/#:~:text=The%20lawmakers%20say%20that%20Lorex%20products%20also%20present%20a%20%E2%80%9Cknown%20security%20risk%2C%E2%80%9D%20citing%20recent%20security%20flaws%20found%20in%20its%20products%2C%20and%20the%20company%E2%80%99s%20apparent%20legal%20requirement%20to%20comply%20with%20China%E2%80%99s%20intelligence%20law%20upon%20request."&gt;US lawmakers claim&lt;/a&gt; that Lorex devices still pose a potential risk to US consumers. It’s hard to tell how much of it is geopolitical games and how much is a legitimate concern. Lorex told us all its “products marketed in the U.S. are authorized by the FCC ... for consumers and private sector business customers” and pointed us to &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lorex.com%2Fblogs%2Fnews%2Florex-responds-to-stakeholder-inquiries-related-to-supply-chain&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F22811985%2Fbest-smart-floodlight-security-camera" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;this statement&lt;/a&gt; about its supply chain. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KpTNyV"&gt;The camera also has a narrow field of view (122 diagonal) compared to the Reolink (180), and its AI detection is spotty, frequently telling me my cat was a vehicle. (Smokey is smooth, but not that smooth.) While the Lorex has some better features and a better app, the Reolink has a wider field of view and higher video quality, which makes it easier to recommend for most people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="UUwpjl"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:11953769"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="FpQoj7"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photos by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="yYCOfp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update February 12th, 2024, 1PM ET: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Added new picks, new details throughout, and updated features and prices. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="qaIbqk"&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="UfbeAx"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="R2Zr4Q"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hllbBI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="W09KF1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KrP97s"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7plPwd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="e6lWt5"&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="div-gpt-ad-athena_features_desktop_3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="UG9NdT"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="c3DZmI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="QN6DWO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="PCAjIS"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="yKnvyf"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="GPDAAt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KLCOjY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/22811985/best-smart-floodlight-security-camera"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/22811985/best-smart-floodlight-security-camera</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jennifer Pattison Tuohy</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-02-08T09:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-02-08T09:30:00-05:00</updated>
    <title>This iPod-like button could be a great smart home controller</title>
    <content type="html">
  &lt;p&gt;With customizable icons and an intuitive click wheel, the Linxura solves a big problem with smart buttons. But it needs to dial up its integrations before it’s worth your money. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap p-large-text" id="AFX3ks"&gt;When my husband and I settle in to watch our latest show (currently &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24055841/amazon-mrs-and-mrs-smith-review-donald-glover-maya-erskine"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mr. &amp;amp; Mrs. Smith&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), a quick “Hey Siri, Movie Time” turns off the lights in our open-plan living / kitchen space, lowers the shades, adjusts the thermostat, and turns on the TV. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EuAogm"&gt;Then, the dog inevitably gets out of his bed and triggers the hallway motion sensor, and the lights turn back on, or my daughter comes downstairs for a snack, and the kitchen motion sensor turns those lights on. I don’t want to shout “Hey Siri” mid-show or get out my phone and be pulled down a notification rabbit hole. I just want to press a button from the comfort of the couch and descend back into darkness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="0OwXvA"&gt;Enter the &lt;a href="https://www.linxura.com/collections/linxura"&gt;Linxura Smart Controller&lt;/a&gt; (link-sure-ah), a souped-up $100 smart button shaped like a hockey puck, with &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPod_click_wheel"&gt;an iPod-like&lt;/a&gt; four-button click wheel surrounding an e-paper display. It can scroll through up to 13 screens, each showing four icons (one for each button), and gives me control over multiple gadgets in my home with just one device. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="VMnLBZ"&gt;I can turn off all the living room lights with the press of a button. If the robot vacuum resumes its job mid-action sequence, I can stop it with a click. If my son comes home late, I can lock the door behind him. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="o463y7"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="scorecard:12245709"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="aoydKu"&gt;It’s a smart solution to a common problem in the smart home: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/2/23533816/mui-board-second-gen-smatter-smart-home-control-interface"&gt;reliable, intuitive physical controls&lt;/a&gt;. It also doesn’t require a proprietary bridge or hub, something most of its competition does. Instead, it works over Wi-Fi. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="spsNJX"&gt;Unfortunately, the Linxura, launched in late 2023, has a way to go before it’s indispensable. During my testing, it only worked with Amazon Alexa, IFTTT, Philips Hue, Lifx, and Sonos. (Google Home integration was added after I finished my testing.) These integrations are all cloud-based, and some were seriously laggy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Fx3w6i"&gt;The company promises support for more platforms, including &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22832127/matter-smart-home-products-thread-wifi-explainer"&gt;Matter&lt;/a&gt;, integrations with more manufacturers, and local control for Sonos and Hue (more on that in a bit). But today, while the hardware feels like a win, the software integrations are not there yet.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/wNSqC1VgtdC94xlw7GnI9YiRxa8=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25270765/247013_Linxura_smart_control_JTuohy_0005.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;To control a device with the Linxura, you click, double click, or click-then-scroll to adjust brightness, volume, etc. Scrolling without clicking takes you to the next page of icons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="347jgU"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23301952/wemo-stage-scene-controller-review-apple-homekit-smart-home"&gt;Smart buttons&lt;/a&gt; allow you to control your smart home devices without pulling out your phone or shouting at a voice assistant and hoping it gets it right. Unlike a phone, they’re not tied to one person, making it easier for everyone in your home to control things like lights, locks, fans, shades, and thermostats. And while you &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; create complex automations so your lights never accidentally turn on during movie time, it’s still a lot of work to set up, and there are always scenarios you didn’t anticipate. That’s where a button comes in handy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="2TV9rQ"&gt;&lt;q&gt;Linxura has promised support for more platforms, including Matter&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="6LxNkr"&gt;Smart buttons are generally wireless and battery-operated, so you can put them where you need them or use them like remote controls. Most require you to remember what you programmed them to do, making them useless for anyone else unless you put dozens in strategic spots (like light switches). To get around this conundrum, some come with little icon stickers or have raised dots on the surface to let you distinguish them by touch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uui4oM"&gt;The Linxura’s e-paper screen fixes this problem in an ingenious way. Each of the Linxura’s four buttons get its own icon and can perform three actions: click, double click, or click and hold then rotate the wheel (clockwise or counterclockwise). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="aQ3fch"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"The Philips Hue Tap Dial is for the superusers ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2022/8/20/23311283/philips-hue-tap-dial-switch-review"},{"title":"Wemo’s Stage Scene Controller is the light switch evolved ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23301952/wemo-stage-scene-controller-review-apple-homekit-smart-home"},{"title":"How the smart home is finally getting out of your phone and into your home ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/24043060/smart-home-interface-map-view-samsung-lg-amazon-ces-2024"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="T7NH6n"&gt;The e-paper display isn’t the sharpest, and the three-to-four-character text descriptions are tiny, but there are lots of icons to choose from — including light, lock, vacuum, and fan — so it’s easy enough to see what you’re controlling. There’s an attempt at backlighting, which turns on when you pick up the device using a built-in light and capacitive sensor. This helps at night, although it illuminates the screen unevenly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="VRoLvP"&gt;An e-paper screen instead of LCD means a longer battery life (up to three months on a single charge, according to the company — I was down to 80 percent after a week of testing). The built-in battery is charged via an included USB-A to USB-C cable. The controller is small and easy to lose, but a magnetic mount accessory ($14.99) gives it a home on a wall or coffee table. The app has a “find me” feature that will beep the button to help you find it, but it’s very quiet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="CB2dDZ"&gt;I’d love it if the Linxura were smart enough to know which room you were in, so if you carried it to another room, the screen would adapt when you were in the bedroom versus the kitchen. As it is, it’s very much designed to be used in one space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div class="c-image-grid"&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/MsnMWcnIcqKqfEsDDTm70k9silY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25270771/247013_Linxura_smart_control_JTuohy_0011.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Linxura’s battery is charged with an included USB-C cable.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="c-image-grid__item"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/YEZlc7OVUh41b_ihw2Qlis0D8aA=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25270772/247013_Linxura_smart_control_JTuohy_0012.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;A power / reset button is on the back, and the controller can snap into a magnetic mount.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="jZ5LWP"&gt;Setting up and connecting my smart home devices to the Linxura was straightforward (if a bit tedious) thanks to its well-laid-out app and clear instructions. I started with Alexa, as all the lights in my house work with the platform. In fact, I could link almost every Alexa-connected device to a button, although some had limited functions. (I couldn’t open my garage door, only close it, and only one of my many cameras could be connected — a Blink Floodlight — and that was just to control the light.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="2DMZvL"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The hardware feels like a win; the software integrations are not up to scratch&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="zqXtey"&gt;I set one button to toggle on / off a group of lights with a press and rotate clockwise to dim and counterclockwise to brighten. This took a while since it requires setting up each button action as a separate routine in the Alexa app. Setting up 52 devices or scenes (a button can control a scene or group in Alexa) to this controller would mean creating over 200 Alexa Routines. It can be done, but if you’ve spent much time with the Alexa app, you know you’ll need the patience of a saint to accomplish this. Of course, you might only need it to do four things for you, which should take about 15 minutes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AljRoT"&gt;Once through setup, the buttons worked every time to trigger a device, scene, or group — but with noticeable lag, probably due to the cloud-to-cloud communication. One connection to a &lt;a href="https://bondhome.io/"&gt;Bond&lt;/a&gt; controller through Alexa took a full 45 seconds to turn on the fan. But I achieved my initial goal and could turn off all the lights downstairs when settled on the couch with just a click of a button. Smart home harmony for the win. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="xLsWoj"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="gallery:12245781"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="2aciS8"&gt;The problem with the lag, though, is I often thought it hadn’t worked and clicked again, which meant lights would turn on and then back off a few seconds later. I also found scrolling through the screens was a bit too easy — occasionally thinking I was dialing to adjust brightness only to find I was now closing my garage door.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="K3xLzi"&gt;The cloud connections directly to Hue and Sonos were easier to set up, more responsive, and offered a glimpse of the Linxura’s potential. Once I linked accounts, I could set up and edit control for each button action in the Linxura app — no need to go into the Sonos or Hue apps or mess around with Alexa Routines. I paired a button with a Hue light and had it dim, brighten, toggle on or off, and even change color. But a bug in the Linxura app wouldn’t let me scroll through my Hue lights — meaning I could only choose from the five lights at the top of the page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="BEPcBs"&gt;&lt;q&gt;To be truly useful, the Linxura needs local control and more integrations&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="MqOy2K"&gt;The Sonos integration was smoother, and I could set the single press to start / stop music from my Sonos Arc, rotate to control volume, and double-click to play the next track on my current playlist. The volume control was laggy, and it was easy to accidentally blast the sound or dial it down to mute — I now know how loud a Sonos Arc can get. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KgbL4I"&gt;I also had to choose a single speaker; it didn’t let me control a group (Linxura says this feature is coming). A hundred bucks is a lot to pay for that feature, though, when this &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ikea.com%2Fus%2Fen%2Fp%2Fsymfonisk-sound-remote-gen-2-30527312%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F24064662%2Flinxura-smart-controller-review" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$18 Ikea remote&lt;/a&gt; has more functionality with Sonos (although you do need a &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ikea.com%2Fus%2Fen%2Fp%2Fdirigera-hub-for-smart-products-white-smart-50503414%2F&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F24064662%2Flinxura-smart-controller-review" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$70 Ikea hub&lt;/a&gt; to use it).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Ed-ms0bfLbzW4Fe-7j25CJqxFEE=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25270769/247013_Linxura_smart_control_JTuohy_0009.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The click wheel moves easily, and the buttons are satisfyingly clicky.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="GvKdNe"&gt;Overall, I love the idea here — it’s a simple, intuitive controller. Its app is well laid out and easy to use. But at $100, it’s pricey, and while it’s nice that it doesn’t require a proprietary hub or bridge, that’s part of why it’s not super responsive. To be truly useful, it needs local control and more integrations. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="Jwj7mm"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="tiktok-embed" cite="https://www.tiktok.com/@verge/video/7333674143868669215" data-video-id="7333674143868669215" data-embed-from="oembed" style="max-width: 605px;min-width: 325px;"&gt; &lt;section&gt; &lt;a target="_blank" title="@verge" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@verge?refer=embed"&gt;@verge&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt;A button, a button, my smart home for a button … that works locally and controls all my devices. Ah well, in the meantime, this Linxura Smart Controller is a new smart button featuring a handy e-paper screen and customizable icons that show you what you’re controlling when you click its buttons. The iPod-like click wheel can do things like dim lights or control the volume on your Sonos speakers. It’s a great alternative to voice control or using your phone. But it’s all cloud-based, so it can be slow, and it only works with Alexa and Google Home platforms. Support for Matter, Apple Home, and more is promised, but if you want those wait before spending $100 on it. &lt;a title="smarthome" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/smarthome?refer=embed"&gt;#smarthome&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="smartbuttons" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/smartbuttons?refer=embed"&gt;#smartbuttons&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="apple" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/apple?refer=embed"&gt;#apple&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="google" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/google?refer=embed"&gt;#google&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="matter" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/matter?refer=embed"&gt;#matter&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a title="techtok" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/tag/techtok?refer=embed"&gt;#techtok&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;a target="_blank" title="♬ original sound - The Verge" href="https://www.tiktok.com/music/original-sound-7333674496928959263?refer=embed"&gt;♬ original sound - The Verge&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/section&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;script async="" src="https://www.tiktok.com/embed.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="4J7Ams"&gt;Support for Google Home was added recently. (I haven’t been able to fully test it yet, but &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O-BG9Gry7IA"&gt;the setup process&lt;/a&gt; is similar to using Alexa.) Linxura tells me it has support for SmartThings and Wiz coming next, with Matter, SwitchBot, Homey, and local control for Sonos and Lifx slated for Q2. Apple Home, Ecobee, Nest thermostats, Wemo, and August are scheduled for Q3 and Home Assistant, Nanoleaf, Resideo, Yale, and Rachio for Q4. Linxura says the hardware is fully compatible with all its future integrations, so you shouldn’t need to buy a new device when or if they’re launched.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="vS7pkH"&gt;That’s an ambitious plan. And as every &lt;em&gt;Verge&lt;/em&gt; reader knows, never buy a product on the promise of future features. I’ll monitor its progress and update this review if and when it reaches critical mass. For now, if you use Amazon Alexa or Google Home, you might find this device useful (if you can handle a bit of lag and a lot of setup).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/4UFxLc1oHd3nyhJtTo1xAAPi71s=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25270763/247013_Linxura_smart_control_JTuohy_0003.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The smart controller comes in three colors: black and white (pictured) and gray.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="1AfZwR"&gt;Getting a smart home control device to work with every platform and manufacturer — and to work well — is not a problem unique to Linxura. Flic — arguably the leader in smart buttons — works with Apple HomeKit, SmartThings, and Amazon Alexa but not Google Home. But its &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/12/23870169/flic-twist-smart-home-button-launch-matter-apple-homekit"&gt;Flic Twist controller&lt;/a&gt;, which has a dial similar to the Linxura’s, is limited in certain platforms. Similarly, the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/8/20/23311283/philips-hue-tap-dial-switch-review"&gt;Hue Tap Dial&lt;/a&gt; works in Apple Home and Alexa and supports Matter, but its dial control only works with Hue lights. Both of these also require a proprietary bridge, adding to the cost. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="j03Mgp"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Compatible-HomeKit-Automatically-Accessories-Scenes-Thread/dp/B0C7BLSMMW?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Onvis five-button controller&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23301952/wemo-stage-scene-controller-review-apple-homekit-smart-home"&gt;Wemo Stage Scene Controller&lt;/a&gt; only work with HomeKit, despite using Thread. The &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/TUO-Support-Control-Accessories-HomeKit/dp/B0CCRDV8GH?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Tuo Smart Button&lt;/a&gt; uses Matter-over-Thread, but only Apple Home and Samsung SmartThings have adopted Matter button support. This type of confusing interoperability is precisely what Matter was designed to fix. The smart home standard is supposed to make it so that companies don’t have to set up and maintain individual integrations with everyone. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23997548/matter-smart-home-2023-platforms"&gt;But it’s not there yet&lt;/a&gt; — at least not for buttons. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="hvbdDJ"&gt;It’s hard to ding this device for not solving a problem nobody else has. But it hasn’t. It &lt;em&gt;has&lt;/em&gt; done a decent job of fixing the “How am I supposed to know what this button does?” issue. And for that, I say, good job, Linxura. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="p4JPkV"&gt;As much as I enjoy the e-paper screen and the satisfying rotating click wheel, based on Linxura’s limited integrations and cloud dependency, it’s too hard to recommend today. If it delivers on its future integrations, and if Matter sorts out support for smart buttons, well, then it gets a lot more interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-wide-block"&gt;&lt;div id="IZ2Znf"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12246859"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="N1QXkP"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photos by Jennifer Pattison Tuohy / The Verge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24064662/linxura-smart-controller-review"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24064662/linxura-smart-controller-review</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jennifer Pattison Tuohy</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
