<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Microsofts</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-15T12:26:31-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/microsoft/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/microsoft" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T12:26:31-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T12:26:31-04:00</updated>
    <title>Microsoft is stuffing pop-up ads into Google Chrome on Windows again</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Screenshot of a Bing pop-up on Windows" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/XgfK1JBj_QVULcVQ4gSx7E_CPEI=/0x0:1320x880/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209773/microsoftbingpopup.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image composite: &lt;a class="ql-link" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/antivirus/comments/1beg1bi/is_this_microsoft_bing_popup_malware/" target="_blank"&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt; (TheDyslexicCow) / Tom Warren / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="obIFaN"&gt;Microsoft is once again injecting pop-ups into Google’s Chrome browser in a bid to get people to switch to Bing. The software giant first &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/30/23851902/microsoft-bing-popups-windows-11-malware"&gt;introduced malware-like pop-up ads&lt;/a&gt; last year with a prompt that appeared over the top of other apps and windows. After pausing that notification to address “unintended behavior,” the pop-ups have returned again on Windows 10 and 11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mwvdBw"&gt;Windows users have reported seeing the new pop-up in recent days, advertising Bing AI and Microsoft’s Bing search engine inside Google Chrome. If you click yes to this prompt, then Microsoft will set Bing as the default search engine for Chrome. These latest prompts look like malware, and once again have &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/antivirus/comments/1beg1bi/is_this_microsoft_bing_popup_malware/"&gt;Windows users asking&lt;/a&gt; if they are legit or nefarious. Microsoft has confirmed to &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; that the pop-ups are genuine and should only appear once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="cFVYZn"&gt;“This is a one-time notification giving people the choice to set Bing as their default search engine on Chrome,” says Caitlin Roulston, director of communications, in a statement to &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;. Roulston framed the pop-up as offering perks to Windows users, since they can get more chat turns in Copilot if they accept the notification. “We value providing our customers with choice, so there is an option to dismiss the notification.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/WsQ3wNO9p-oLw4CESv0J73z5Noc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/24883698/bingpopup0.jpeg"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Screenshot by Tom Warren / The Verge&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Microsoft used similar pop-ups in Windows last year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="3JI6ak"&gt;If Microsoft really valued providing Windows users with choice, then it would offer up an easy way to disable these pop-ups for good. There are a variety of ways that Microsoft attempts to prompt Windows users into switching to Bing and Edge, making it difficult to avoid them through tweaking settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EqvcBs"&gt;I’ve been growing increasingly frustrated with Microsoft’s attempts to aggressively push pop-up ads on Chrome users in recent years. Microsoft has been using pop-ups inside Chrome, on the Windows taskbar, and elsewhere to promote its own services. Microsoft even once &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/21310611/microsoft-edge-browser-forced-update-chromium-editorial"&gt;forced people into Edge after a Windows Update&lt;/a&gt;, and it regularly presents a full-screen message to try to get Windows users to switch to Bing and Edge after updates are applied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="XoF4t7"&gt;Earlier this year, Microsoft even &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/16/24074712/microsoft-edge-automatic-chrome-import-data-bug-fix"&gt;had to fix an issue&lt;/a&gt; where its Edge browser was automatically importing browsing data and tabs from Chrome without consent. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24054329/microsoft-edge-automatic-chrome-import-data-feature"&gt;I personally experienced the bug&lt;/a&gt;; after I rebooted my PC for a Windows update, Microsoft Edge automatically opened with the Chrome tabs I was working on before the update.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="734GG7"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/8/30/23851902/microsoft-bing-popups-windows-11-malware"&gt;I wrote in August&lt;/a&gt; that I was “counting the days until the next annoying pop-up appears,” and here it is a little over six months later. I’m still hoping Microsoft will eventually give up with these annoying pop-ups and respect Windows users’ choice to pick whichever search engine and browser they wish to use.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101887/microsoft-bing-popups-windows-11-google-chrome"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101887/microsoft-bing-popups-windows-11-google-chrome</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T14:25:07-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T14:25:07-04:00</updated>
    <title>Microsoft launches Copilot Pro worldwide with a one-month free trial</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A colorful illustration of Microsoft’s Copilot AI assistant" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/WyfqQJDnTI3si-91cXd9FAJrj98=/150x0:1770x1080/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73207400/1920x1080_Copilot_Blog_Image.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Microsoft&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="xDGt6G"&gt;Microsoft is expanding its $20 monthly Copilot Pro subscription to more markets today, after launching the AI-powered assistant &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/15/24038711/microsoft-copilot-pro-office-ai-apps"&gt;for consumers in January&lt;/a&gt;. The expansion sees Copilot Pro available in 222 countries in total, and Microsoft is launching a free one-month trial to entice consumers to subscribe to its AI vision of the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ww7apb"&gt;Copilot Pro includes priority access to the latest OpenAI models, the ability to build your own Copilot GPT, and access to Copilot inside Office apps if you’re already a Microsoft 365 Personal or Home subscriber. Now, Microsoft is also unlocking Copilot Pro inside the Office web apps, so you don’t need a separate Microsoft 365 subscription to use the chatbot inside Word, Outlook, and other free web apps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="zHsHBf"&gt;This Copilot Pro integration will also be available in mobile apps soon. “We’ll extend this benefit to our free mobile apps as well, including the Microsoft 365 app and Outlook for iOS and Android, in the coming months,” &lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=nOD%2FrLJHOac&amp;amp;mid=24542&amp;amp;u1=verge&amp;amp;murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.microsoft.com%2Fen-us%2Fmicrosoft-365%2Fblog%2F2024%2F03%2F14%2Fbringing-copilot-to-more-customers-worldwide-across-life-and-work%2F" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;says Divya Kumar&lt;/a&gt;, general manager of search and AI marketing at Microsoft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="oBrYZF"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Microsoft’s next big AI push is here after a year of Bing ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/7/24064440/microsoft-super-bowl-ad-ai-copilot"},{"title":"Microsoft’s new Copilot Pro brings AI-powered Office features to the rest of us","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/15/24038711/microsoft-copilot-pro-office-ai-apps"},{"title":"One month with&amp;amp;nbsp;Microsoft’s AI vision of the future: Copilot Pro","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/21/24078972/microsoft-copilot-pro-ai-hands-on-features"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="P2YLYe"&gt;If you want to try out Copilot Pro you’ll need to install the Copilot app on iOS or Android to get the free month offer. Microsoft has been trying to entice consumers to use the Copilot mobile app since launching it at the end of 2023, including with a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/7/24064440/microsoft-super-bowl-ad-ai-copilot"&gt;Super Bowl ad&lt;/a&gt; that focused solely on the mobile version.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5mkh09"&gt;Microsoft is also extending the availability of its Copilot for Microsoft 365 to more businesses. “Customers that have Microsoft 365 F3 and F1, Office 365 E1, Business Basic, and more will be eligible to purchase Copilot for Microsoft 365 in the coming weeks,” says Kumar. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="paprE5"&gt;Microsoft is now gearing up to show off more improvements to Copilot in the coming months, including some Windows 11 changes that are likely to be detailed at the company’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/14/24073220/microsoft-build-event-schedule-may-21"&gt;Build developer conference in May&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100993/microsoft-copilot-pro-launch-free-trial"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100993/microsoft-copilot-pro-launch-free-trial</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T11:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T11:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Intel’s new Core i9-14900KS arrives today for $689 with boosts up to 6.2GHz</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Illustration of Intel’s new Core i9-14900KS processor" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/PHc_3J6safkIuOFAOCOs5LKhf1w=/267x0:2195x1285/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73206666/14900ks.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Intel&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="HEuPlJ"&gt;Intel is launching its flagship Core i9-14900KS processor today, with clock speeds that boost all the way up to 6.2GHz. That’s 200MHz more than the previous Core i9-13900KS that &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/12/23551748/intel-6ghz-processor-core-i9-13900k-release-date-price"&gt;launched last year&lt;/a&gt; and was the first desktop processor to break the 6GHz barrier at stock speeds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="0s2g5r"&gt;This new Core i9-14900KS will be priced at $689, $10 less than the previous 13900KS, and will be available in stores today. The 6.2GHz max turbo frequency is an out-of-the-box boost, so there could be room for overclocking to push these speeds even further. The 14900KS has the same 24 cores found on the 14900K, with eight performance cores and 16 efficiency ones. It does run at a 150-watt base power, though, instead of the 125 watts found on the 14900K.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="izY4O3"&gt;Other than the power and turbo frequencies, the 14900KS is almost identical to the 14900K. It’s essentially a “binned” version that has been selected to run at a higher clock speed. Z790 and Z690 motherboards will support the 14900KS with the latest BIOS updates.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ag_9keaz8I54w7nQoTJ7ioNy7Rc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334268/14900ksbenchmarks.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Intel&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Intel’s own 14900KS benchmarks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="qrM6w6"&gt;Intel is promising up to 15 percent better gaming performance from the 14900KS over the 13900KS and up to 73 percent for 3D production multitasking workflows over AMD’s Ryzen 9 7950X. It will be interesting to see just how well the 14900KS performs against AMD’s Ryzen 7 7800X3D, which has dominated PC gaming performance recently. Intel’s own benchmarks suggest the 14900KS may well beat the 7800X3D in some games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="aUibof"&gt;The Core i9-14900KS will likely be one of the last LGA 1700 socket processors on the market, as Intel is moving to a new socket for its upcoming generation of CPUs. Retailers will start stocking the 14900KS on shelves today priced at $689. This new processor will also be available inside OEM systems, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TVFBbV"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Correction March 14th, 12:40PM ET:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this story stated the 14900KS started at $699. It starts at $689. We regret the error.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24099713/intel-core-i9-14900ks-release-date-price-features"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24099713/intel-core-i9-14900ks-release-date-price-features</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-13T13:59:05-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-13T13:59:05-04:00</updated>
    <title>Microsoft Teams is finally moving to a single app for personal and work </title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Microsoft Teams illustration" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/H3BbbY3TPsKFPHXGRA-3gmaDrHs=/0x0:2640x1760/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73204499/microsoftteams.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Microsoft&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="ze3cyC"&gt;Microsoft is finally creating a single version of Microsoft Teams that will allow you to switch between personal and work accounts easily. The new unified app is currently in testing and will let Microsoft Teams users switch between multiple tenants and personal or work account types.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="waLPtu"&gt;This new version of Teams will be rolled out to commercial users &lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=nOD%2FrLJHOac&amp;amp;mid=24542&amp;amp;u1=verge&amp;amp;murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.microsoft.com%2Fen-us%2Fmicrosoft-365%2Froadmap%3Ffilters%3D%26searchterms%3D383006" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;in April&lt;/a&gt; and will include an account switcher that’s accessible from the profile section. “We received consistent feedback from personal and work users: you prefer a single Teams app that allows you to easily access and switch between personal and work accounts,” says Microsoft &lt;a href="https://blogs.windows.com/windows-insider/2024/03/13/announcing-windows-11-insider-preview-build-26080-canary-and-dev-channels/"&gt;in a blog post&lt;/a&gt;. “This update lets you use one app for all kinds of Teams accounts.”&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/h_wrSFFphoqwTxM6jnrR23bFMJU=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334215/01_UnifiedMeControl.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Microsoft&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can easily switch between accounts in the new Microsoft Teams app.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="TwY65M"&gt;In future updates, you’ll also be able to select the account you want to use when joining a meeting link or even join a meeting without signing in. This unified app will even let you launch personal and work accounts for Teams with separate icons on the taskbar instead of having to install and launch separate apps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4yB1EM"&gt;Notifications are also being improved in this updated Teams app, so you can see which team a notification has come from. “In addition, personal notifications have more details, giving clear and easy actions from the notification banner,” says Microsoft.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/npfz2AwzBBHI1Y_NbcW7yg12IM4=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334218/04_TFLNotificationCropped.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Microsoft&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Improved Microsoft Teams notifications.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="bBw1eA"&gt;Microsoft has long had a rather confusing experience for Teams users who use both personal and work accounts. Windows 11 integrated Teams directly into the taskbar, but this Chat experience only worked for personal accounts. Microsoft walked away from this direct integration in recent Windows 11 updates, but you still need to download and install two separate Teams apps to access both personal and work meetings. That meant having Microsoft Teams (free) and Microsoft Teams (work or school) both installed, and it’s easy to launch the wrong one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="jIHnTx"&gt;Microsoft is now planning to remove the Microsoft Teams (free) app in the future and convert everyone to this single app which will just be Microsoft Teams. This new Teams experience will be part of an upcoming update to Windows 11, version 24H2, which will be available later this year.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099723/microsoft-teams-unified-app-personal-work-accounts"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099723/microsoft-teams-unified-app-personal-work-accounts</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-13T12:59:24-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-13T12:59:24-04:00</updated>
    <title>Microsoft’s AI Copilot for Security launches next month with pay-as-you-go pricing</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Illustration of Microsoft Copilot for Security" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/faIcaTLBaDRqSeeaxjWbR8kCy7U=/99x0:1161x708/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73204276/copilotsecurity.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Microsoft&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="G3nB5T"&gt;Microsoft is &lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=nOD%2FrLJHOac&amp;amp;mid=24542&amp;amp;u1=verge&amp;amp;murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.microsoft.com%2Fen-us%2Fsecurity%2Fblog%2F2024%2F03%2F13%2Fmicrosoft-copilot-for-security-is-generally-available-on-april-1-2024-with-new-capabilities%2F" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;launching its Copilot for Security&lt;/a&gt; next month, bringing its generative AI chatbot to the cybersecurity space. Copilot for Security is designed for cybersecurity professionals to help them protect against threats, but it won’t be a one-off monthly charge like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/15/24038726/microsoft-copilot-microsoft-365-business-launch-availability"&gt;Copilot for Microsoft 365&lt;/a&gt;. Instead, Microsoft will charge businesses $4 per hour of usage as part of a consumption model when Copilot for Security launches on April 1st.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="I1vqXZ"&gt;Powered by OpenAI’s GPT-4 and Microsoft’s own security-specific model, Copilot for Security is essentially a chatbot where cybersecurity workers can get the latest information on security incidents, summaries of threats, and more. Microsoft &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/3/28/23659711/microsoft-security-copilot-gpt-4-ai-tool-features"&gt;first started testing this chatbot&lt;/a&gt; nearly a year ago, and it includes access to the latest information on security threats and Microsoft’s 78 trillion daily signals that the company collects through its threat intelligence gathering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="PMTZ3H"&gt;&lt;div style="left: 0; width: 100%; height: 0; position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sNaxv2zflmc?rel=0" style="top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute; border: 0;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="accelerometer; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share;"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="UmieBY"&gt;Copilot for Security includes a pinboard section for collaboration between cybersecurity employees, and the ability to summarize events for reporting purposes. Like many other AI chatbots, you can use natural language inputs, feed in files for analysis, or even get Copilot for Security to analyze code. All the prompts are saved in a history log for auditing at a later date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="QMm4mp"&gt;The pay-as-you-go pricing is designed to allow businesses to scale what they need for AI-powered cybersecurity efforts. “We will have one simple pricing model that covers both the standalone Copilot experience, and embedded experiences across the Microsoft Security product portfolio,” says Microsoft. “A consumption model means it will be easy to get started quickly and on a small scale, to experiment and learn with no upfront per device or per user charges.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8lDxRL"&gt;Microsoft’s push for AI in cybersecurity comes as the company is under attack from Russian state-sponsored hackers. Nobelium, the same group behind the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/12/13/22173035/hackers-russia-breached-us-government-agencies-email-cozy-bear"&gt;SolarWinds attack&lt;/a&gt;, managed to spy on some Microsoft executive email inboxes for months. That initial attack also led to some of Microsoft’s source code being stolen, with the hackers getting access to the company’s source code repositories and internal systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="5rj93K"&gt;Microsoft is in the middle of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/2/23943178/microsoft-security-secure-future-initiative-cybersecurity"&gt;overhauling its software security&lt;/a&gt; following serious Azure cloud attacks in recent years. Thirty thousand organizations’ &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/3/5/22316189/microsoft-exchange-server-security-exploit-china-attack-30000-organizations"&gt;email servers were hacked&lt;/a&gt; in 2021 due to a Microsoft Exchange Server flaw, and Chinese hackers &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/12/23792371/security-breach-china-us-government-emails-microsoft-cloud-exploit"&gt;breached US government emails&lt;/a&gt; via a Microsoft cloud exploit last year.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099670/microsoft-copilot-for-security-pricing-launch-date-features"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099670/microsoft-copilot-for-security-pricing-launch-date-features</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-08T19:31:05-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-08T19:31:05-05:00</updated>
    <title>Activision QA workers form the largest US video game union yet</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Vector illustration of the Xbox logo." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/4eP_xLoTdVRZM3M-37Bk6UtI87A=/20x0:2021x1334/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73193239/STK048_XBOX_D.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="s5c9hq"&gt;Around 600 workers in Activision Publishing’s quality assurance department have formed a union. Assisted by the Communications Workers of America, the employees completed their vote with the results certified on Friday, March 8th. With that, Activision Quality Assurance United – CWA becomes the latest union to arise out of Microsoft’s gaming division and the largest video game union in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="6BxLhe"&gt;In 2022, Microsoft &lt;a href="https://cwa-union.org/news/releases/cwa-microsoft-announce-labor-neutrality-agreement"&gt;affirmed a labor neutrality agreement with the CWA&lt;/a&gt; which eases the organization process at the company and its subsidiaries including Activision Blizzard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="uWviLk"&gt;In an interview with &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;, Tom Shelley, a technical requirements specialist and one of Activision Quality Assurance United’s organizers, said the labor neutrality agreement and Microsoft’s acquisition of Activision Blizzard last year made their goals of unionizing easier to accomplish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="21oBTs"&gt;“This has been an emergent effort that’s arisen in the last few weeks in response to the opportunities we’ve had to freely organize following the merger,” Shelley said. “As QA workers, we often have the weakest protections and lowest pay of any workers in the industry — even though our work is integral to the success of the companies we work for and the titles we make.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="m8RK8C"&gt;In quality assurance, workers test games looking for bugs and other issues, flagging them for other developers to fix. Since the majority of QA jobs are typically entry level, the industry has a reputation for devaluing these roles, emphasizing the need for labor protections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="xDVwSD"&gt;Shelley praised Microsoft for voluntarily recognizing the union and hopes it will inspire more organizing at the company and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="XgB87W"&gt;Last year, Microsoft voluntarily recognized a union of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/12/5/23495139/microsoft-union-zenimax-bethesda-cwa"&gt;300 QA workers at ZeniMax online&lt;/a&gt;. It joined the union at &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/12/2/23489932/activision-blizzard-albany-qa-union"&gt;Blizzard Albany&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/5/23/23138412/activision-blizzard-union-vote-game-workers-alliance"&gt;Raven Software&lt;/a&gt;. Video game labor unions are picking up steam but have faced difficulties in light of the rampant layoffs. In 2023, the CWA &lt;a href="https://www.gamesindustry.biz/sega-of-america-accused-of-threatening-workers-with-mass-layoffs-over-unionisation"&gt;filed an unfair labor complaint against Sega&lt;/a&gt;, claiming the company was planning to “phase out” temporary employees who were part of the company’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/4/24/23683648/sega-of-america-unionize-cwa"&gt;Aegis union that formed last year&lt;/a&gt;. When Sega eventually did lay off employees, Aegis said union negotiations were able &lt;a href="https://www.gamesindustry.biz/sega-of-america-to-lay-off-61-employees"&gt;to save a number of jobs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/8/24094602/activision-blizzard-qa-workers-unionizing-microsoft"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/8/24094602/activision-blizzard-qa-workers-unionizing-microsoft</id>
    <author>
      <name>Ash Parrish</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-08T09:43:28-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-08T09:43:28-05:00</updated>
    <title>Microsoft says Russian hackers stole source code after spying on its executives</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Microsoft logo" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/Y9yyeHzmAwfWU_CF8qXzUK0nR2E=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73191488/STK095_Microsoft_04.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration: The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="taVRaY"&gt;Microsoft &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/19/24044561/microsoft-senior-leadership-emails-hack-russian-security-attack"&gt;revealed earlier this year&lt;/a&gt; that Russian state-sponsored hackers had been spying on the email accounts of some members of its senior leadership team. Now, Microsoft is disclosing that the attack, from the same group behind the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2020/12/13/22173035/hackers-russia-breached-us-government-agencies-email-cozy-bear"&gt;SolarWinds attack&lt;/a&gt;, has also led to some source code being stolen in what Microsoft describes as an ongoing attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="SebPnn"&gt;“In recent weeks, we have seen evidence that Midnight Blizzard [Nobelium] is using information initially exfiltrated from our corporate email systems to gain, or attempt to gain, unauthorized access,” explains Microsoft in a &lt;a href="https://msrc.microsoft.com/blog/2024/03/update-on-microsoft-actions-following-attack-by-nation-state-actor-midnight-blizzard/"&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt;. “This has included access to some of the company’s source code repositories and internal systems. To date we have found no evidence that Microsoft-hosted customer-facing systems have been compromised.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="bbAvSK"&gt;It’s not clear what source code was accessed, but Microsoft warns that the Nobelium group,  or “Midnight Blizzard,” as Microsoft &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/4/19/23689456/microsoft-weather-cybersecurity-threat-actors-naming"&gt;refers to them&lt;/a&gt;, is now attempting to use “secrets of different types it has found” to try to further breach the software giant and potentially its customers. “Some of these secrets were shared between customers and Microsoft in email, and as we discover them in our exfiltrated email, we have been and are reaching out to these customers to assist them in taking mitigating measures,” says Microsoft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="2nnlGn"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Hackers backed by Russian government reportedly breached US government agencies","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2020/12/13/22173035/hackers-russia-breached-us-government-agencies-email-cozy-bear"},{"title":"Microsoft warns of ‘sophisticated’ Russian email attack targeting government agencies","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2021/5/28/22458202/microsoft-nobelium-hack-usaid-email-phishing-hacking-target-solarwinds"},{"title":"Microsoft is overhauling its software security after major Azure cloud attacks","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/2/23943178/microsoft-security-secure-future-initiative-cybersecurity"},{"title":"Microsoft&amp;amp;nbsp;explains how Russian hackers spied on its executives","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/26/24051708/microsoft-hack-russian-security-attack-senior-leadership-emails"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="fIqh4P"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/26/24051708/microsoft-hack-russian-security-attack-senior-leadership-emails"&gt;Nobelium initially accessed Microsoft’s systems&lt;/a&gt; through a password spray attack last year. This type of attack is a brute-force approach where hackers utilize a large dictionary of potential passwords against accounts. Microsoft had configured a non-production test tenant account without two-factor authentication enabled, allowing Nobelium to gain access.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7TkGg3"&gt;“Across Microsoft, we have increased our security investments, cross-enterprise coordination and mobilization, and have enhanced our ability to defend ourselves and secure and harden our environment against this advanced persistent threat,” says Microsoft. “We have and will continue to put in place additional enhanced security controls, detections, and monitoring.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="chqZpz"&gt;The attack on Microsoft initially took place just days after the company announced its &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/11/2/23943178/microsoft-security-secure-future-initiative-cybersecurity"&gt;plan to overhaul its software security&lt;/a&gt; following serious Azure cloud attacks. Microsoft has been at the center of several high-profile security attacks in recent years, including 30,000 organizations’ &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/3/5/22316189/microsoft-exchange-server-security-exploit-china-attack-30000-organizations"&gt;email servers getting hacked&lt;/a&gt; in 2021 due to a Microsoft Exchange Server flaw and Chinese hackers &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/12/23792371/security-breach-china-us-government-emails-microsoft-cloud-exploit"&gt;breaching US government emails&lt;/a&gt; via a Microsoft cloud exploit last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="MhgtQo"&gt;Microsoft is still investigating Nobelium’s latest attacks on its systems. “Our active investigations of Midnight Blizzard activities are ongoing, and findings of our investigations will continue to evolve,” says Microsoft. “We remain committed to sharing what we learn.”&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/8/24094287/microsoft-hack-russian-security-attack-stolen-source-code"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/8/24094287/microsoft-hack-russian-security-attack-stolen-source-code</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-07T07:13:26-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-07T07:13:26-05:00</updated>
    <title>Microsoft confirms Surface and Windows AI event for March 21st</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="The Microsoft Surface Laptop 5 open on an office table. The screen displays a green ribbon." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/JUekKKCzVTOhAffyliyp_MMAvJs=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73188493/226368_Surface_Laptop_5_AKrales_0005.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo by Amelia Holowaty Krales / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="Q30sDo"&gt;Microsoft has quietly announced a “digital event” for Surface, Windows, and Copilot later this month. The March 21st &lt;a href="https://modernworkannounce.event.microsoft.com/?ranMID=24542"&gt;“new era of work” event&lt;/a&gt; is targeted at Microsoft’s business customers and will feature &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091211/microsoft-surface-pro-10-surface-laptop-6-release-date-specs"&gt;new Surface Pro 10 and Surface Laptop 6 devices for businesses&lt;/a&gt;, as we reported earlier this week, with a focus on Microsoft’s upcoming AI improvements to Windows 11.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HUYfUF"&gt;The Surface Pro 10 and Surface Laptop 6 commercial versions will be minor spec bumps, according to sources familiar with Microsoft’s plans. Microsoft will also offer an OLED display on the Surface Pro 10 for consumers, which the company is expected to reveal later this spring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="8BbTB2"&gt;&lt;q&gt;The Surface Laptop 6 may include a new design&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="1oIGv8"&gt;The new Surface Laptop 6 could be the most interesting device, thanks to a new design that will reportedly include thinner display bezels, rounded corners, a haptic touchpad, and two USB-C and one USB-A ports. Microsoft is rumored to be shipping both Intel Core Ultra and Snapdragon X Elite-based models of its latest Surface hardware, with Intel models expected in April and the Arm ones in June.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Cvvkta"&gt;The event page for Microsoft’s March event simply says “tune in here for the latest in scaling AI in your environment with Copilot, Windows, and Surface,” suggesting this will be a rather low-key event that’s focused on Microsoft’s big “AI PC” push.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="RTNGtK"&gt;Microsoft is also working on a new AI Explorer experience for Windows 11, that’s designed as a far more advanced version of its AI assistant. &lt;a href="https://www.windowscentral.com/hardware/surface/exclusive-microsoft-will-unveil-oled-surface-pro-10-and-arm-surface-laptop-6-this-month-ahead-of-major-windows-11-ai-update"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Windows Central &lt;/em&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt; that it will catalog everything you do on your PC so you can search for moments in a timeline using natural language. Microsoft tried to bring this same idea to life as a &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2017/5/11/15610612/microsoft-windows-10-timeline-feature"&gt;Timeline feature in Windows 10&lt;/a&gt;, but the lack of app support meant it never really took off and was eventually &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/14/22384316/windows-10-timeline-feature-cortana-sync-ios-android-removed"&gt;removed years later&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093154/microsoft-surface-windows-ai-event-2024"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093154/microsoft-surface-windows-ai-event-2024</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-06T17:27:48-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-06T17:27:48-05:00</updated>
    <title>LinkedIn was down</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A pedestrian walks by a sign at a LinkedIn office on July 26, 2023 in San Francisco, California. LinkedIn announced plans to cut nearly 200 jobs at offices in the San Francisco Bay Area. The cuts follow 700 layoffs earlier in the year." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/3LBNSSG8NdctWAcYrhG1JovTRp0=/13x0:3501x2325/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73187397/1572709127.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Photo by Justin Sullivan/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="IWfWLv"&gt;Just one day after &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091207/meta-outage-facebook-instagram-threads-down-signed-out"&gt;Meta’s network went offline for a while&lt;/a&gt;, LinkedIn was inaccessible around the world, cutting off job listings, resumes, and even influencers. &lt;a href="https://downdetector.com/status/linkedin/"&gt;DownDetector&lt;/a&gt; started noting reports of problems after 3:45PM ET.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="276sVy"&gt;Both the apps and website went offline temporarily, while &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin-status.com/"&gt;LinkedIn’s status page confirmed the issues&lt;/a&gt; with a message posted at 4:04PM ET saying, “Some members may be experiencing issues on LinkedIn. We’re actively working on this and will provide updates as we have them. Thanks for your patience!” As of 5:05PM ET, the most recent message says, “This has now been resolved and we’re back up and running. Apologies for any inconvenience caused and thanks for your patience!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="V3no58"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-conversation="none"&gt;
&lt;p lang="en" dir="ltr"&gt;Sorry about the interruption. We're back up and running.&lt;/p&gt;— LinkedIn Help (@LinkedInHelp) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/LinkedInHelp/status/1765498870815936703?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;March 6, 2024&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="TrNrte"&gt;There’s no sign this problem with the Microsoft-owned social network was connected to Meta’s technical issue on Tuesday or problems elsewhere — no problems were listed with Azure’s cloud or any other services we could spot. The internet connectivity trackers &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/netblocks/status/1765485071664877681"&gt;at NetBlocks&lt;/a&gt; confirmed the outage affected multiple countries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="o2UqNs"&gt;X execs took a victory lap when Andy Stone had to tweet because Threads and Facebook were down yesterday, and again pitched their new hiring pages during this short disruption, but now things are back to normal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dgImXJ"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update March 6th, 5:27PM ET:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; Noted access has been restored.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092667/linkedin-outage-down-error"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092667/linkedin-outage-down-error</id>
    <author>
      <name>Richard Lawler</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-06T11:29:05-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-06T11:29:05-05:00</updated>
    <title>Microsoft AI engineer warns FTC about Copilot Designer safety concerns</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Microsoft logo" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/LONV33IapQjlyYa5CgznAdKR9Uk=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73186401/STK095_Microsoft_04.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Illustration: The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="5bjx6j"&gt;A Microsoft engineer is bringing safety concerns about the company’s AI image generator to the Federal Trade Commission, &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/03/06/microsoft-ai-engineer-says-copilot-designer-creates-disturbing-images.html"&gt;according to a report from CNBC&lt;/a&gt;. Shane Jones, who has worked for Microsoft for six years, wrote a letter to the FTC, stating that Microsoft “refused” to take down Copilot Designer despite repeated warnings that the tool is capable of generating harmful images.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mEeUJz"&gt;When testing Copilot Designer for safety issues and flaws, Jones found that the tool generated “demons and monsters alongside terminology related to abortion rights, teenagers with assault rifles, sexualized images of women in violent tableaus, and underage drinking and drug use,” CNBC reports. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HwRSzU"&gt;Additionally, Copilot Designer reportedly generated images of Disney characters, such as Elsa from &lt;em&gt;Frozen&lt;/em&gt;, in scenes at the Gaza Strip “in front of wrecked buildings and ‘free Gaza’ signs.” It also created images of Elsa wearing an Israel Defense Forces uniform while holding a shield with Israel’s flag. &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt; was able to generate similar images using the tool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="3tq0eO"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Satya Nadella says the explicit Taylor Swift AI fakes are ‘alarming and terrible’ ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/26/24052196/satya-nadella-microsoft-ai-taylor-swift-fakes-response"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="svs29e"&gt;Jones has been trying to warn Microsoft about DALLE-3, the model used by Copilot Designer, since December, CNBC says. He &lt;a href="https://www.geekwire.com/2024/microsoft-ai-engineer-says-company-thwarted-attempt-expose-dall-e-3-safety-problem/"&gt;posted an open letter&lt;/a&gt; about the issues on LinkedIn, but he was reportedly contacted by Microsoft’s legal team to remove the post, which he did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="FRMu4v"&gt;“Over the last three months, I have repeatedly urged Microsoft to remove Copilot Designer from public use until better safeguards could be put in place,” Jones wrote in the letter obtained by CNBC. “Again, they have failed to implement these changes and continue to market the product to ‘Anyone. Anywhere. Any Device.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="rsKmvD"&gt;In a statement to &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;, Microsoft spokesperson Frank Shaw says the company is “committed to addressing any and all concerns employees have in accordance with” Microsoft’s policies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="9RzzDB"&gt;“When it comes to safety bypasses or concerns that could have a potential impact on our services or our partners, we have established in-product user feedback tools and robust internal reporting channels to properly investigate, prioritize and remediate any issues, which we recommended that the employee utilize so we could appropriately validate and test his concerns.” Shaw also says that Microsoft has “facilitated meetings with product leadership and our Office of Responsible AI to review these reports.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="q0AzkT"&gt;In January, Jones wrote to a group of US senators about his concerns after &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/25/24050334/x-twitter-taylor-swift-ai-fake-images-trending"&gt;Copilot Designer generated&lt;/a&gt; explicit images of Taylor Swift, which spread rapidly across X. Microsoft CEO &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/26/24052196/satya-nadella-microsoft-ai-taylor-swift-fakes-response"&gt;Satya Nadella called the images&lt;/a&gt; “alarming and terrible” and said the company would work on adding more safety guardrails. Last month, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/22/24079876/google-gemini-ai-photos-people-pause"&gt;Google temporarily disabled&lt;/a&gt; its own AI image generator when users found that it created pictures of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/21/24079371/google-ai-gemini-generative-inaccurate-historical"&gt;racially diverse Nazis&lt;/a&gt; and other historically inaccurate images.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="99umKs"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update March 6th, 6:09PM ET: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Added a statement from Microsoft.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092191/microsoft-ai-engineer-copilot-designer-ftc-safety-concerns"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092191/microsoft-ai-engineer-copilot-designer-ftc-safety-concerns</id>
    <author>
      <name>Emma Roth</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
