<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>The Verge -  Entertainments</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/community_logos/52801/VER_Logomark_32x32..png</icon>
  <updated>2024-03-15T14:18:31-04:00</updated>
  <id>https://www.theverge.com/rss/entertainment/index.xml</id>
  <link type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/entertainment" rel="alternate"/>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T14:18:31-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T14:18:31-04:00</updated>
    <title>PC games start at just $1 in Steam’s spring sale</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/QxhWt9VzPWr3GQZCuEydQvH9L-8=/0x0:920x613/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73210131/steam_spring_sale_2024.0.png" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;From AAA blockbusters to indie cult classics, there are tons of games up to 95 percent off.&lt;/em&gt; | Valve / Steam&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="g0AV6L"&gt;You’d think most gamers would have indulged enough over the long winter season that they wouldn’t want to spend the first moments of spring doing the same, but rainy days are still a thing, yeah? And the grind never truly stops for many of us. That’s why I can appreciate the &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steam spring sale&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, happening now through March 21st. It happens around this time every year and offers up to 90 percent off thousands of titles. You can find deals on game-of-the-year-worthy titles like &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1086940/Baldurs_Gate_3/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Baldur’s Gate 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; for $53.99&lt;/a&gt; ($6 off), for example, while &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2344520/Diablo_IV/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diablo IV&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is 50 percent off&lt;/a&gt; no matter which version you buy, whether it’s the base game going for $34.99 or the &lt;em&gt;Ultimate Edition&lt;/em&gt; for $49.99.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="aPUdPk"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"10 great Windows PC games from 2023 ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23979457/best-windows-pc-games-2023"},{"title":"Steam Deck OLED review: better, not faster ","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23951655/steam-deck-oled-review"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="MORknD"&gt;It’s also a great chance to check out older titles you may have passed on, such as &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/1091500/Cyberpunk_2077/?snr=1_4_springsale__629"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cyberpunk 2077&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (50 percent off, down to $29.99) or &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/2369390/Far_Cry_6/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Far Cry 6&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for $14.99 ($45 off). There are tons of cult classics, indie hits, and other low-key titles on sale starting at just $1, too, like the undying &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/550/Left_4_Dead_2/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Left 4 Dead 2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. We’re not seeing any discounts on the &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/steamdeck/"&gt;Steam Deck&lt;/a&gt; or any of the VR headsets in &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/vrhardware/"&gt;Steam’s hardware store&lt;/a&gt;, unfortunately, but be sure to explore more games from the sale if you’re looking for something new to play.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="cuowaA"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12193366"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="YOuFUD"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:12193982"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="O8BIEr"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10197689"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="BoKVbF"&gt;Considering &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24089999/apple-macbook-air-m3-announced-13-15-inch"&gt;Apple has officially signaled the M1 MacBook Air’s death knell&lt;/a&gt;, Walmart’s latest sale on the outgoing model feels like a last call. The retailer is offloading the &lt;strong&gt;8GB RAM, 256GB SSD MacBook Air with M1&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/482924/565706/9383?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fip%2FApple-MacBook-Air-13-3-inch-Laptop-Space-Gray-M1-Chip-8GB-RAM-256GB-storage%2F609040889&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;$699&lt;/a&gt;, which is $300 off compared to its original price and $50 cheaper than the $749 it’s often gone for toward the end of its retail run. It’s a new all-time low price, which we predicted would happen, but perhaps not this soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="MWFMry"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Apple’s new M3 chips have big GPU upgrades focused on gaming and pro apps","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2023/10/30/23938676/apple-m3-chip-gpu-upgrade-hardware-accelerated-ray-tracing-gaming-specs-release-date"},{"title":"The MacBook Air’s wedge is truly gone — and I miss it already","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24090112/macbook-air-wedge-laptops-design"},{"title":"Look at this bonkers, beautiful Mac-iPad hybrid","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24090192/look-at-this-bonkers-beautiful-mac-ipad-hybrid"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="T3p1Cm"&gt;Although it’s discontinued, the M1 Air is still getting support and can still serve as a perfectly capable laptop for someone dipping their toes into the MacBook waters for the first time, or perhaps to replace an aging Intel-based model. It’s up to most basic school, work, and browsing tasks for those with lighter needs who would benefit from the long battery life (up to 18 hours) and power efficiency afforded by the Apple-made chipset. I’ve even found this memory-starved model capable of lightweight 4K video editing, photo editing, and other creative tasks. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="4RwrHd"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:9737407"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="gKBJ9y"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="actionbox" data-anthem-component-data='{"title":"Verge Deals on X","description":"Join more than 50,000 followers and keep up with the best daily tech deals with @vergedeals","label":"Follow us!","url":"http://bit.ly/2JzR5Ud"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;h2 id="6DvR1d"&gt;A few more ways to save&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="LzC9S2"&gt;The keyboard has become something of a fashion statement on the modern desk, and&lt;strong&gt; 8Bitdo’s wireless retro mechanical keyboard &lt;/strong&gt;— down to $84.99 ($15 off) at &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CCP8KYGG/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; — offers a distinct look resembling a Super Nintendo for those who favor a nostalgic aesthetic&lt;strong&gt;. &lt;/strong&gt;The tenkeyless board offers both 2.4GHz and Bluetooth wireless connectivity options (in addition to wired), an integrated volume knob, and ships with two oversized buttons that you can program to execute your favorite macros and other custom functions. The hot-swappable PCB allows you to switch out the Kailh Box V2 switches with ease, too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="UsUAyM"&gt;If you own a Samsung Galaxy smartphone and you need an alternative to AirTags, it’s worth considering a&lt;strong&gt; four-pack of Galaxy SmartTag2 trackers. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://howl.me/clP25RGFVQ5"&gt;Samsung has it down to $74.99&lt;/a&gt; ($25 off). Similar to Apple’s version, SmartTag2 uses Bluetooth ultra-wideband for pinpoint compass-guided directions to your lost items. That functionality requires a&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Galaxy Note 20 Ultra, S21 Plus and Ultra or newer, or a Galaxy Z Fold 2 and newer, although you can use any Samsung phone with SmartThings Find to track down the last known location. The battery can last up to 500 days and up to 40 percent longer in a low-power state, Samsung says, and the trackers can survive a bit of rain or dust with IP67 protection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="R4Byuf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22958216/kitchen-tools-personal-gear-gadgets-favorites"&gt;favorite&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;’s Allison Johnson, the &lt;strong&gt;Breville Barista Express&lt;/strong&gt; is an attractive and versatile espresso machine that &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Breville-BES870XL-Barista-Express-Espresso/dp/B00DS4767K/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clP4iJVM1gt"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://westelm.e54b.net/c/482924/267856/4336?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.williams-sonoma.com%2Fproducts%2F2101673%2F&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Williams Sonoma&lt;/a&gt; have down to $559.99 right now ($140 off). It grinds its own beans at whichever consistency you desire and has an integrated microfoaming milk frother, both helping to make delectable cups of the good stuff with a presentation that will make you forget all about those expensive Starbies runs. It’s also easy to clean and maintain, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/10/23864688/breville-barista-express-home-espresso-maintenance"&gt;says Allison&lt;/a&gt;, whether you’re using its self-cleaning option or opening it up for a deep scrub.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="7enZCU"&gt;If you’re looking for a flagship-rivaling smartphone that simply does exactly what you need it to, we see nothing wrong with the &lt;strong&gt;OnePlus 12R.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s already a great value at $499.99 for the unlocked 128GB storage model, and both &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0CW9R75NB/?tag=theverge02-20" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Amazon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://howl.me/clP3JT0Cvjg"&gt;Best Buy&lt;/a&gt; are throwing in a $100 gift card to sweeten the deal. We wish it had wireless charging and more substantial ingress protection compared to midrange contemporaries from Samsung and Google. Otherwise, it’s hard to find a smartphone at this price with its display quality and size (the 6.78-inch, 1080p display has a 120Hz variable refresh rate), not to mention its respectable photography potential and the strong processing power of the Snapdragon 8 Gen 2. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24072383/oneplus-12r-review-screen-camera-price"&gt;Read our review&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;aside id="aSZQAL"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="newsletter" data-anthem-component-data='{"slug":"deals"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101003/steam-spring-sale-m1-macbook-air-breville-barista-express-espresso-machine-deal-sale"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101003/steam-spring-sale-m1-macbook-air-breville-barista-express-espresso-machine-deal-sale</id>
    <author>
      <name>Quentyn Kennemer</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T11:29:48-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T11:29:48-04:00</updated>
    <title>Doctor Who’s new season streams in May</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="A man wearing a leather trench coat, a striped blue and white shirt with a deep neck, and baggy trousers. Next to the man is a woman wearing a leather bomber jacket, a cardigan skirt, black stockings, and leather boos. Both the man and the woman are leaning on opposite sides of a circular hallway of what seems to be a spaceship." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/zwoH4OkFRdsxxMNiwOVCsWOXn5w=/0x0:2000x1333/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209592/jpp_who_170623_0005_embargoed_15_6415cf64.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Ncuti Gatwa as The Doctor, and Millie Gibson as Ruby Sunday. | BBC / Disney Plus&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="vmHrGh"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/10/25/23422663/doctor-who-disney-plus-bbc-streaming-announcement"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Doctor Who&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;’s most recent Christmas Special gave us a interesting taste of what showrunner Russell T Davies has been dreaming up for &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/12/23996697/doctor-who-the-giggle-bigeneration"&gt;Ncuti Gatwa’s run as the time traveling alien&lt;/a&gt;, and it won’t be long until we get to see what’s coming next.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZKCoyF"&gt;Disney Plus announced today that &lt;em&gt;Doctor Who &lt;/em&gt;season 14 starring Ncuti Gatwa as the Fifteenth Doctor and Millie Gibson as his companion Ruby Sunday will premiere with two new episodes on May 10th in the US and internationally, except for the United Kingdom. UK viewers will be able to stream the new episodes via BBC iPlayer beginning at 12AM on May 11th (GMT) before it is available on BBC One later in the day. In &lt;a href="https://thewaltdisneycompany.com/doctor-who-debut-disney-plus/"&gt;a press release&lt;/a&gt; about the new season, Davies teased that the Doctor and Ruby’s adventures will involve “a terrifying secret that’s been spanning time and space for decades.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="T0xbhF"&gt;News of the premiere date comes months after news broke that, after starring in the show for just a single season, Gibson is already set to be replaced by actress Varada Sethu as the Doctor’s companion for reasons that have not been made clear.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101820/doctor-who-season-14-ncuti-gatwa-millie-gibson-premiere-date"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101820/doctor-who-season-14-ncuti-gatwa-millie-gibson-premiere-date</id>
    <author>
      <name>Charles Pulliam-Moore</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T10:58:12-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T10:58:12-04:00</updated>
    <title>FCC clamps down on confusing ‘hidden fees’ in your cable TV bill</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Dollars float through pillars, as if to exit a bank" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/9zq22Yj8b76DwgrNB9z3hVeOpjk=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209464/STK417_H_Herrera_Money_03.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The ruling aims to make it easier to accurately compare subscription prices against other providers.&lt;/em&gt; | Illustration by Hugo Herrera / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="aT5hLP"&gt;Cable and satellite TV providers will need to ensure they show the total price of subscription plans as a “prominent single line item” — including costs described as extra fees — under a rule adopted by the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) on Thursday. The FCC says the &lt;a href="https://docs.fcc.gov/public/attachments/DOC-401215A1.pdf"&gt;new rule (pdf)&lt;/a&gt; for “all-in” pricing will make it easier for customers to compare prices against competing providers and streaming services by eliminating the “misleading practice of describing video programming costs as a tax, fee, or surcharge.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="ZPotRN"&gt;“No one likes surprises on their bill,” said FCC Chairwoman Jessica Rosenworcel in a &lt;a href="https://docs.fcc.gov/public/attachments/DOC-401215A2.pdf"&gt;separate statement (pdf)&lt;/a&gt;. “The advertised price for a service should be the price you pay when your bill arrives. It shouldn’t include a bunch of unexpected junk fees that are separate from the top-line price you were told when you signed up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="YWD5CF"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="twitter-tweet"&gt;
&lt;p lang="en" dir="ltr"&gt;TV providers often use deceptive junk fees to hide real prices. We are putting an end to this form of price masking by requiring cable &amp;amp; satellite TV providers to clearly specify the “all-in” price for video programming in their promotional materials &amp;amp; on subscribers’ bills.&lt;/p&gt;— The FCC (@FCC) &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/FCC/status/1768332803123352045?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw"&gt;March 14, 2024&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="rfheLa"&gt;The new rules for transparent pricing on video programming will apply to both subscribers’ bills and promotional materials. The FCC says that companies often obscure certain costs and fees, which “causes significant and costly confusion for consumers.” The Commission has also proposed eliminating early termination fees issued by cable and satellite TV providers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="An example of a Comcast bill showing a breakdown of additional fees and charges." data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/dkJt0t_vrgpf8nwiZgRbNl0P23Q=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25337693/HOW11878_092623_03.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Comcast Xfinity&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Bills like this &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="ql-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=66960X1514734&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.xfinity.com%2Fsupport%2Farticles%2Fnew-bill-design&amp;amp;referrer=theverge.com&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.theverge.com%2F2024%2F3%2F15%2F24101802%2Fcable-tv-bill-fee-satellite-tv-providers-subscription-price-fcc" target="_blank" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;example&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; from Comcast will be required to clearly display the total price, including the extra fees and charges.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="3emTKd"&gt;Forcing companies to display their subscription prices more clearly might be a relief to consumers who are sick of being surprised by unexpected additional fees, but cable providers like &lt;a href="https://www.fcc.gov/ecfs/document/10307141821162/1"&gt;Comcast, Cox, and Charter&lt;/a&gt; have argued that it’s unnecessary. The Internet &amp;amp; Television Association (NCTA) called the ruling “misguided” and claims it will only cause further confusion. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="N00PoO"&gt;“Cable providers offer clear and accurate pricing information to attract and retain subscribers, including ‘all-in’ pricing information before signing up for service,” &lt;a href="https://www.ncta.com/media/media-room/statements-of-ncta-the-internet-television-association-regarding-actions-at-todays-fcc-meeting"&gt;the NCTA said&lt;/a&gt; in response to the ruling. “The FCC’s micromanagement of advertising in today’s hyper-competitive marketplace will force operators to either clutter their ads with confusing disclosures or leave pricing information out entirely.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="AlnDKE"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclosure: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Comcast is an investor in Vox Media, &lt;/em&gt;The Verge&lt;em&gt;’s parent company.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101802/cable-tv-bill-fee-satellite-tv-providers-subscription-price-fcc"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/15/24101802/cable-tv-bill-fee-satellite-tv-providers-subscription-price-fcc</id>
    <author>
      <name>Jess Weatherbed</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-15T10:13:33-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T10:13:33-04:00</updated>
    <title>Are we really going to ban TikTok?</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="An illustration depicting TikTok over the Vergecast team." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/EHwDyc3uJH6WLplmQFPcGzu815k=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73209314/VST_0315_Site.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Alex Parkin / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="tv0Uat"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23651507/tiktok-ban-us-news"&gt;The TikTok ban&lt;/a&gt; might be for real this time. Nearly &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/9/22525953/biden-tiktok-wechat-trump-bans-revoked-alipay"&gt;four years after&lt;/a&gt; the first attempt to get the ByteDance-owned company either sold or barred from the US, a new bill is &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24097125/house-bill-vote-tiktok-ban-china-bytedance-divestment"&gt;flying through congressional votes&lt;/a&gt;, and President Joe Biden has already &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/9/24095348/president-biden-says-hell-sign-a-tiktok-ban-if-passed"&gt;said he’ll sign it&lt;/a&gt; if it comes to his desk. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="oEfzyZ"&gt;On &lt;a href="https://pod.link/vergecast"&gt;this episode of &lt;em&gt;The Vergecast&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we talk about what’s inside the Protecting Americans From Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act (everybody calls it PAFFACAA, just kidding; nobody calls it that, everybody just calls it “The TikTok Ban”) and what we know about TikTok’s connection to China. The answer: not a lot! But four years in, Congress seems more convinced than ever, and that might mean something. Or it might not. We spend a long time debating what that means.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="QkZrXb"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://player.megaphone.fm/VMP6905517148" style="border: 0; width: 100%; height: 200px;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="NC84Mv"&gt;After that, we discuss &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24097247/former-activision-ceo-bobby-kotick-is-apparently-eyeing-tiktok"&gt;who might buy TikTok&lt;/a&gt;, whether TikTok is even for sale, and what companies like Meta, Snap, and X stand to gain from a TikTok ban. And finally, we try to decide which outcome is the most likely: a TikTok ban, a TikTok sale, or nothing at all?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="bIpyw8"&gt;Once we dispense with the TikTok news, we talk about &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099533/youtube-tv-app-redesign-comments-shopping"&gt;YouTube’s new redesign for TVs&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099337/spotify-music-video-beta-11-markets-supported-artists"&gt;Spotify’s push into music videos&lt;/a&gt; — which are both, in a way, actually stories about TikTok. Neil Young &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099330/neil-youngs-music-is-back-on-low-res-spotify-two-years-after-rogan-protest"&gt;makes a surprise reappearance&lt;/a&gt; on the show, and then it’s time for a lightning round. Brought to you by your favorite new band, Algorithmic Warfare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="RNEOJ6"&gt;
&lt;div data-analytics-viewport="video" data-analytics-action="volume:view:article:middle" data-analytics-label="Are we really about to ban TikTok? | The Vergecast|115759" data-volume-uuid="5f55831ed" data-volume-id="115759" data-analytics-placement="article:middle" data-volume-placement="article" data-volume-autoplay="false" id="volume-placement-365" class="volume-video" data-volume-player-choice="youtube"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="ehBTgI"&gt;If you want to read more on everything we covered in this show (there’s a lot!), here are a few links to get you started, first on TikTok:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="X9g3CD"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23651507/tiktok-ban-us-news"&gt;TikTok ban: all the news on attempts to ban the video platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="UecVfE"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091278/congress-tiktok-bytedance-ban-divest-bill"&gt;Lawmakers introduce bill that would punish app stores for hosting TikTok&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="ImCUQS"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24097125/house-bill-vote-tiktok-ban-china-bytedance-divestment"&gt;House passes bill that could ban TikTok&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="edg1nD"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/9/24095348/president-biden-says-hell-sign-a-tiktok-ban-if-passed"&gt;President Biden says he’ll sign a TikTok ban, if passed.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="r5wMDh"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099721/tiktok-ban-senate-house-vote-divest-bill"&gt;TikTok’s fate now lies with the Senate after House advances path to a ban&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="G3QQB8"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24100175/tiktok-ceo-tells-users-to-make-their-voices-heard-against-a-bill-that-could-ban-the-app-in-the-us"&gt;TikTok CEO tells users to “make their voices heard” against a bill that could ban the app in the US.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="kf72JW"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099896/nancy-pelosi-is-playing-tiktok-toe"&gt;Nancy Pelosi is playing TikTok-toe.&lt;/a&gt; (Ditto)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="wNhx2Q"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24097416/donald-trump-has-even-more-to-say-about-the-tiktok-ban"&gt;Donald Trump has even more to say about the TikTok ban.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="KwvrGU"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093308/tiktok-congress-ban-push-notification"&gt;TikTok is urging users to call Congress about a looming ban&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="dh31N5"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093490/the-tiktokers-are-revolting"&gt;The TikTokers are revolting.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="c1Y3br"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/11/24097247/former-activision-ceo-bobby-kotick-is-apparently-eyeing-tiktok"&gt;Former Activision CEO Bobby Kotick is apparently eyeing TikTok.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="0VNlCO"&gt;And on the streaming news of the week:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="pf24W5"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099533/youtube-tv-app-redesign-comments-shopping"&gt;YouTube is revamping its TV app to make videos feel way more interactive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="KYLE54"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099337/spotify-music-video-beta-11-markets-supported-artists"&gt;Spotify now has music videos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Zt6Hg4"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099330/neil-youngs-music-is-back-on-low-res-spotify-two-years-after-rogan-protest"&gt;Neil Young’s music is back on “low res Spotify” two years after Rogan protest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="akgRDV"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099677/don-lemon-elon-musk-x-canceled"&gt;Elon Musk cancels Don Lemon’s show on X after a ‘tense’ interview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="kCPQNp"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/lindayaX/status/1767675796334776506"&gt;Linda Yaccarino on X: “X is becoming a video first platform&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="ezAObe"&gt;And in the lightning round:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li id="QB4zvj"&gt;Alex Cranz’s pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/10/24096762/kate-middleton-edited-photo-royal-family-possible-fake"&gt;British monarchy rocked by bad Photoshop job&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="jcG1Xn"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098548/kate-middleton-royal-family-photoshop-manipulated-image"&gt;The Kate Middleton photo scandal is a rare — and consequential — flub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="DrwqJQ"&gt;Nilay Patel’s pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100501/spacex-starship-launch-third-flight-test-success"&gt;SpaceX successfully launches Starship in third flight test&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Te7A5S"&gt;David Pierce’s pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098334/apple-ios-web-distribution-eu-app-store-changes"&gt;Apple to allow iOS app downloads direct from websites in the EU&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="YNDPUb"&gt;Alex’s second pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/24098771/dyson-vis-nav-robot-vacuum-hands-on"&gt;Hands-on with the Dyson 360 Vis Nav robot vacuum&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="ICMx6J"&gt;David’s second pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/13/24099723/microsoft-teams-unified-app-personal-work-accounts"&gt;Microsoft Teams is finally moving to a single app for personal and work&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li id="Zwysf2"&gt;Nilay’s second pick: &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/7/24093109/nikon-acquiring-red-cameras-film-motion-picture-tv"&gt;Nikon is acquiring US camera manufacturer RED&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="seBzTK"&gt;We’re really curious to hear what you think about the TikTok ban in particular. As always, you can get in touch with us by emailing vergecast@theverge.com, calling the &lt;em&gt;Vergecast&lt;/em&gt; Hotline at +1-866-VERGE11, or hitting us up on Threads. Or TikTok! For now.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24101704/tiktok-ban-kate-middleton-photoshop-vergecast-podcast"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24101704/tiktok-ban-kate-middleton-photoshop-vergecast-podcast</id>
    <author>
      <name>David Pierce</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T16:59:33-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T16:59:33-04:00</updated>
    <title>Max annual plans are up to $60 off ahead of March Madness  </title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Vector illustration of the Max logo." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/nIhT008fRnnm_CL_TM6prj6eEZw=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73207822/STK055_HBOMAX__C.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;With Max, you can stream sports as well as shows and movies like &lt;/em&gt;Wonka&lt;em&gt; and &lt;/em&gt;The Last of Us&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; | Image: Cath Virginia / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="AiyXgM"&gt;Whether you’re looking for cheap cable-free ways to watch the NCAA championship games or are simply worried about Max’s &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091397/max-password-sharing-crackdown-netflix"&gt;forthcoming password-sharing crackdown&lt;/a&gt;, today’s Max deal arrives at the perfect time. Right now, Max is taking an additional 30 percent off of its annual subscription for one year, for a total 40 percent discount compared to the cost of a monthly subscription. The annual plans start at &lt;a href="https://max.prf.hn/click/camref:1101lqHRA/pubref:Verge/ar:MM031524/destination:https%3A%2F%2Fauth.max.com%2Fproduct"&gt;$69.99 ($30)&lt;/a&gt;, which is like paying $5.83 per month, but you can go ad-free for &lt;a href="https://max.prf.hn/click/camref:1101lqHRA/pubref:Verge/ar:MM031524/destination:https%3A%2F%2Fauth.max.com%2Fproduct"&gt;$104.99 ($50 off&lt;/a&gt;) while the Max Ultimate Ad-Free tier is down to &lt;a href="https://max.prf.hn/click/camref:1101lqHRA/pubref:Verge/ar:MM031524/destination:https%3A%2F%2Fauth.max.com%2Fproduct"&gt;$139.99 ($60 off)&lt;/a&gt;. Even better, new, returning, and existing subscribers are eligible for this deal, so everybody can save.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="1l5OEK"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Sonos soundbars and speakers are on sale just in time for March Madness","url":"https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100247/sonos-ray-beam-sub-mini-move-2-march-madness-deal-sale"},{"title":"Release dates and trailers for the biggest streaming movies and TV shows in 2024","url":"https://www.theverge.com/24065499/netflix-disney-plus-max-release-date-trailer-streaming-calendar"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="3ez4vP"&gt;The main difference between the plans is that the ad-free tiers let you download content for offline viewing. The Ultimate Ad-Free plan also lets you stream select content in 4K UHD with Dolby Atmos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="0L6lDA"&gt;Otherwise, all three annual plans let you stream the 2024 NCAA Division I Men’s Basketball Championship live games as well as access Max’s vast collection of shows and movies. That include hits like &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/23/24080871/wonka-starts-streaming-on-max-next-month"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wonka&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Euphoria&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/22737214/dune-review-hbo-max-denis-villeneuve-timothee-chalamet-sandworm"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dune&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23543145/hbo-the-last-of-us-review"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Last of Us&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23799181/barbie-review-mattel-warner-bros-greta-gerwig"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Barbie&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; as well as forthcoming presentations like Oscar-winning film &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/12/24098639/the-boy-and-the-heron-will-soon-stream-on-max"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Boy and the Heron&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and the next season of &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091101/house-of-the-dragon-sounds-like-its-coming-back-in-june"&gt;&lt;em&gt;House of the Dragon&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="gdkbv0"&gt;Just make sure to mark your calendars, though; the deal ends April 9th, and you’ll be charged the full price when your subscription comes up for renewal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="m26rua"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="productcard:10286290"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;aside id="iZhusS"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="newsletter" data-anthem-component-data='{"slug":"deals"}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100899/max-march-madness-the-boy-and-the-heron-deal-sale"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100899/max-march-madness-the-boy-and-the-heron-deal-sale</id>
    <author>
      <name>Sheena Vasani</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T16:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T16:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Spotify says its iPhone app updates in the EU are getting held up by Apple</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="An illustration of Spotify’s logo." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/7kLZIck-Zl86M-MPHm-Pkhb8JxU=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73207641/STK088_VRG_Illo_N_Barclay_5_spotify.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Nick Barclay / The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="an6zpV"&gt;Even after Apple was &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24005938/european-commission-antitrust-apple-investigation-anti-steering-rules-app-developers"&gt;hit with a $2 billion fine&lt;/a&gt; in the European Union over years-old complaints from Spotify about its App Store rules, Spotify says Apple is stonewalling updates issued in compliance with that very ruling. In an email to the European Commission obtained by &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;, Spotify writes that Apple has “neither acknowledged nor responded to Spotify’s submission” to bring subscription pricing information into the app, preventing it from updating the app at all for its users, even to put out fixes for bugs or add other features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="nnqpm9"&gt;On March 5th, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/5/24091430/spotify-links-pricing-information-iphone-eu-app"&gt;Spotify submitted an update&lt;/a&gt; to Apple that puts links to Spotify’s website, along with pricing information for different subscription options, directly in the EU version of its app, without using Apple’s payment system. Spotify made the change in response to a ruling issued the day before &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24005938/european-commission-antitrust-apple-investigation-anti-steering-rules-app-developers"&gt;by the European Commission&lt;/a&gt;, which said Apple’s anti-steering rules are “illegal” and ordered Apple to start allowing developers to include information about “alternative and cheaper music subscription services.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3y1hBP"&gt;Apple &lt;a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/the-app-store-spotify-and-europes-thriving-digital-music-market/"&gt;responded to the decision on March 4th&lt;/a&gt; by saying it would appeal and pointing out a list of “ways Apple creates value for Spotify, at no cost to their company,” which happened to include this bullet point:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p id="3pn1gv"&gt;Our App Review team has reviewed and approved 421 versions of the Spotify app — usually with same-day turnaround — and frequently expedites reviews at Spotify’s request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/PMaxOBwwuXdPYaT2YS_MvBleYhk=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25336218/DMA_Media_Stills_2__1_.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Spotify&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spotify’s update includes pricing information and links to subscriptions.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="ueCClH"&gt;In the email, Spotify says it hasn’t heard back from Apple since submitting the update.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="MWfdMD"&gt;The company writes that this is “yet another example of how Apple if unchecked, will seek to circumvent and/or not comply with the Commission’s decision.” It also urges the European Commission to contact Apple and requires that it approve Spotify’s changes. “Given Apple’s track record, Spotify is concerned that Apple’s delay is intentional and is aimed at delaying or avoiding compliance altogether,” the email reads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dTlXmI"&gt;“It’s been nine days now and we’re still waiting to hear from Apple about our app submission to show EU consumers pricing and a link to our website, which we are now authorized to do by the European Commission’s decision on the music streaming case,” Spotify spokesperson Jeanne Moran says in an emailed statement to &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;. “Apple’s delay directly conflicts with its claim that they turn around reviews on app submissions within 24 hours, and it also flies in the face of the timeline for adoption the Commission laid out.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Q1fHHM"&gt;Apple didn’t provide a comment in response to a request from &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="Yzf5jU"&gt;This ruling is separate from the &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24091592/eu-dma-competition-compliance-deadline-big-tech-policy-changes"&gt;EU’s Digital Markets Act&lt;/a&gt; (DMA) regulations for big tech platforms that have only been around for about a week, but the European Commission has already intervened in response to one of Apple’s DMA-related decisions. Earlier this month, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/6/24092158/epic-apple-developer-account-terminated-digital-markets-act-alternative-ios-app-store"&gt;Apple revoked Epic Games’ developer license&lt;/a&gt; because of criticism CEO Tim Sweeney made about Apple’s DMA compliance plan. Epic Games &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/8/24094543/epic-games-ios-developer-license-apple-dma"&gt;got its developer license back days later&lt;/a&gt;, citing “a swift inquiry” from the European Commission.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100944/spotify-ios-app-update-eu-apple-dma"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100944/spotify-ios-app-update-eu-apple-dma</id>
    <author>
      <name>Emma Roth</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T14:40:52-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T14:40:52-04:00</updated>
    <title>Netflix is bringing back Black Mirror in 2025</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Annie Murphy in Black Mirror" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/xipD6xdQwNz8P99sJpSWES4JNGo=/149x0:1274x750/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73207440/black_mirror_s6.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Netflix&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="NYk6Ic"&gt;A seventh season of &lt;em&gt;Black Mirror&lt;/em&gt; is on the way. Netflix has confirmed that Charlie Brooker’s sci-fi anthology will return in 2025 and that the new season will be six episodes long.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="NzxdmR"&gt;There aren’t many details yet, of course. But the company does say that, while it’ll otherwise consist of new stories, one of the episodes will be a sequel to “&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/USS_Callister"&gt;USS Callister&lt;/a&gt;” from season 4, which starred Jesse Plemons. “Robert Daly is dead, but for the crew of the USS Callister, their problems are just beginning,” the description reads.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="Hr7CP7"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data='{"stories":[{"title":"Black Mirror season 6: exploring Netflix’s sci-fi anthology, one episode at a time","url":"https://www.theverge.com/23760609/black-mirror-season-6-episode-reviews"}]}'&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="fVFXPr"&gt;The show’s return will mark a relatively brief hiatus, at least by &lt;em&gt;Black Mirror&lt;/em&gt; standards. &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23760609/black-mirror-season-6-episode-reviews"&gt;Season 6 premiered last year&lt;/a&gt; and included some strong episodes, covering everything from &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/6/15/23761949/black-mirror-season-six-beyond-the-sea-aaron-paul-josh-hartnett-review"&gt;space-themed horror&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23763326/black-mirror-mazey-day-review-season-6-netflix"&gt;a paparazzi thriller&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/23763339/black-mirrors-joan-is-awful-netflix-future-streaming"&gt;a satire of the future of streaming&lt;/a&gt; that proved &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/13/23794224/sag-aftra-actors-strike-ai-image-rights"&gt;all too prescient&lt;/a&gt;. So while we don’t know yet what exactly the new episodes will cover, it’s a safe bet more recent tech stories like AI and the metaverse might provide some inspiration.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24101013/black-mirror-season-7-netflix-date-trailer"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24101013/black-mirror-season-7-netflix-date-trailer</id>
    <author>
      <name>Andrew Webster</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T13:23:03-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T13:23:03-04:00</updated>
    <title>Wooting built the best gaming keyboard — now a new model introduces ‘Rappy Snappy’</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="The Wooting 80HE keyboard" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/G_5YNOpBUc59F6CuURAT8UOhqcQ=/112x0:1215x735/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73207223/uBM9Fi.0.png" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Wooting&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="qvcR4C"&gt;Wooting’s 60HE is widely regarded as one of the best, if not &lt;em&gt;the &lt;/em&gt;best, gaming keyboard on the market. That’s all thanks to &lt;a href="https://wooting.io/rapid-trigger"&gt;Rapid Trigger&lt;/a&gt;, a feature that speeds up how quickly you can activate a key to respond in games like &lt;em&gt;Valorant &lt;/em&gt;or &lt;em&gt;Counter-Strike 2&lt;/em&gt;. Now, Wooting is &lt;a href="https://wooting.io/wooting-80he"&gt;launching the 80HE&lt;/a&gt;, a larger keyboard with an 80 percent layout. It comes with a new “Rappy Snappy” feature that combines with Rapid Trigger to make it even faster to pull off moves like strafing and bunny hopping in games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="HAmwdi"&gt;“Rappy Snappy is our new spin on Rapid Trigger, so it compares two keys together and the one that gets pressed the furthest is prioritized,” explains Wooting CEO Calder Limmen. “You could, for example, use it on your A and D keys to make counter strafing more snappier.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="BEoFub"&gt;&lt;div style="left: 0; width: 100%; height: 0; position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%;"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uz9pTOLbeos?rel=0" style="top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute; border: 0;" allowfullscreen="" scrolling="no" allow="accelerometer; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share;"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="o6QgyE"&gt;If Rappy Snappy and Rapid Trigger aren’t already fast enough, Wooting is also using what it calls a “true” 8KHz polling rate on the 80HE, which should allow it to report keypresses to a computer eight times faster than a typical keyboard. (You’ll find a similar feature on Razer’s recent &lt;a href="https://razer.a9yw.net/c/482924/642901/10229?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.razer.com%2Fgb-en%2Fgaming-keyboards%2Frazer-blackwidow-v4-75&amp;amp;sharedid=theverge.com" rel="sponsored nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;BlackWidow V4 75&lt;/a&gt;.) And just like the 60HE, you’ll also have adjustable actuation to control the keypress travel before key activation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="2JNaqd"&gt;Everyone had been asking Wooting to make a tenkeyless (TKL) keyboard with its Rapid Trigger feature that SteelSeries, &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/5/23989237/keychron-q1-he-hall-effect-analog-switches-price-release-date-specs-features-mechanical-keyboard"&gt;Keychron&lt;/a&gt;, and others have copied, but the company decided to go with the slightly more compact 80 percent layout instead. Compared to the 60HE, the 80HE offers an F row, arrow keys, and a cluster of keys that includes delete, page up / down, insert, pause, and print screen.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/xc6sQ3WJ2r_1FfcEu-h36znyhys=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25336025/rmmtkS.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Wooting&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Wooting 80HE is very much an 80 percent keyboard and not a TKL.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="43AFSB"&gt;The Wooting 80HE will ship in ANSI, ISO, and even JIS layouts, with the option to pick between a PCR plastic case and a more expensive zinc alloy. It’s all mounted on a silicone gasket mount that should improve both the sound and feel of typing. You can also configure your own “Module” variant, with the option to pick between Lekker linear 45 and 60 switches or Gateron’s Jade switches. Wooting will also supply double-shot keycaps or etched ABS ones if you don’t want to use your own set.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="KIo0zC"&gt;The base PCR version is priced at $200, including keycaps and switches. If you step up to the zinc alloy version, then that’s $300, and prices for the Module version start at $185.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="eYM7mm"&gt;Wooting is opening a “Founders’ Campaign” for the 80HE today, allowing anyone interested in the keyboard to preorder one within 31 days to receive a free switch pack, a unique Discord role, and your name on the 80HE page. At the time of writing, more than 6,000 orders have been placed and more than €2.1 million (about $2.3 million) raised. Wooting is expecting to deliver the first batch of 80HE keyboards in August.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100819/wooting-80he-keyboard-rappy-snappy-feature"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100819/wooting-80he-keyboard-rappy-snappy-feature</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T11:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T11:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>Intel’s new Core i9-14900KS arrives today for $689 with boosts up to 6.2GHz</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Illustration of Intel’s new Core i9-14900KS processor" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/PHc_3J6safkIuOFAOCOs5LKhf1w=/267x0:2195x1285/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73206666/14900ks.0.jpeg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Image: Intel&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p id="HEuPlJ"&gt;Intel is launching its flagship Core i9-14900KS processor today, with clock speeds that boost all the way up to 6.2GHz. That’s 200MHz more than the previous Core i9-13900KS that &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/1/12/23551748/intel-6ghz-processor-core-i9-13900k-release-date-price"&gt;launched last year&lt;/a&gt; and was the first desktop processor to break the 6GHz barrier at stock speeds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="0s2g5r"&gt;This new Core i9-14900KS will be priced at $689, $10 less than the previous 13900KS, and will be available in stores today. The 6.2GHz max turbo frequency is an out-of-the-box boost, so there could be room for overclocking to push these speeds even further. The 14900KS has the same 24 cores found on the 14900K, with eight performance cores and 16 efficiency ones. It does run at a 150-watt base power, though, instead of the 125 watts found on the 14900K.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="izY4O3"&gt;Other than the power and turbo frequencies, the 14900KS is almost identical to the 14900K. It’s essentially a “binned” version that has been selected to run at a higher clock speed. Z790 and Z690 motherboards will support the 14900KS with the latest BIOS updates.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt=" " data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/ag_9keaz8I54w7nQoTJ7ioNy7Rc=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25334268/14900ksbenchmarks.png"&gt;
      &lt;cite&gt;Image: Intel&lt;/cite&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;Intel’s own 14900KS benchmarks.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="qrM6w6"&gt;Intel is promising up to 15 percent better gaming performance from the 14900KS over the 13900KS and up to 73 percent for 3D production multitasking workflows over AMD’s Ryzen 9 7950X. It will be interesting to see just how well the 14900KS performs against AMD’s Ryzen 7 7800X3D, which has dominated PC gaming performance recently. Intel’s own benchmarks suggest the 14900KS may well beat the 7800X3D in some games.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="aUibof"&gt;The Core i9-14900KS will likely be one of the last LGA 1700 socket processors on the market, as Intel is moving to a new socket for its upcoming generation of CPUs. Retailers will start stocking the 14900KS on shelves today priced at $689. This new processor will also be available inside OEM systems, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TVFBbV"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Correction March 14th, 12:40PM ET:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this story stated the 14900KS started at $699. It starts at $689. We regret the error.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24099713/intel-core-i9-14900ks-release-date-price-features"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24099713/intel-core-i9-14900ks-release-date-price-features</id>
    <author>
      <name>Tom Warren</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <published>2024-03-14T06:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-14T06:00:00-04:00</updated>
    <title>How Nintendo’s destruction of Yuzu is rocking the emulator world</title>
    <content type="html">  

    &lt;figure&gt;
      &lt;img alt="Photo illustration of a Nintendo Switch with a broken screen and the Yuzu logo." src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/dAcb5U9gtPqdbOUGfmn4bjwKwsk=/0x0:2040x1360/1310x873/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/73206063/STK465_VIDEO_GAMES_CVirginia.0.jpg" /&gt;
        &lt;figcaption&gt;Cath Virginia / The Verge | Photos from Getty Images, The Verge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    &lt;/figure&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;The leading Nintendo Switch emulator is a smoking crater. Others are wary — but hopeful — for the future.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="p--has-dropcap" id="RqrFBU"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24090357/nintendo-yuzu-emulator-lawsuit-settlement"&gt;When Nintendo sued the developers of Yuzu out of existence on March 4th&lt;/a&gt;, it wasn’t just an attack on the leading way to play Nintendo Switch games without a Switch. It was a warning to anyone building a video game emulator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TgV2iz"&gt;Seven developers have now stepped away from projects, are shutting them down, or have left the emulation scene entirely. Of those that remain, many are circling the wagons, getting quieter and more careful, trying not to paint targets on their backs. Five developers declined to talk to &lt;em&gt;The Verge&lt;/em&gt;, telling me they didn’t want to draw attention. One even tried to delete answers to my questions after we’d begun, suddenly scared of attracting press.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="Ws9uQX"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12277492"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="eFuTt7"&gt;Not everyone is so afraid. Four other emulator teams tell me they’re optimistic Nintendo won’t challenge them, that they’re on strong legal footing, and that Yuzu may have been an unusually incriminating case. One decade-long veteran tells me everyone’s just a &lt;em&gt;bit&lt;/em&gt; more worried. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="8Ci5rO"&gt;But when I point out that Nintendo didn’t have to prove a thing in court, they all admit they don’t have money for lawyers. They say they’d probably be forced to roll over, like Yuzu, if the Japanese gaming giant came knocking. “I would do what I’d have to do,” the most confident of the four tells me. “I would want to fight it... but at the same time, I know we exist because we don’t antagonize Nintendo.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="b6FhGl"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/yuzu/comments/1bbaq4s/the_real_current_situation/"&gt;There’s a new meme&lt;/a&gt; where Yuzu is the mythical Hydra: cut off one head, and two more take its place. It’s partly true in how multiple forks of Yuzu (and 3DS emulator Citra) sprung up shortly after their predecessors died: Suyu, Sudachi, Lemonade, and Lime are a few of the public names. But they’re not giving Nintendo the middle finger: they’re treating Nintendo’s lawsuit like a guidebook about how &lt;strong&gt;not &lt;/strong&gt;to piss off the company. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="qvDFN6"&gt;In its legal complaint, Nintendo claimed Yuzu was “facilitating piracy at a colossal scale,” giving users “detailed instructions” on how to “get it running with unlawful copies of Nintendo Switch games,” among other things. Okay, no more guides, say the Switch emulator developers who spoke to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="X5GXuG"&gt;They also say they’re stripping out some parts of Yuzu that made it easier to play pirated games. &lt;a href="https://arstechnica.com/gaming/2024/03/heres-how-the-makers-of-the-suyu-switch-emulator-plan-to-avoid-getting-sued/"&gt;As &lt;em&gt;Ars Technica&lt;/em&gt; reported&lt;/a&gt;, a forked version called Suyu will require you to bring the firmware, title.keys, and prod.keys from your Switch before you can decrypt and play Nintendo games. Only one of those was technically required before. (Never mind that most people don’t have &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2018/4/24/17276214/nintendo-switch-hack-jailbreak-security-homebrew-apps-games"&gt;an easily hackable first-gen Switch&lt;/a&gt; and would likely download these things off the net.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="3iszMK"&gt;The developer of another fork tells me he plans to do something similar, making users “fend for yourself” by making sure the code doesn’t auto-generate any keys.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;figure class="e-image"&gt;
        &lt;img alt="tl;dr yuzu doesn’t require firmware or title.keys, just prod.keys, while suyu requires all three" data-mask-text="false" src="https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/eHBUL1mRMUHENSk4H1nsA303LeY=/400x0/filters:no_upscale()/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_asset/file/25333185/yuzu_vs_suyu.jpg"&gt;
      &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Suyu moderator sums it up for us.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
  &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="nsPUg4"&gt;Most developers I spoke to are also trying to make it clear they aren’t profiting at Nintendo’s expense. One who initially locked early access builds behind a donation page has stopped doing that, making them publicly available on GitHub instead. The leader of another project tells me nothing will ever be paywalled, and for now, there’s “strictly no donation,” either. When I ask about the Dolphin Emulator, which &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/6/1/23745772/valve-nintendo-dolphin-emulator-steam-emails"&gt;faced a minor challenge from Nintendo&lt;/a&gt; last year, I'm told it &lt;a href="https://opencollective.com/dolphin-emu"&gt;publicly exposes its tiny nonprofit budget&lt;/a&gt; for anyone to scrutinize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="4nJZil"&gt;But I don’t know that these steps are enough to prevent Nintendo from throwing around its weight again, particularly when it comes to emulating the Nintendo Switch, its primary moneymaker. One thing to know about this whole situation: the stakes are higher than they’ve ever been. Emulators have typically lagged behind new console generations since it can take a lot of horsepower to digitally replicate the functionality of a console and time to learn its secrets. But that hasn’t been true for Switch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="fhVs9h"&gt;Not only did hackers find &lt;a href="https://medium.com/@SoyLatteChen/inside-fus%C3%A9e-gel%C3%A9e-the-unpatchable-entrypoint-for-nintendo-switch-hacking-26f42026ada0"&gt;an unprecedented vulnerability&lt;/a&gt; in the original Switch less than a year after release, the emulator scene also managed to develop software that plays Switch games &lt;em&gt;better than the Switch itself &lt;/em&gt;within its own lifespan. They muscled in on Nintendo’s turf by competently running on Switch-style portable devices like the Steam Deck as well as some phones. YouTubers published tutorials on emulating Switch games, some of which Nintendo &lt;a href="https://www.eurogamer.net/steam-deck-nintendo-emulation-videos-are-disappearing-from-youtube"&gt;reportedly threatened with copyright claims&lt;/a&gt;; Valve even (&lt;a href="https://kotaku.com/yuzu-nintendo-switch-emulator-steam-deck-dock-valve-1849632836"&gt;briefly&lt;/a&gt;) showed the Yuzu emulator in an official Steam Deck video.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="Cnt7Vi"&gt;
&lt;div class="iframely-embed"&gt;&lt;div class="iframely-responsive" style="height: 500px; padding-bottom: 0;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Steam/comments/xy8s0g/valve_reuploaded_the_latest_steam_deck_video_to/" data-iframely-url="https://cdn.iframe.ly/api/iframe?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FSteam%2Fcomments%2Fxy8s0g%2Fvalve_reuploaded_the_latest_steam_deck_video_to%2F&amp;amp;key=9ef4a209439e42bc59783ba959d50197"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script async="" src="https://cdn.iframe.ly/embed.js" charset="utf-8"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="i5U1BM"&gt;But the speed of technology may also make it easier for Nintendo to challenge emulators, several developers admit. While Nintendo didn’t begin properly introducing encryption until the Wii, the Switch apparently has five different layers of encryption, and Nintendo’s complaint against Yuzu primarily alleged that the emulator was encouraging users to circumvent them. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="SOGa8E"&gt;That’s an argument that hasn’t yet been tested by the courts, and there’s at least one major reason to think Nintendo might not win if it tried. Section 1201 of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act &lt;em&gt;does&lt;/em&gt; allow people to narrowly circumvent copy protection for “interoperability of an independently created computer program with other programs,” and the Dolphin Emulator team &lt;a href="https://dolphin-emu.org/blog/2023/07/20/what-happened-to-dolphin-on-steam/"&gt;has publicly argued&lt;/a&gt; that would even extend to sharing decryption keys. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;aside id="yt6TG8"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="readmore" data-anthem-component-data="{&amp;quot;stories&amp;quot;:[{&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Read the emails: Valve helped Nintendo kick the Dolphin Emulator off Steam&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;url&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://www.theverge.com/2023/6/1/23745772/valve-nintendo-dolphin-emulator-steam-emails&amp;quot;},{&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Dolphin emulator gives up on Steam — but won't remove Wii decryption key&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;url&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://www.theverge.com/2023/7/20/22302205/dolphin-emulator-steam-legal-argument&amp;quot;}]}"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="fTv5xw"&gt;But many earlier emulators would never have faced that kind of challenge, and again, no developer has the money to fuck around and find out. “We’re lucky that the systems we’re using are simpler, they don’t have the advanced encryption techniques,” says one developer who focuses on early Nintendo consoles. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="7OhXQk"&gt;Another suggests that the safest emulators are for consoles so old or emulated at so high a level, they don’t even require users to bring a copyrighted BIOS. Sony PSP emulator PPSSPP, for example, &lt;a href="https://www.ppsspp.org/docs/faq/#:~:text=Do%20I%20need%20a%20BIOS%20file%20to%20run%20PPSSPP%2C%20like%20I%20would%20with%20PSX/PS1%20and%20PS2%20emulators%3F"&gt;can help defend itself by saying&lt;/a&gt; it emulates everything, including a BIOS and operating system, using its own code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="EZontQ"&gt;But the longer I talk to them, the clearer it becomes that the emulator faithful have been slightly shaken by the collapse of Yuzu. None seem completely convinced that Yuzu was doing it wrong. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;aside id="Rin2Pq"&gt;&lt;q&gt;First rule of emulator club: you do not talk about piracy&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="qnD0sp"&gt;“The Yuzu Discord was really careful about not mentioning piracy — they even scanned the logs from bug reports to check whether the people are using self-made copies of games,” one fork contributor tells me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="TOCaYA"&gt;“They had a metaphorical gun to their heads,” says another, calling bullshit &lt;a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24090357/nintendo-yuzu-emulator-lawsuit-settlement#:~:text=also%20says%20Yuzu%20is%20%E2%80%9Cprimarily%20designed%20to%20circumvent%20and%20play%20Nintendo%20Switch%20games.%E2%80%9D"&gt;on Yuzu’s admission&lt;/a&gt; that it was “primarily designed to circumvent and play Nintendo Switch games” and thus broke the law. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="U3o1mA"&gt;None of the developers I spoke to have a tremendous amount to lose. It’s not their livelihoods at stake, and they don’t have extra mouths to feed. But they’re still relying on the good graces of companies like Nintendo. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="c-float-left c-float-hang"&gt;&lt;div id="w4WcHV"&gt;&lt;div data-anthem-component="aside:12279375"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="95A8lC"&gt;The big companies do sometimes profit from letting emulation run its course. You can download classic games for the Nintendo Switch and PlayStation 5 &lt;em&gt;today&lt;/em&gt; because of emulators. Nintendo is said to have hired from the scene for &lt;a href="https://www.nerd.nintendo.com/"&gt;its own in-house emulation team&lt;/a&gt;, and Sony definitely did, hiring at least one developer of the PlayStation 2 emulator PCSX2 &lt;a href="https://www.timeextension.com/features/meet-the-company-bringing-classic-games-to-switch-ps5-and-xbox-by-mistake"&gt;to bring PS2 games to PS4&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="c-end-para" id="sIQguy"&gt;Today, his company, Implicit Conversions, works with Sony to put PS1 and PSP games on PS5, with downloadable Sony games &lt;a href="https://www.implicitconversions.com/#:~:text=identification%20purposes%20only.-,Shipped%20Titles,-About%20Us"&gt;like &lt;em&gt;Twisted Metal &lt;/em&gt;and &lt;em&gt;Syphon Filter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;quietly powered by emulation.&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;It’s one reason to be optimistic: maybe Nintendo will see at least some benefit in leaving the rest of the scene alone.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.theverge.com/24098640/nintendo-emulator-yuzu-lawsuit-switch-aftermath"/>
    <id>https://www.theverge.com/24098640/nintendo-emulator-yuzu-lawsuit-switch-aftermath</id>
    <author>
      <name>Sean Hollister</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
